Crystal Geyser is the only     major US spring water bottled
at the mountain source.
[ Air horn blows ]
[ Dagny's "Backbeat" plays ]
Meredith: There are moments       when all the stars align.
When everything seems               as it should be.
♪
♪ Right now ♪                   Your life seems             to have sorted itself out.
♪ You got me feeling like     I can't believe I let you go ♪
It's not like              all our problems go away.
Oh, no.              What?
We fell asleep.
We fell asleep?                                     Yeah.
My kids will be up.               They'll see you.
Why is that                   such a bad thing?
I've been over here                 a lot lately.
And they've never seen you. Do you think that's an accident?
What, so you don't want me           to meet them?
Not in my bed.
Okay, I understand.                             Okay. [ Laughs ]
Not yet.                   Just tell me where to go.
Down the stairs     and out through the back door.
Okay,                    I'll be quiet as a mouse.
♪ If you really wanna dance              some more ♪
It's just that the problems        are suddenly manageable.
♪ We're                 borderline wasting time ♪
♪ Pick it up and tell me ♪
You feel so good,             you wonder if it's real.
♪ That you love me              like you did before ♪
♪ I understand, understand ♪
♪ I been feeling it so long ♪
♪ I'm flying                when I'm in your arms ♪                      [ Sighs ]
And if I've learned anything...        [ Knocking at door ]
♪ I'm burning up, burning up ♪     ...I can tell you...it is.
♪ Feeling like a kid myself                again ♪
It's very real...
[ Music stops ]
...but it will not last.
Are you Major Owen Hunt?
I am.
Sir, I'm Major William Allen.  This is Chaplain Jane Roosevelt.
We're with            the Army Human Resource Command.
♪
Is this about my sister,                    Megan?
Major, we have reason to believe              that...
[ Buzzing ]               [ Speaking distortedly ]
[ Breathing echoes ]
♪
[ Distorted speaking continues ]
[ Breathing echoes ]
♪
Captioning provided by          ABC Studios and ABC, Inc.
and brought to you by Ford.      We go further, so you can.
Richard: Just tell them               I'll need to push
my 3:00 lecture to 4:00.
Thank you.
Aren't you supposed to be                at counseling?
I went.                    I went three times.                                        Mm.
I barfed up                 all my childhood sadness.
I told them all my demons.
I participated.
I feel like                 I got enough out of it.
Edwards...
What I did was wrong.
I know. I'm sorry.
But I don't think I should miss  out on another day of education
because I didn't get a stupid    piece of paper signed.
Ah, you feel calm?              You feel controlled?
Yes, yes.
How's your throwing arm?
Retired.
Give it to me.
[ Pen clicks ]
Now get back to work. And if, uh, Dr. Minnick...
I will talk to Dr. Minnick.
You are                   the One True King, sir.
Get out of here.   [ Laughs ]
♪
What do you mean,              you're there? Where?
I hired a guy. He gave me      his name and where he works.
Turned out he was scheduled
to do a minimally invasive         conference here in L.A.
So, you're there         and Jo's husband is there.
Yeah,                  I'm looking right at him.
Alex!                     What are you doing?
I don't know.
[ Sighs ] I don't know          if I'm gonna do anything.
Come home.
I can't yet.
I gotta go.
Do I need a badge                  or something?
What do we have?
BP's 95 palp.
Somnolent, but responsive         to painful stimuli.
Stats are 92                 with 100 percent oxygen.
On my count,                   one, two, three.
It's an MVC?                                   Sort of.
Two people in one car drove off          a cliff on Admiral Way.
Do we have a name?                 Haven't seen an ID yet.
They didn't find a purse?
They didn't even find                   a blouse.
She came in                  dressed like this.
Why are people driving around     with no clothes on?
Passenger's next door.                Maybe he knows.
Talk to me!
Male passenger, 30s,
unconscious                 and intubated at the scene.
Vitals are stable.
Uh, large bruises,              right chest and abdomen.
Was he dressed?   Except for his pants.
So, these two                  were not driving.
They were parking.
The theory                 is they got overexcited
and popped the car                   into gear.
Premature acceleration.
You know, it happens               to a lot of guys.
People need to get busy            where God intended --
parking lots,                  where it's flat.
[ Both laugh ]
[ Buzzing ]              [ Distorted conversations ]
[ Elevator bell dings                 distantly ]
[ Breathing echoes ]
[ Elevator door thuds open ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
♪
[ Breathing echoes ]
[ Heartbeat ]
[ Distorted conversations ]
♪
[ Speaking distortedly ]
[ Buzzing continues ]
He's got a head lac, and they    both have abdominal injuries.
Uh, Bailey's here,              and I paged Dr. Grey.
You can jump in                   if you want,
but I think                  we got it covered.
[ Buzzing continues ]      [ Speaking distortedly ]
[ Distorted voice ]                     Okay.
[ Speaking distortedly ]
♪
Denise:                   Somebody please help, please!
Please!                   Please, someone help us!
My baby can't breathe!
Gary:                 She's choking on something.
[ Buzzing continues ]      [ Sobs ]
[ Baby choking ]
02 and crike kit, please?
Is she dying?
[ Sniffles, crying ]                         Mommy, is she dying?
Gary:                    She's choking on something.
Okay.
Move. Move!
[ April                    breathing quickly ]
Oh, my God!
Gary: Hey, stop!                  [ Baby crying ]
-Oh!                  -You're okay. You're okay.
How long                  had she been choking?
I don't know --
a -- a few minutes -- five?                        Page neuro.
The baby's brain may have been deprived of oxygen for too long.
Next time,                   call an ambulance.
What?
[ Crying continues ]
♪
We know how it feels to be       treated like a trophy.
Waxed and shined.
We have seen the glory come,     go, and come again.
But a Cadillac is no trophy.
What you see is our future,
And It will inspire every car    that follows.
♪
Starting Thursday at Kohl's
save on gifts for mom
and get Kohl's Cash for you!
Pick out a diamond              ring for just $79.99
and get $10 Kohl's Cash!
A cookware set
and get $20 Kohl's Cash!
Or the Fitbit Charge 2
and you'll get $30 Kohl's Cash!
Kohl's.
There's nothing more               important to me
than my vacation.
So when I need to                book a hotel room,
I want someone                 that makes it easy
to find what I want.
Booking.com gets it.
They offer free cancellation,
in case I decide to go from       kid-friendly to kid-free.
Now I can start relaxing
even before the vacation begins.
Your vacation is very important.
That's why Booking.com               makes finding
the right hotel for             the right price easy.
Visit Booking.com now
to find out why                 we're Booking.yeah
Hey Allergy Muddlers
Are you one sneeze away from    being voted out of the carpool?
Try ZYRTEC®
It's starts working hard at hour                one
And works twice as hard when you    take it again the next day.
Stk with ZYRTEC® and Muddle No                More®.
Know what makes retirement              less scary?                ("Mambo No. 5" playing)
Getting a check every month.
With an income annuity            from New York Life,
you pay some money up front
and then get checks           for the rest of your life.
One, two, three, four,                five checks.
Be good at life.                  New York Life.
Introducing McDonald's new       Signature Crafted Recipes.
Like the Maple Bacon Dijon                 burger.
Applewood smoked bacon with        sweet maple seasoning.
Grilled onions.
And a creamy Dijon sauce with a          hint of honey.
On chicken or seared beef.
When I'm with you...
...The rest of the world...
...Fades away.
So I got you something...
...That stands out...
...As beautifully as you do...
Jared has more              exclusive LeVian pieces
than any other jewelry            store in the world.
That's why he went to Jared.
Lower extremity deformity
with a large hematoma.
Can't find a pedal pulse.
Trauma panel,           type and cross her eight.
I hope the sex was good.
Is sex in a car                  ever that good?
All those windows...
[ Groaning ]                      Hey. Miss.
Hey, you're okay.         You're at Grey-Sloan Memorial.
I do need you to keep still             though, okay?
Abdomen's very distended.     Bring me the ultrasound now.
Is he alive?
Can you tell us your name?
Alison.
Please,                    is he -- he alive?
[ Coughing ]                                    Oh, oh!
-Rapid intubation.             -Oh, okay. Okay. Okay.
I need 7-O ET tube.
She has a lot of blood             in her abdomen.                          [ Coughing ]
Alison, we're gonna take you          up to the O.R. now.
[ Monitor beeping rapidly ]    Pressure's dropped,                  70 over 40!
She's bleeding out.
Hang blood on the infuser    and prep her for REBOA catheter.
No hemotympanum.
Battle sign                 behind the right ear.
He needs a head CT.
I need you to explain          why you're here, Edwards.
Yeah, I got a six-centimeter        oozing forehead lac here.
I'm gonna need a suture tray               when you're done.
You assigned counseling.         I've been counseled.
Andrew: Lactate 2.1,
crit is 42,                    labs are good.
I'm seeing fluid               in Morrison's pouch.
You went to counseling                 for a minute.
My paper's been signed              by Dr. Webber.
Oh, of course he did.
We need to clear him               for a liver lac.
And until we rule that out,                DeLuca,
we need to keep him             on close observation.
No, DeLuca.
That's all you, Edwards.    No, I can't.                     I'm on neuro.
You were. And now,       you're on babysitting duty.
[ Scoffs ] I'm sorry, two        horndogs crash their sexmobile,
and I don't get a surgery             out of it?
Well, lucky for you.      You can sew up my head lac.
[ Tool clatters ]                    [ Sighs ]
I should've just gone          to the stupid counseling.
Damn right you should have.
Page me                   when you get the scans.
[ Monitor beeping ]
♪
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, hey.          [ Laughs ]
What does that do?
This is epinephrine.
It's for cardiac arrest.
Do you know what that is?
Okay. So, we'll just put that         back there
and find out                  who you belong to.
Where are your parents?
Over here.
♪
She's breathing fine.
I think you can start                to feed her.
Yeah, what about                 her -- her brain?
The other doctor said               the oxygen, uh...
I think I found                something of yours.
Oh, my God.                                     Oh my gosh,                 where have you been?
Please keep a close eye on her.   It's very busy in here today.
Yeah, I got it. Gary, put the phone down.
Well, I'm texting Karen. Why are texting the nanny?
She's off this week.
Yeah, but there's, like,           a lot going on, right?
So, maybe she could just...
Erin, you have to stay               with Daddy, okay?
Her neurological exam                 looks fine.
Her reflexes are good.                She's alert.
I'd like to keep her here     for a few hours for observation
as a precaution,                    all right?
Yeah, okay.     Um, the other doctor...
[ Baby crying ]         ...the one who, um,               pounded on her --
what's his name?
Was that Dr. Hunt?                              Yes.
Uh, we'd like to talk to him                 if we could.
I'll, uh,                  tell him to come by.
What was that about? I don't know.
♪
[ Sighs ]
Hey. What are you doing?
Okay, uh...
Did you treat a choking baby                 this morning?
What,                are we not speaking now?
Yes! Why?
Uh, baby's in the PICU               for observation.
She looks good, but the parents            want to speak to you.
Why?                                       I don't know.
I don't know if they're upset              or if they just...
Upset                    because I saved their baby?
Look,                I am just the messenger.
They want to speak to you.
[ Sighs ]                   I'll talk to them.
Fine.
♪
[ Sighs ]
[ Mid-tempo music plays ]       [ Indistinct conversations ]
It's okay.                  I'll see you inside.
All right.
♪
Sorry to bug you.
Are --                    Are you Paul Stadler?
Hi. Do I know you?  No, but I know you.
I couldn't put down                  your paper
on new approaches to antibiotic  resistance to pathogens.
Ah, yes.              Thanks. Uh, that was fun.
It was part of                 a whole WHO thing.
Listen, I am this close          to a grant for IBS research,
and your stuff...
I'm sorry.
I'm Alex.
Stevens.
Uh, can I buy you a drink?
[ Laughs ]                       Absolutely.
♪ Dynamite ♪
[ Bottles clink ]
♪
♪ Baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ I think you dynamite ♪
♪ Oh ♪
[ Distorted laughing ]
♪ And that's all right ♪
♪ She kind of prehistoric ♪         [ Cellphone ringing ]
God, stop calling!
Ugh!
I told my girlfriend that,       "I will see you on Monday,"
but every 20 minutes, she's      like, "What are you doing?"
[ Both laugh ]
Out of town                 means out of town, bitch!
Paul.
Alex.
This is from your wife.
What?
[ Ringing continues ]
[ Both grunting ]
♪ Hunh ♪
♪ Ha ♪
♪ Whoo! ♪
♪
[ Sirens wailing ]
[ Door buzzes ]
[ Door clangs shut,                lock engages ]
♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
We, the entertainment-loving     people,
want all our rooms to be TV      rooms.
Because those are the best       rooms.
Because they have TVs in them.
And, when we're not in those     rooms,
we want our shows to go with us.
Anywhere?
You got that right, kid show     thing.
Get a DIRECTV all-included       package for 4 rooms.
Only $25 a month, price          guaranteed for 2 years.
Available for AT&T Unlimited     Plus customers.
Hi guys. It's great to be here.
In the desert.
At the mall.
On the mountain.
At school.
At the beach.
In the Big Easy.
Yeah.                            Yeah.
Today I want to show you guys
the next-gen Chevy Equinox.
What do you think?
That's pretty.
Pretty sexy.
It's all-wheel drive.                Look at that.
It looks aggressive.
But not overbearing.
It's not too big.
Not too small.
It looks like it can go
off-roading.
But at the same time,
it looks like a car you can         take to a nice event.
You can dress it up
or dress it down.
Seems like the perfect car              for anybody.
I would take it anywhere.
I want one.
I love it.
She's a bad mama jama.
Chevy stepped their game up.
Come.
Explore a place where you can    fly on the back of a banshee.
Walk under floating mountains.
And navigate a mystical river.
Welcome to a                world - beyond belief.
Pandora - The World of Avatar.
Only at the Walt Disney               World Resort.
It's the biggest news ever
at Olive Garden
Introducing new
Giant Stuffed Pastas             starting at $12.99.
Pastas so big                you could share them,
but so delicious,                you won't want to.
Giant Stuffed Pastas.
For a limited time                at Olive Garden.
WELCOME TO MAXX YOU.
YOU ARE WHIMSICAL, VIBRANT,           STATEMENT MAKING.
WE SEE WHAT MAKES YOU UNIQUE.
SO WE HAVE SOMETHING                FOR EVERYONE,
AT A PRICE THAT'S               JUST RIGHT FOR YOU.
MAXX YOU. MAXX LIFE.
T.J.MAXX
[ Air rushing ]
[ Monitor beeping ]
You doing a single              interrupted suture layer, then?
No,                  running a subcuticular.
Oh, even better.                Not conscious yet?
No. The girlfriend?   Still in the O.R.
His head CT is clear.  He has a grade-three liver lac.
Dr. Grey wants serial abdominal        exams and six-hour crits.
[ Monitor beeping rapidly ]    Oh, all right, sir.
Hold on. Hold on. All right, I'm gonna get this    out of your throat, okay?
One second,                 I'm gonna count to three
and                     you're gonna blow it out.
One, two, and three.
[ Coughing ]           There you go. Great job.
Okay.                                 [ Coughing ]
Get you sat up.                  Clear that airway.                       What's happening?
Okay.
What are you doing?
Sir, you are in the hospital,                     okay?
You had an accident.
Let's get started                 with your name.                                  [ Gasping ]
What's your name?                                     Keith.
Okay.                                     Keith, Keith,                  you're safe, okay?
We have Alison here, too.
Alison?                    Mm-hmm.
She's here?                  I-Is she all right?
Did you talk to her?
She was unconscious               when she came in.
Alison has pretty severe          internal injuries.
We've got her in surgery              right now.
Alison's in surgery?
Okay. Uh, uh,             w-when will she be out?
Oh, well,                  that's hard to tell.
I have to go.     No no, settle down.                 Settle down.
I have to go see her!     You need to stay in bed.
You're not going anywhere,             hold on.
Hold on. You need              to lie in bed, okay?
You have an injury                 to your liver.
If you move,              it can make it much worse.
I have to...
Look, we are gonna make sure     to let you know how she is
as soon as she's out,                    okay?                                               Okay.
Right now,                  I need you to relax.
Okay.
Okay?                                       Okay.
Thank you.                                     Thanks.
Great.
All right.
You're right.            It perfed the esophagus.
So, do you need                  to open him up?
No, I think we should wait a day             and keep him on TPN.
[ Switches clicking ]
I know this girl.                 She's trouble.
Hey, Erin.                     Whatcha doing?
What does this do?
This...
does that.
Whoa.                      Is that his ribs?
Mm-hmm, it's his ribs.                              What's that?
That little thing                  is a bullet.
Nuh-uh.              Uh-huh.
It broke his rib!
She's better at this                   than you.
[ Laughs ]
Did he die?
No, no, no.
I mean, it hurt a bunch,      but I think he'll be all right.
My dumb baby sister almost died.                  She choked.
And where are your parents?         Are they in the E.R.?
In the ICU.
I saw a man                  with only one ear.
Whoa, really?             Well, I'd like to see that.
Would you like to see that?            Sure.
Yeah, maybe you could show us          the one-eared man
on the way back to your folks.
What do you say?                           Yeah, come on.
[ Chuckling ]                     Yeah? Okay.
Okay.                      Is this him? Sir?
Uh, we think               this might belong to you.
I think we found you          a radiologist in training.
Gary: Yeah, thanks.          You're welcome.
Sorry about that.              No, no.
Thank you.            No worries.
That poor bloke                is losing his mind.
Yeah, some people               just need a nanny.
[ Pen clicks ]
So, do you want to, um,    come over for dinner tonight?
What about the kids?
With the kids.
You seem to like kids.           They seem to like you.
Yeah.
Yeah, sure. I mean,             maybe I could bring something.
Then you wouldn't                  have to cook.
That's okay.       I'll make something they like.
After they go to bed,                  you can...
stay.
Not all night,                 just...for a while.
Sounds good.
Edwards, I assume   your patient's awake and stable
if you felt comfortable                 leaving him.
Alert and oriented                  times three.
Lacs are repaired.               Vitals are stable.
He's looking for an update        on his girlfriend.
Oh, hey,                       is she awake?
Not yet.
How is her boyfriend, husband,    driving instructor?
Definitely not husband.
Dr. Pierce            repaired an aortic injury,
but she's not              out of anesthesia yet.
-Okay.                      -Why not husband?
'Cause car sex                is only for when it's new.
Or it could be cheating.
Or why do it?
Someone                   is always uncomfortable
with the gearshifts               and the consoles.
And just limbs,                    everywhere.
You people need                   bigger cars.
Keith was asking about her         as soon as he woke up.
Keith?                          Yeah, the copilot.
Ah.
She did the same thing.
-She asked about him first, too.               -Hmm.
[ Clicks tongue ]                They're in love.
That figures.
"That figures"?                 What do you mean?
Well,                 two people who are in love
would want to go to a beautiful    place to share their love.
It figures that            they would wind up bleeding
in the bottom of a canyon.
Wow.                                     That's so cynical.
That's what happened!
Keith wants to be here          when she wakes up, okay?
But Grey wants him immobile             for 24 hours.
Guys, maybe it wasn't love,        all right?                                    Woman: Dr. Avery.
It's not romance             we're talking about here.
It was emergency sex,
and they were                 just too damn horny
to remember                  the parking brake.
That's super cynical.
What is wrong                  with you people?
-Seriously.                         -Wow.
You should let him come see her. You should figure it out.
Why? Because Prince Charming's     kiss is gonna wake her up?
Prince Charming            has a grade-three liver lac
that could kill him                 if he moves.
-Cynic!                          -Cynic!
That's not -- whatever.
Amelia.
Okay, so this is fun.
Owen is giving me         the silent treatment now.
No. Not you, me.
I need your help.                                    What?
I invited him over tonight.
Nathan?
To meet the kids.
Wow.
I know. I feel...
Nervous.     ...nauseous.
I feel really sick.
Because you think           the kids will like him,
and then it'll fall apart
and he'll be gone         and the kids will be sad.
No, it's not that.                                It's that.
I know this because I'm  the queen of thinking this way.
I always think              everybody's gonna die.
Yeah, but you're crazy.            I'm just...sick.
Derek is dead.
Maggie is fine.
There is nothing in your way                   but you.
Let yourself have this.
Look at you                  being the sane one.
Moments.
I have moments.
[ Woman speaking indistinctly               on PA ]
Dr. Hunt?
Yes. You asked to see me?      Yes.
[ Voice breaking ]               Um, this morning...
This morning...
[Crying]                     ...you saved her.
You saved our baby girl.
I never could have done               what you did.
[ Buzzing ]           [ Speaking distortedly ]
[ Breathing echoing ]
♪
[ Distorted voice ]                   Stop it.
[ Distorted voice ]            We thought we lost her,
but you brought her back                  to us.
Stop it!
♪
[ Breathing heavily ]
[ Sighs ]
Two soldiers             came to the house today.
They said they found her.
They said they found Megan.
Owen, I'm so sorry.
♪
[ Breathing deeply ]
At least you know.
Maybe                you can find some peace.
They said                    that she's alive.
♪
♪ Hit it! ♪
♪ Now look what you made me do ♪
♪ You and me baby it takes two ♪
♪ Bringing new moves              to the old school ♪
♪ Time for the whole            world to enjoy the view ♪
♪ We can go left                They can go right ♪
♪ Save me a dance for             the end of the night ♪
♪ When I'm with                  you it's a party ♪
♪ Don't care where we're going ♪
♪ 1, 2, 3 get loose now! ♪
♪ It takes two to              make a thing go right ♪
♪ It takes two to              make it out of sight. ♪
♪I don't care about the funny       way you wear your hair♪
♪Someday you'll let me put my            comb up there♪
♪'Til then you're beautiful and            I just stare♪
Happy birthday.
I love it.
I am groot.
Yes, let's get tattoos. Perfect.
I am groot!
Someone's after you?
♪
I am groot!
I see it.
Yes!
So, uh...  Shhh...
Be the guardian of your galaxy    in the all-new Ford EcoSport.
Only in theaters May 5th.
♪
Where did we find the      inspiration for our new flavors?
It walked right in the door.
Introducing new Signature            Crafted Recipes.
Pico Guacamole.
Sweet Barbecue Bacon.
Maple Bacon Dijon.
Get a free medium Fries and soft drink in the McDonald's App with
purchase of any Signature        Crafted Recipe sandwich.
You bring your flavor to the                world.
We bring ours to you.
Wish your skin                    could bounce
back like it                       used to?
Neutrogena Hydro                 Boost Water Gel.
With hyaluronic acid
it plumps                     skin cells with
intense hydration                 and locks it in.
For supple,                     hydrated skin.
Hydro Boost.
From Neutrogena
Allergies with nasal congestion?
Find fast relief                behind the counter
with Claritin-D.
[ upbeat music ]
Strut past that aisle            for the allergy relief
that starts working in          as little as 30 minutes
and contains the best
oral decongestant.
Live Claritin Clear,             with Claritin-D.
[Mom] Now that the kids have           flown the coop,
this place is too big.
[Dad] We raised them from eggs.
[Brad] Try Apartments-dot-com.
It's easy to downsize. Oh, how           about Florida?
[Dad] The kids will love it!
[Brad] Change your apartment.          Change the world.
I lost my sight
when I was 14 years old.
So I really navigate the world              by touch.
When Dove asked me to try out          this body wash...
I was excited that it was foam.
It was so light and soft...
Not sticky.
It's light.
It's different.
It's foam.
[ Wind rushing ]
They said they found her                 in a basement
in a rebel-held                   neighborhood.
There was a raid,     and they just left her there.
She was there for, uh...
Where is she now?
[ Sighs ] Germany.                 Army Hospital.
Did you talk to her?                 How was she?
When is she getting here?                         I haven't...
No, I haven't.     Oh, my God, Evelyn.
What did your mother say?        H-Have you told her?
How do we -- How do we even know                that it's her?
What if it's not?
What if they --         What if they got it wrong?
I mean...                                      Owen.
They might have.               This might not be true!
-Okay.                   -It might not be true.
Well...
let's find out.
Let's find out for sure.
Okay.
[ Horns honk ]            [ Indistinct conversations ]
♪
Dr. Stadler's work
combined the worlds of fiber    optics and abdominal surgery...
♪ Word around town             and the whispers loud ♪
...forging the way          for an almost new specialty.
He started his research...
♪ The lights all show,           nobody makes a sound ♪
...when he was still a student          at Johns Hopkins,
showing an early interest                  in...
♪ From the rooftops,        hear 'em callin' out my name ♪
[ Sighs ]
Good luck out there. Yeah. Thanks.
♪ Sideways talking               never to my face ♪
You nervous?
No, I'm good.                I'm just about to make a speech.
[ Clears throat ]
I'm a friend of Brooke's.
♪ You don't want to be             the last to know ♪
Your wife, Brooke Stadler.
The one who left you.
Yeah, how's she doing?             Where is she now?
You don't get to know that.
You don't get to think about her                  ever again.
And if you come near her,
I will find you               and I will kill you.
♪ Can't say                 I never told you so ♪
You understand?
♪ Whoo, ooh, whoa, ooh ♪     Who are you?
Doesn't matter.         ...Paul Stadler.
[ Applause ]                          I know your name.
I know who you are.
And I'm watching you.
Dr. Paul Stadler.
Good luck.
♪ Can't say                 I never told you so ♪
♪ Whoo, ooh, whoa, ooh ♪          [ Applause continues ]
♪ Whoo, ooh, whoa, ooh ♪
♪ Remember my name,              remember my name ♪
Hey, Jo, it's me.
♪ Whoo, ooh, whoa, ooh ♪     [ Jo grunting ]
[ Door scrapes open ]
♪ Remember my name ♪
[ Jo choking ]
[ Grunts ]
Hey, Alex.                       [ Grunts ]
[ Thuds ]
[ Sniffles ]
Found her.
Thanks.
♪ You don't want to be             the last to know ♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Monitor beeping ]
Whoa.
Whoa, no!                              [ Grunting ]
No, no, no, no.               What did I tell you?
I have to go.                      What did I tell you?
Lie down. Lie down.
You're not supposed to move                 for 24 hours.
Your liver           could start bleeding again.
You could bleed out.
No. Let me go, okay?                                I can't.
I was the last face                she looked at.
And now she's gonna wake up          in a hospital
with a tube in her throat        and no idea how she got here,
and surrounded by strangers      and probably hurting like hell.
She's gonna be so scared.
You -- You don't know               how that feels.
Yeah, I do, actually.                     I do.
Then let me be there                   for her.
Let me be there                when she wakes up.
I-If she can just see me first,  she'll know she's okay.
S-She'll know,                a-and she won't be so scared.
Please?
Let me do that for her.
Help me.
Please.
Amelia: Nein,       ich versuche jetzt den status
den patienten zu finden.
Danke.
Yes, I'm calling on behalf              of Major Owen Hunt.
I'm looking for a patient.
Ask for Teddy Altman.
What?      Ask to talk to Dr. Altman.
Is there a Dr. Altman                    there?
Yes, I'll hold.
You speak German.
Hey, Dr. Altman.
This is Amelia Shepherd        from Grey-Sloan Memorial.
I, uh --
I work with Owen Hunt.
Yes.
No.
One sec.
I'm sorry.                       He won't --
Yeah, I'm -- I'm --    I'm calling about his sister.
Okay.
Uh, we just need                   to confirm...
Right.
No, uh,             could we transfer her here
as soon as she touches down?
Yes, transfer to Grey-Sloan.
Thank you so much.
She said                 she tried to call you.
Megan is being transferred              from Landstuhl now.
She will land at Madigan.    [ Scoffs ]
And then,                 we'll bring her here.
We -- We don't even know             if it's her.
Owen, Teddy knows her.
Teddy saw her.
♪
[ Sniffling ]
I called Merritt Campbell.
She's the best PTSD expert              there is right now.
She'll be here                   in the morning.
Yeah, well, let's just wait      and see how Megan is...
Okay.                    But I meant for you.
For you, too.
♪
[ Chuckles ] I got married         right over there.
And I got divorced.
Then, I got married again.           [ Chuckles ]
Then I went on                    with my life.
And I left Megan               in a hole in the ground
for almost 10 years.
Weeks would go by, and I...      didn't give her a thought.
I couldn't spare her                   a thought
when she was being held             and tortured...
...and I don't know what.
♪
I stopped looking.
[ Crying ] I gave up.
I gave up on her.
I gave up.
[ Crying ]
♪
[ Elevator bell dings ]
[ Elevator door opens ]
[ Button clicks ]
So, Alison's waking up?
Oh, you're not cynical.
No, you're the one                 that's cynical.
Maybe they were in love,         or maybe they were just horny.
It doesn't matter.                                    Okay.
We all love,
and we all get horny,            and we all get hurt,
and then we come through            the other side.
And we get to help them                do that.
We get to help them                  love again.
Or screw again.
Either way. Win-win.
But I-I think they're in love.      I choose love.                                     Yeah.
What do we have to be cynical     about? Is my point.
Oh, that --                  that's your point.
Got it.            Shut up.
[ Elevator bell dings,                doors open ]
♪
[ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Elevator bell dings ]
Is she waking up?
Yes, starting to.           Avery, you need something?
Jackson:                     No, just curious.
Okay. Alison.
[ Groans ]                        Alison. You with us?
[ Groans ]
What happened?
You were in an accident.
Is he dead?                    Did I kill him?
Oh. No, no, no, it's okay.          You didn't do anything.
Please tell me                    I killed him!
What did you say?
There was a man in my car.
Y-Yes. Yes, he's here.                 We have him.
No. He -- He got into my car,  and he put a knife to my throat!
[ Sniffles ]            He made me drive to the woods.
He was trying to rape me.
And I thought, "No.
No. I'm not letting you                 do this.
I'm not gonna let you do this,      not even if it kills me."
A-And I hit the gas.
Please t-tell me he's dead.
Call security.
Stephanie's with him.
♪
I am breaking the rules                   for you.
So be very still, okay?
Thank you so much.              You are a lifesaver.
All right.            Let's get you out of here.
♪
How's it going?
Oh, it's going good.
Yeah, it's going good.           This is uh, this is my jam.                               Yeah?
Yeah, it's going good.           This is uh, this is my jam.                        What is that?
What?
The moment you realize the             gardening gene
skipped a generation.
At Lowe's, our grow together            planting system
takes the guess work out of      creating a beautiful yard.
All projects have a                starting point.
Start with Lowe's.
Hey, it looks good huh?
Not bad.
Now get 2 select hanging baskets      or planters for only $10
at the Lowe's           "Outdoor Entertaining Event."
♪
If you want to be          a world traveler, start by...
Ooh, is that a Galaxy S8?
Handsome screen.
Well, pack that...
...oop, oh OK,                 we're moving fast.
You'll need a tour guide.
Apparently not.
Don't forget a big camera.
Or that phone will work.
Traveling by yourself                can be lonely.
And...                you've already made friends.
♪
OK, I guess you have the      world traveler thing covered.
Right now at Kohl's
get 25% off Nike for mom.
That's 25% off select Nike     shoes, apparel and accessories
just in time for Mother's Day!
And, everyone gets                  Kohl's Cash!
Earn it on everything!
Spend it on anything!
Right now at Kohl's.
[ Horn honks ]
Oh! [ Panting ]
[ Taxi door opens ]                           Paul: Ah.
Oh, sorry. I tho--          I thought this was mine.
Um, you going to the airport?              You wanna split it?
[ Horn honks ]
No, I'll --                 I'll let you have this one.
I'll get the next one.
Thanks, man.
[ Sighs ]
[ Taxi door closes ]
Airport, please.
♪
[ Elevator bell dings ]
ICU is reserved for,               uh, family only,
so I'm gonna fudge it.
Just follow my lead, okay?
[ Men panting ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
Brody, Brody, Brody.               What's going on?
Someone was assaulted.                          What?
Yeah, I heard                a patient got raped.
They're looking                   for the guy.
Hey, hey. No, no!           Don't get up. Don't get up.
[ Grunting ]       [ Gasps ]
[ Breathing quickly ]
Now, you're gonna show me             the way out of here.
Okay?
♪
[ Lock disengages ]
Okay, backpacks upstairs.
Let's get you guys changed.
Mommy has a friend coming over             for dinner.
Zola: Is it Owen?
No, it's someone                 you haven't met.
Then why is Owen here?
I don't--                    What's going on?
Why don't you get the kids                 squared away
and we'll talk upstairs?
Okay. All right.             Let's go, guys. Come on.
♪
This guy's been            an absolute train wreck...
He -- He said...
I said some place              where people don't go,
like a service elevator.                       I know. I know.
Are you screwing with me?                                 No.
'Cause if you are...                   We just -- We just have to              get past him, okay?
Then we're fine.
And I said, "I don't know       how he could have broken it
playing Ping-Pong,"         [Chuckling] but, you know...
Look, just give him a script     for Keflex and send him home.
Woman: You got it.               Thanks, Dr. Warren.
Hey.                   Um, y-you need a hand?
No, no.                  We're fine. We're good.
Liver lac.              Taking him for a test drive.
Really?
Yeah, Minnick's orders.
All right.                      [ Chuckles ]
All right.
All right,                   where are we going?
Here.
[ Beeps ]
Aah!
♪
You think you're funny,                  huh?
No, this goes right down             to the loading dock.
You think it'll be funny         when I cut your throat?
It's either this, or...
You told me I can't walk,
and now you're sending me          down the stairs?
You're trying to kill me!
It's either this   or the elevator with the police.
It's just this -- this is --           this is what you want.
Here.               Let me give you the card.
No!
No, no.
No, you're not gonna run         and tell them where I am.
You're gonna help me             down the stairs, all right?
Move.
[ Breathes sharply ]
I want someone with that woman            every second.
I want two officers                 on this door.
Patient's gone. So is Edwards.       I can't find her anywhere.
She's not responding                 to any texts.
Call a Code Orange.             Lock this place down.
♪
Keith: [ Grunting ]
Stephanie:                  [ Whispering indistinctly ]
Oh, will you quit                 that praying?!
I'm not praying.
Then what                   do you keep saying?
I'm saying, "Please bleed out.    Please bleed out."
Yeah, I guess                 I kinda am praying.
Shut up.
Aah!
Aah!                                 I said don't try anything.
[ Breathing heavily ]
See?                       See what happens?
If you...
[ Door opens ]
[ Door closes ]
[ Gasping ]
In here.
♪
[ Sniffles ]
[ Indistinct conversations ]
Erin: Hi.            [ Gasps ] What the hell?
You need to go.
You need to go out that door --        okay? -- right now.
It won't open again.
[ Whispering ]                      Shut up.
[ Sniffles ]                     Hey, sweetie.
What's your name?                             Don't --
Erin.
Erin,                    where are your folks at?
In the ICU with my baby sister                  who choked.
You need to go, okay?               Wait.
And I'll let you out, okay?         Hold on!
[ Gasps ]
It's all right,                    sweetheart.
Don't. Don't.             I'm just gonna let her out,
and then you and I can keep    going where we're going, okay?
No. She'll tell them                 what she saw.
She doesn't know                   what she saw.
I want my mom.                Okay?
Then we'll just go.                   We'll go.
Leave her locked in here,      and we'll go down the stairs.
And by the time they find her,     we will be long gone, okay?
Yeah, okay.                                 Okay.
Okay.
[ Beeping ]
No.
No, no!            Open it!
I can't. I can't.                    I can't!
It's locked.                  We're in lockdown.
Why?
Because a rapist                is in the hospital.
What,                    we're trapped in here?
We're trapped in here.
♪
Hi Guys. It's great to be here.
In the desert. At the mall.      On the mountain. At school.
At the beach.                    In the Big Easy.       Various: Yeah. Yeah.
Today I want to show you guys    the next-gen Chevy Equinox.
What do you think?              Woman:                       That's pretty.
Woman 2:                         Pretty sexy.
It's all-wheel drive.               Look at that.
Man:                     It looks aggressive.
Woman 3:                   But not overbearing.
It's not too big.                  Not too small.
It looks like it could              go off-roading.
But at the same time,            it looks like a car
you could take                   to a nice event.
You can dress it up              or dress it down.
This part's awesome.
Moderator:                       The all-new Equinox comes        with built in 4G LTE Wi-Fi.
There's Wi-Fi?
Moderator:                       Even a bird's-eye                surround vision camera.
Woman 4:                         Wow, it shows                    the view from up above?
How's it doing that?                   (Laugh)
Boy:                  I really like the sunroof.
Children:                What? Woah! Hello, world!
I feel like I'm only             saying good things.
Which is annoying.                   (Laughter)
Moderator:                       And all it takes to open         the Chevy Equinox liftgate
is the motion of your foot.               (Laughter)
Easy peasy.
I could definitely               get a lot in there.
I could put my entire            band's equipment...
Various:                         Snowboard. Surfboards.           Mountain bike.
Even a sousaphone                would fit in there.              Yeah.
What's a sousaphone?                        (Laughter)
Seems like the perfect           car for anybody.
I would take                     it anywhere.
I want one.                      I love it.
She's a bad mama-jama.
(Laughter)
Man 4:                Chevy stepped their game up.
Introducing McDonald's new       Signature Crafted Recipes.
(Laughter)              Like the Sweet Barbecue Bacon              sandwich.
Tangy barbecue sauce made with            sweet onions.
Thick cut Applewood smoked                 bacon.
And topped with crispy, golden               onions.
On chicken or seared beef.
Need a fast absorbing                 moisturizer?
Try NIVEA In-Shower body lotion.
Wash.
Apply. It absorbs fast.
For 24 hour moisture.
Quickly rinse for smoother skin.
Ready to go!
NIVEA In-Shower Body Lotion.
Also available with                 Cocoa Butter.
♪ ♪ ♪
TAKING A CHANCE IS TOUGH.
WASHING COTTON IS EASY.
OH LIECHTENSTEIN...
IT'S L-I-C-T-H,
NO L-I-T-C-H, L-I-C-T?
OK GOOGLE,             HOW DO YOU SPELL LIECHTENSTEIN?
LIECHTENSTEIN IS SPELLED:                L-I-E-C-H-
YEAH THAT'S WHAT I MEANT.
In my experience there are only   two things guaranteed to grow,
the cash value of your           New York Life policy,
a policy that keeps             your family protected.
And my famous Crenn Soufflé,
which literally                never stops growing.
Be good at life.
New York Life.
Quin was crazy about curls.
But it took a twist of fate
to find a high-end curler      at such a head turning price.
And that's the beauty of        a store full of surprises.
You never know what               you're gonna find,
but you know                you're gonna love it.
♪
AAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA!!!!!
Tom?
SNICKERS® Satisfies.
So, and you're sure                  it's her?                                       It's her.
The Army won't tell you          unless they're certain.
And when is she coming?
Now. Tomorrow.
Does Nathan know?
No. Owen hasn't even told                   his mom,
so, no,               Nathan doesn't know yet.
I'll tell him.
Well, if he's coming over,                  just wait.
No. If Derek were alive,
I would want to know                  right now.
Can you watch...                                     Yeah.
Okay, Ellis                  needs her stuffie.
Story and bed by 8:00.
Yeah.
[ Insects chirping ]         [ Indistinct conversations ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
-Have they found him yet?                  -No.
And no word from Edwards?
No, and I can't                go looking for her.
I'm stuck here.    [ Sighs ]
Sit down.                                        [ Sighs ]
Sit down.
Look.
There are cops everywhere.
They'll find her.
I know. I just...
I left her                  in the room with him.
[ Beep at door ]
[ Police radio chatter ]
You know...
he probably got out
before they even called                 the lockdown,
or they would've found him.
He's long gone.
Well, if that's true,
then why isn't she answering          her texts?
Maybe it's locked on             the other side of a door         from where she is.
I can't get to my phone                  right now.
Yeah. Maybe so.
I mean, maybe.
Hey, she's okay.
Edwards is fine, all right?                  She's fine.
You're not cynical.
I'm not cynical enough.
I was actually rooting                   for them.
You made up a good story           about a patient.
Every one of us                  has done that.
I liked your version a hell of   a lot better than the real one.
♪
[ Grunting ]
Why is he so mad?       [ Thumping on door ]
He's, uh,                    having a bad day.
-[ Grunts ]             -Let's just stay quiet, okay?
I wanna go to my mom.           I want my mom and dad.
Ugh! There's gotta be             a way out of here!
There's got to be a way               to open it!
There isn't,                 or I would've tried.
You open the door                   right now!
I can't, okay?                      I can't!
Nothing                 is gonna open those doors
except security             calling off the lockdown.
Or -- Or, like,                emergency services.
W-What --                    What do you mean?
It's like -- like a fire.          A fire or something.
[ Breathing quickly ]
♪
Come on.
Come on, come on, come on!             Come on.
♪
Give me something     that I can start a fire with.
No. No! You can't.
You're not --                You can't start a fire in here!
Shut up, okay?
I'm just gonna set off                the sprinklers.
Make the doors open.       There'll be an evacuation.
Now, what can I use?
No, that's crazy.              You're gonna kill us all.
Erin: Will this work?
[ Breathes sharply ]
Will this make a fire?
[ Breathing quickly ]
You're a good girl.
♪
You got it. Atta girl.              Bring it here.
Set it on the floor              right there.                                    Stop it. Stop it.
Now, go in there and get         one of those blue things.
Stop making her help you.   You can help me.
And I can stand here with her.        Either way.
Now -- Now, squirt that stuff    all over the blue thing.
Don't do it. Don't do it, Erin!            Don't do it. Don't --
She's not              starting a fire for you.
Dammit!                                     Don't do it.
Dammit!
Come here. Come here.
-Come here.                     -Come to me.
Hey, hey, hey.                You -- You stay right there.
Right there.
You stay right there.
♪
I don't like him.
Stephanie: It's okay.             He's gonna go soon.
[ Grunting ]
[ Sighs ]
Okay, okay.
Okay.
Now, when the doors unlock,
I'm gonna take your card            and the girl...
No! No, no.
Nobody's gonna stop a guy
carrying a kid                out of a burning building.
No, she stays with me.
[ Chuckling ]                 No, you stay here.
Someone will find you               at some point.
[ Sparker clicking ]       [ Grunting ]
♪
Okay, Erin.                 My name is Stephanie.
I want you to do me a favor.             Okay?
I just want you to turn around   and cover your eyes.                                      Okay.
Like hide and seek.                                    Okay.
Okay, turn around.               Keep them covered.
Meredith: There are days
when you feel like           you can conquer anything.
[ Spker clicking ]                Keith: [ Grunting ]
♪
[ Fire ignites ]
Yeah, yes.
[ Chuckling ] Yes!
Come on.
Come on!
[ Breathing quickly ]              Come on. Come on.
[ Breathing heavily ]
♪
And it feels like everything            will be okay.
[ Breathing quickly ]
♪
[ Fire crackles ]
[ Screaming ]
♪
[ Panting ]
[ Groaning ]
Li I told you,              the feeling doesn't last.
I'm not trying to be cynical.
It's just that, even when    a day starts out so, so well...
Keith: [ Groaning ]
[ Breathing quickly ]            Oh, it's okay. It's okay.
You're okay, all right?          You're okay. We're okay.
[ Sniffling ]
We're gonna go.
I'm gonna take you              to see your parents.
It's okay.
[ Groaning continues ]
[ Groaning stops ]
♪
Oh, God.
Oh, no.
What is it?
Go. Go all the way                over there, okay?
Stay over there!
No! Stephanie.
I'll be right back, okay?
...that day can end...              [ Door opens ]
♪
[ Explosion, glass shattering ]
[ All gasping ]
[ Explosions ]
...so, so badly.
[ Curtis Mayfield's             "Move On Up" plays ]           I can confirm that, yes,         as of early this morning,
United States forces         have successfully dismantled
all the remaining drones.
[ Reporters clamoring ]                  Carol.
Carol: What about             the people responsible?
Unfortunately,               I'm unable to tell you
anything more at this time.
The important thing           to remember here, folks,
is that the threat                  is now gone.
Are there                   any more questions?
[ All speaking indistinctly ]
With all this behind him,
what will President Grant             be focusing on
in his final days                   of office?
The President                 will continue to be
both passionate and eager,                 Carol,
with a long list of interests      he still hopes to tackle.
♪ Toward your destination ♪      [ Both breathing heavily ]
♪ Though you may find             from time to time ♪                  [ Laughs ]
♪ Complication ♪                      Marcus:                  The transition of power
will be both successful                 and easy,
not just                 for the President-Elect,
but for the country                   as well.
Today, Americans             should be feeling excited
about what lies ahead,
invigorated             by the promises of tomorrow.
Well...                     [Exhales deeply]
...what do you think?
I think you                  should have told me
what a maid of honor                  has to do.
Well, is it too much?                 Not enough?
♪ Bite your lip ♪              No.
You look beautiful.
♪ And take a trip ♪
Now, I don't have              too many more chances
to stand up here in front of        all you lovely people,
and, well,                  avoid your questions.
[ Laughter ]                  ♪ Just move on up ♪
But, I, for one,                am more optimistic
about this country's future          now more than ever.
We may just have another        week-and-a-half left here,
but we are not done.
We're not even close                to being done.
♪ So hush now, child ♪                    Nine more days                    left of this.
Nine more days.
♪ And don't you cry ♪
[ Laughs ]
Trust me, people,             when we're finished...
♪ Your folks                might understand you ♪               ...you'll know.
♪ By and by ♪               [ Both exhale sharply ]
[ Laughs ]
♪ Move on up ♪
-- Captions by VITAC --
Captioning provided by          ABC Studios and ABC, Inc.
and brought to you by Ford.      We go further, so you can.
[ Door opens ]
Rowan:                Mr. Rosen, of all the people       I expected to see me off,
you were not on the list.
You're leaving?          I am.
Retiring.
My work here                   is finally done.
[ Chuckles ]                     At long last.
She is headed off
to the American Museum             of Natural History,
and I am heading off             to white sand beaches,
crystal-blue water.
I trust                     you are not here
to try to keep that                from happening.
No. No, no, no.          Good.
Because the assassination of            Frankie Vargas
is a closed case,                   is it not?
It is, yes. Absolutely.
No, I'm not here             in any official capacity.
Ah.                                     I'm here...
Well, I'm here               to ask about Samantha,
the mean one                  with the ponytail.
She and I, we were --   Yes. I know.
I've been trying to figure out           what her real name is.
She gave me another one      during the interrogation --
Grace Dennis --           but it was another dead end.
She ever                   say anything to you,
leave anything behind
that might help me                  identify her?
A credit-card receipt?       Mnh-mnh.
She had a toothbrush             in my bathroom, red.
I threw it away.
Now I wish                     I had kept it.
I could run her DNA              through the system,
identify her that way.
Or perhaps, Mr. Rosen,
it's time to move on?
If you knew                how it felt to be used,
someone                   pretends to love you
and then uses you to try          to torpedo democracy...
But you're                   leaving on a trip,
and I'm taking up                   your time.
Safe travels.
Wait.
I, um...
I may have something               that could help.
♪
These all pardon petitions?                       Fitz: Uh-huh.
I need to choose             which convicted prisoners
to pardon                 by the end of the week.
You know you have                dozens of people
to sort through these                  for you.
I'm being thorough --
hands on.          [ Giggles ]
You're being irresponsible,
because you're scared.
Scared? Of what?
Of Abby.
Of trusting Abby.                  [ Papers fall on table ]
I want this done right.       Hmm.
You need to talk to her,                   Fitz.
Have the difficult                  conversation.
Either you let her back in           or you let her go.
Don't you have another President          to challenge and annoy?
I do.
Mm.
[ Door closes ]
♪
[ Camera shutter clicking ]
Abby: Today's schedule --
You've got Marcus at 11:00.
He'll prep you               for the BNC interview,
tell you what kind of questions  you're likely to be asked.
Then at 2:00 we've got Ackerman  coming over for pardons.
His aide gave me a heads up              last night
about which petitions              he'll be pushing.
I could stay --
tell you which ones                I'd recommend.
It's being taken care of.
Why don't you take               the rest of the day              and work from home?
Everything's good here.