♪
>> Announcer: TODAY --
WE'RE MAKING YOUR WEEKNIGHTS
EASY WITH DELICIOUS DISHES THAT
PACK A PUNCH!
IT'S TIME FOR "THE CHEW'S"
WEEKNIGHT WOWS!
MARIO'S CUTTIN' FOOTLOOSE IN THE
KITCHEN WITH THE
INCREDIBLE KEVIN BACON!
THEN -- REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK
CONTINUES -- AND CLINTON'S
TEAMING UP WITH MICHAEL TO MAKE
A MEDITERRANEAN FAVORITE THAT'LL
LEAVE YOU STUFFED!
PLUS CARLA'S HANGING WITH THE
STAR OF "SCANDAL" --
DARBY STANCHFIELD!
WE'RE GETTING WOWED, RIGHT NOW,
ON "THE CHEW"!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>>> HELLO AND WELCOME TO "THE
CHEW"!
THANK YOU, GUYS!
YOU KNOW, IF YOUR MONDAY WAS
"MEH" AND YOUR TUESDAY WAS
"TIRED" -- THEN GET READY TO
HAVE YOUR WEEK SHAKEN UP!
OUR DISHES TODAY ALL PACK A
"POW" AND WILL MAKE YOU SAY --
>> Audience: WOW!
>> WOW!
IT'S AN HOUR OF QUICK AND EASY
"WEEKNIGHT WOWS"!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WOWSER!
>> HOW YOU GUYS DOIN'?
>> FANTASTIC!
>> GREAT!
>> HUMP DAY!
HAVE YOU HAD ANY "WEEKNIGHT
WOWS" LATELY -- MEAL-WISE?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I WAS LIKE, "YES."
>> OH, REALLY?
OKAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> LYING!
>> LYING.
>> OH, I HAD ONE.
>> NO, HE WAS TALKING ABOUT LIKE
WITH -- YOURSELF.
>> OH!
>> WE SAY "WOW."
YES.
>> OKAY, GO ON.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING --
>> THINK ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
>> CARLA HALL LIVE FROM THE
BEDROOM.
"I'M TAKIN' A NAP!"
>> NO, BUT IN TERMS OF FOOD, I
HAVE.
>> WHAT'D YOU COOK?
>> I COOKED A MOROCCAN BEAN
SALAD AND INSPIRATION WAS
FROM --
MORRIS CHESTNUT CAME TO THE
SHOW.
>> OH, YEAH.
>> AND HE HAD HIS BOOK, "THE
CUT."
AND SO ONE OF THE RECIPES --
THIS BEAN SALAD IS NOT YOUR
MOMMA'S, NOT YOUR SOUTHERN "AT A
PICNIC", THREE BEAN, SLOPPY
SALAD.
THIS IS A SPICY --
IT IS DELICIOUS.
IT HAS HARISSA AND ONIONS AND
CARROTS AND HERBS.
>> IT LOOKS GOOD.
>> IT IS SO FREAKIN' GOOD!
>> DID YOU HAVE THAT AS YOUR
MAIN COURSE?
>> I DID.
>> YOU DID?
>> WHAT ELSE DID YOU SERVE WITH
>> I DID.
IT?
>> WHAT ELSE DID YOU SERVE WITH
>> THAT WAS IT.
IT?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT WAS IT.
>> OH.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH.
YEAH, THESE ELECTRIC KISSES --
>> OH, MY GOD.
[ LAUGHTER ]
YEAH, THESE ELECTRIC KISSES --
THEY HAD MY EARRINGS POPPING
[ LAUGHTER ]
OFF!
THEY HAD MY EARRINGS POPPING
>> HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS?
OFF!
COOK ANYTHING GOOD THIS WEEK?
>> HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS?
>> I MADE A LITTLE, YOU KNOW --
COOK ANYTHING GOOD THIS WEEK?
BEEN A LITTLE BIT CRAZY AT THE
>> I MADE A LITTLE, YOU KNOW --
RESTAURANT, BUT LIZ AND I STILL
BEEN A LITTLE BIT CRAZY AT THE
TRY TO SIT DOWN FOR DINNER
RESTAURANT, BUT LIZ AND I STILL
BEFORE A SHIFT.
TRY TO SIT DOWN FOR DINNER
SO, WE MADE SOME RICOTTA RAVIOLI
BEFORE A SHIFT.
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF SAGE AND
SO, WE MADE SOME RICOTTA RAVIOLI
BROWN BUTTER.
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF SAGE AND
>> OH, THAT'S MY FAVORITE SAUCE
BROWN BUTTER.
IN --
>> OH, THAT'S MY FAVORITE SAUCE
>> I KNOW.
IN --
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> I KNOW.
THAT LOOKS SO GOOD.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> PLASTIC, PUT THE -- AND READY
THAT LOOKS SO GOOD.
COOKIE --
>> PLASTIC, PUT THE -- AND READY
>> I AM A GENIUS.
COOKIE --
>> STOLE THAT ONE RIGHT FROM --
>> I AM A GENIUS.
>> YEAH, BUT I STOLE -- RIGHT,
>> STOLE THAT ONE RIGHT FROM --
EXACTLY.
>> YEAH, BUT I STOLE -- RIGHT,
I STOLE THAT FROM MOLDOVAN
EXACTLY.
CULTURE FROM 200 YEARS AGO.
I STOLE THAT FROM MOLDOVAN
>> I KNOW.
CULTURE FROM 200 YEARS AGO.
IT'S SO GOOD THOUGH.
>> I KNOW.
THAT COOKIE JUST MAKES ALL THE
IT'S SO GOOD THOUGH.
DIFFERENCE.
THAT COOKIE JUST MAKES ALL THE
>> IT REALLY TURNS IT UP.
DIFFERENCE.
>> YEAH.
>> IT REALLY TURNS IT UP.
>> BUT WE COOK -- I COOK A LOT
>> YEAH.
ON THE WEEKDAYS JUST 'CAUSE IT'S
>> BUT WE COOK -- I COOK A LOT
SIMPLE AND FASTER.
ON THE WEEKDAYS JUST 'CAUSE IT'S
AND I'VE BEEN ROASTING CHICKENS
SIMPLE AND FASTER.
FOR
AND I'VE BEEN ROASTING CHICKENS
A LONG TIME.
FOR
MY WIFE, HOWEVER, DOESN'T LIKE
A LONG TIME.
IT WHEN IT'S A LITTLE PINK ON
MY WIFE, HOWEVER, DOESN'T LIKE
THE THIGH BONE, SO I'VE
IT WHEN IT'S A LITTLE PINK ON
SPATCHCOCKED THE CHICKEN --
THE THIGH BONE, SO I'VE
>> OH, YOU'RE A SPATCHCOCK.
SPATCHCOCKED THE CHICKEN --
>> AND THERE'S A PICTURE RIGHT
>> OH, YOU'RE A SPATCHCOCK.
THERE.
>> AND THERE'S A PICTURE RIGHT
>> YES!
THERE.
>> SPATCHCOCKED.
>> YES!
I LOVE IT OVER VEGETABLES THAT
>> SPATCHCOCKED.
GIVE THE LITTLE GREASY CHICKEN
I LOVE IT OVER VEGETABLES THAT
BITS DOWN BELOW.
GIVE THE LITTLE GREASY CHICKEN
AND THEN IT'S RAMP SEASON RIGHT
BITS DOWN BELOW.
NOW ALL OVER THE EAST COAST AND
AND THEN IT'S RAMP SEASON RIGHT
SOMETIMES IN THE MIDWEST, AND
NOW ALL OVER THE EAST COAST AND
EVEN ON THE WEST COAST.
SOMETIMES IN THE MIDWEST, AND
SO, JUST SAUTEED RAMPS WHICH
EVEN ON THE WEST COAST.
WERE KIND OF LIKE GARLICKY
SO, JUST SAUTEED RAMPS WHICH
ONIONS THAT YOU JUST SERVE ON
WERE KIND OF LIKE GARLICKY
THE SIDE.
ONIONS THAT YOU JUST SERVE ON
AND AS LONG AS YOU MAKE THE SAME
THE SIDE.
AMOUNT, THEN YOU CAN MAKE ALL --
AND AS LONG AS YOU MAKE THE SAME
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AMOUNT, THEN YOU CAN MAKE ALL --
>> I WANNA BRING UP A POINT REAL
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
FAST.
>> I WANNA BRING UP A POINT REAL
THE EAST COASTERS THINK THEY
FAST.
INVENTED RAMPS, BUT THEY'VE BEEN
THE EAST COASTERS THINK THEY
A MIDWESTERN STAPLE FOR A LONG
INVENTED RAMPS, BUT THEY'VE BEEN
TIME.
A MIDWESTERN STAPLE FOR A LONG
>> FIRST OF ALL, I AGREE WITH
TIME.
YOU.
>> FIRST OF ALL, I AGREE WITH
IT'S ONLY THE EAST COAST, BUT WE
YOU.
CHARGE $20.
IT'S ONLY THE EAST COAST, BUT WE
[ LAUGHTER ]
CHARGE $20.
>> WILL THAT JUST COVER IT?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> IN THE MIDWEST YOU GO INTO
>> WILL THAT JUST COVER IT?
THE WOODS AND YOU JUST --
>> IN THE MIDWEST YOU GO INTO
>> CARLA, SAME AS HERE.
THE WOODS AND YOU JUST --
HOW ABOUT YOU, CLINTON?
>> CARLA, SAME AS HERE.
>> I MADE A DELICIOUS --
HOW ABOUT YOU, CLINTON?
ON MONDAY NIGHT, I MADE MY
>> I MADE A DELICIOUS --
FAMOUS BUTTERMILK CHICKEN AND MY
ON MONDAY NIGHT, I MADE MY
ALL-TIME FAVORITE SALAD.
FAMOUS BUTTERMILK CHICKEN AND MY
IT'S THE SAME THAT I MADE
ALL-TIME FAVORITE SALAD.
WITH --
IT'S THE SAME THAT I MADE
>> OH, YES!
WITH --
>> WHEN SHE WAS HERE.
>> OH, YES!
I GOT TO TELL YOU, THAT SALAD IS
>> WHEN SHE WAS HERE.
THE BEST SALAD IN THE WORLD!
I GOT TO TELL YOU, THAT SALAD IS
>> IT'S SO GOOD!
THE BEST SALAD IN THE WORLD!
>> SO GOOD, RIGHT?
>> IT'S SO GOOD!
>> YES!
>> SO GOOD, RIGHT?
>> IT'S GOT WALNUTS AND BLUE
>> YES!
CHEESE.
>> IT'S GOT WALNUTS AND BLUE
>> OH, MY GOD!
CHEESE.
>> AND AVOCADO AND BABY ARUGULA.
>> OH, MY GOD!
>> MMM.
>> AND AVOCADO AND BABY ARUGULA.
>> A REAL -— AN EASY
>> MMM.
VINAIGRETTE.
>> A REAL -— AN EASY
SO, THAT WAS MY --
VINAIGRETTE.
>> LOOK AT US COOKING ON A --
SO, THAT WAS MY --
>> I KNOW!
>> LOOK AT US COOKING ON A --
>> IMAGINE THAT.
>> I KNOW!
WE CAN COOK WHEN WE GO HOME.
>> IMAGINE THAT.
>> YES!
WE CAN COOK WHEN WE GO HOME.
>> RIGHT?
>> YES!
ALL RIGHT.
>> RIGHT?
SO, MOTHER'S DAY IS AROUND THE
ALL RIGHT.
CORNER, SO I THOUGHT --
SO, MOTHER'S DAY IS AROUND THE
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
CORNER, SO I THOUGHT --
HEY, MOM!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HEY, MOMMA!
HEY, MOM!
>> WHO HERE HAS A MOTHER?
>> HEY, MOMMA!
YAY!
>> WHO HERE HAS A MOTHER?
>> I BELIEVE THIS IS THE MOST
YAY!
IMPORTANT DAY OF THE YEAR.
>> I BELIEVE THIS IS THE MOST
>> YOU LOVE ANGEL.
IMPORTANT DAY OF THE YEAR.
>> I LOVE ANGEL AND LIZ --
>> YOU LOVE ANGEL.
YOU KNOW, I LOVE MOTHER'S DAY.
>> I LOVE ANGEL AND LIZ --
>> I DO, TOO!
YOU KNOW, I LOVE MOTHER'S DAY.
>> MY DAD ALWAYS GETS --
>> I DO, TOO!
HE'S ALWAYS, "WHAT ABOUT -- YOU
>> MY DAD ALWAYS GETS --
GET ME A SLEEVE OF GOLF BALLS?"
HE'S ALWAYS, "WHAT ABOUT -- YOU
I'M LIKE, "OH, WE CELEBRATE --"
GET ME A SLEEVE OF GOLF BALLS?"
[ LAUGHTER ]
I'M LIKE, "OH, WE CELEBRATE --"
>> WELL, WE HAVE A MOTHER'S DAY
[ LAUGHTER ]
INSPIRED TASTING HERE.
>> WELL, WE HAVE A MOTHER'S DAY
THESE ARE FROM THE RESTAURANT
INSPIRED TASTING HERE.
AREPERA --
THESE ARE FROM THE RESTAURANT
NO, I MESSED IT UP!
AREPERA --
>> A PERA?
>> AREPERA GUACUCO.
I HAD IT BEFORE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
WHY DIDN'T I TAKE FRENCH IN HIGH
SCHOOL?
HOW DO YOU SAY THAT RESTAURANT
NAME?
>> AREPERA GUACUCO.
>> THERE YOU GO.
AND THAT WAS A TOUGH --
>> AREPERA GUACUCO.
SAY IT.
>> NO.
IT'S IN BROOKLYN, NEW YORK.
BUT THESE ARE AREPAS WHICH ARE
"REINA PEPIADA" AREPAS.
THEY'VE GOT SHREDDED CHICKEN AND
AVOCADO IN THEM.
AND THEY ARE A MOTHER'S DAY
INSPIRED TASTING BECAUSE
LEONARDO MOLINA NAMED THE
RESTAURANT AFTER THE BEACH IN
VENEZUELA WHERE IT WAS BORN AND
HIS MOTHER, CARMEN, COOKS ALL
THE FOOD AND IS KNOWN FOR HER
INCREDIBLE AREPAS, WHICH SHE
MAKES FRESH.
>> MMM.
>> THESE ARE DELICIOUS.
>> THEY'RE DELICIOUS.
>> MMM.
>> MMM!
>> DELICIOUS.
NOT TRADITIONAL THIS WAY, BUT
EXCELLENT.
>> I KNOW!
AND THE AREPA IS SO TENDER.
>> MMM.
>> DELICIOUS.
>> WHAT'S NEXT, CLINTON?
WHAT'S NEXT?
>> WELL, WE'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT
CELEBRITIES WITH THEIR SHIRTS
OFF.
>> OH.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I LOVE A GOOD -- CELEBRITIES
WITH THEIR SHIRTS OFF.
>> YEAH.
WELL, THIS IS THE THING.
THERE'S A NEW TREND HAPPENING
RIGHT NOW.
IF YOU WANT TO GO VIRAL IN THE
KITCHEN, THE BEST WAY TO DO IT
IS TAKE OFF YOUR SHIRT AND COOK
AN EGG.
>> YES!
>> HOLD ON!
HOLD ON!
>> I WOULD SAY "SUPER TREND."
>> WELL, NO.
WHAT IF IT'S NICOLE KIDMAN?
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THESE ARE ALL MEN.
>> OH.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> I WAS THINKING ABOUT DOING
IT, BUT OH WELL.
>> YOU KNOW NICK VIALL FROM "THE
BACHELOR", RIGHT?
WELL, HIS FIANCE, VANESSA, JUST
SHARED A PHOTO OF HIM --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
COOKING TOPLESS.
>> I'M SORRY.
HE DID LIKE 60 PUSH-UPS AND THEN
SAID, "HONEY, TAKE A PICTURE."
>> I KNOW.
YOU CAN TELL BY THE FACT THAT
HIS ARMS ARE LIKE LITERALLY
BULGING OUT RIGHT THEN.
>> I JUST DON'T FEEL THAT YOU
SHOULD BE --
YOU KNOW, AS SOMEONE WHO'S
COOKED FOR A LIVING FOR THE
MAJORITY OF THEIR LIFE, TO GET
IN FRONT OF A STOVE WHERE HOT
FAT IS SPLASHING AROUND.
>> YEAH.
>> WHEN YOU'RE 27, WHO CARES!
>> WHO CARES!
>> STILL BUBBLIN' AROUND.
ALL RIGHT.
WELL, HE'S NOT THE FIRST.
USHER ALSO MADE BREAKFAST IN
NOTHING BUT UNDERWEAR.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
I GOT TO TELL YOU, USHER --
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE IN GOOD SHAPE,
MAN, BUT YOU'RE KILLIN' THAT
EGG.
>> KILLIN' AN EGG!
>> I LOOKED AT THAT EGG UP
CLOSE, IT IS BEING --
>> THAT EGG LOOKS --
THAT EGG IS DEAD.
>> USHER, YOU MAY HAVE IT ALL,
BUT WE GOT THE EGG.
>> WE GOT THE EGG.
>> WE GOT THE EGG, USHER.
>> I'M NEVER GONNA MAKE FUN OF
USHER BECAUSE HE'S PART OWNER OF
THE CLEVELAND CAVALIERS, SO I
GOT TO RESPECT THAT.
>> I'M NOT MAKING FUN OF USHER.
>> KEVIN HART ALSO TENDS TO
GRILL TOPLESS.
HERE'S OUR GRATUITOUS
KEVIN HART --
>> LOOK AT KEVIN.
>> I FIND THE GRILL MORE
ACCEPTABLE THAN BEING INDOORS
AND DOING IT.
>> REALLY?
I'D FEEL LIKE THERE'S A LIVE
FIRE THAT COULD JUMP OUT.
>> IT COULD OF CAME FROM THE
POOL AND YOU'RE JUST WHIPPIN'
SOMETHING UP ON THE GRILL.
>> SO THAT COULD HAPPEN.
STRANGER THINGS HAVE HAPPENED.
ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO YOU GUYS HAVE
COMING UP IN THIS HOUR?
MICHAEL, WHY DON'T YOU GO FIRST.
>> WELL, I THINK I WILL,
CLINTON.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> IT'S REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK,
SO I'M ANSWERING A VIEWER BY
MAKING MEDITERRANEAN STUFFED
PEPPERS WITH FETA!
>> YUM!
>> AND I'M GONNA SHARE A GREAT
MOTHER'S DAY GIFT IDEA FOR THIS
WEEKEND!
>> WELL, SHE'S FINALLY HERE.
FINALLY, FINALLY, FINALLY!
I'M COOKIN' WITH
DARBY STANCHFIELD FROM
"SCANDAL"!
I'M SO EXCITED!
>> BUT FIRST, WE'RE JOINED BY
OUR GUEST WHO DEFINITELY HAS
THAT "WOW" FACTOR.
HE'S A TALENTED ACTOR.
ONE OF HOLLYWOOD'S FAVORITES,
AND NOW HE'S STARRING IN AMAZON
PRIME'S CAPTIVATING NEW SERIES,
"I LOVE DICK."
PLEASE WELCOME BACK,
KEVIN BACON!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> WHOO!
>> HAPPY TO HAVE YOU HERE!
>> HI!
>> HOW ARE YOU, KEVIN?
GOOD TO SEE YOU!
>> KEVIN AND I ARE IN THE
KITCHEN TOGETHER WHEN WE COME
BACK!
DON'T GO AWAY!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
Allergy symptoms
distracting you?
Doctors recommend
taking Claritin every day
of your allergy season
for continuous relief.
Claritin provides powerful,
non-drowsy, 24-hour relief.
For fewer interruptions from
the amazing things
you do every day.
Live Claritin Clear.
Every day.
When you have allergies,
it can seem like triggers
pop up everywhere.
Luckily there's Powerful,
24-hour,
non-drowsy Claritin.
It provides relief
of symptoms that
can be triggered by over
200 different allergens.
Live Claritin Clear.
At KFC, we choose to make...
spicy, crispy
chicken sandwiches.
Not because it is easy...
but because it is hard.
We choose not only to launch
KFC's new Zinger sandwich
and a $5 dollar fill up...
but to take it to space.
Will it be easy?
No.
Will it be hard? Yes.
We've already covered that.
But when we succeed...
we will lick our fingers good!
Space sandwich! Yeah!
Try the Zinger sandwich
before it goes to space.
All eyes are on Olay Ultimate
Eye Cream.
Allure Best of Beauty and Marie
Claire's Most Wanted.
Eyes show emotion, not your age.
Olay Eyes. Ageless.
Shake up your routine with a
completely new way to clean.
New Colgate Total Advanced
Health Mouthwash.
Shake to activate a powerf
cleaning action
that removes twenty four times
more bacteria.
Improve the health of your mouth
with new Colgate Total Advanced
Health Mouthwash.
Shake to clean.
Tonight, they've got
a full house.
So this quick ranch pasta
primavera is the perfect dish.
Sprinkle in a packet of
Hidden Valley Ranch,
add some veggies, and you've got
a meal that's sure to please.
It's time to Ranch Out
with the original,
Hidden Valley Ranch.
>>> Announcer: IT'S AN HOUR OF
"WEEKNIGHT WOWS" TODAY, ON "THE
CHEW!"
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> WELCOME BACK, TO "THE CHEW!"
WE'RE JOINED BY OUR FANTASTIC
GUEST, THE STAR OF MANY
MEMORABLE MOVIES AND A NEW HIT
SERIES --
KEVIN BACON!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SO, WHAT'S A TYPICAL WEEKNIGHT
AROUND YOUR GUYS' HOUSE?
ARE YOU A COOKER?
>> YEAH, WE ARE COOKERS.
YEAH, WE'RE BOTH COOKERS.
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN US IS
SHE'S A RECIPE FOLLOWER, AND I'M
A RECIPE IGNORER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> AH!
>> I MEAN, I GET --
>> THERE'S THE BEAUTIFUL COUPLE.
I THINK, EVERYONE IN AMERICA CAN
SEE.
>> YES.
>> MAYBE THAT'S WHY WE GET
ALONG.
>> RIGHT.
>> BUT, YEAH WE COOK.
WE HAVE A TRADITION, CERTAINLY
AROUND DINNER IN OUR HOUSE, WITH
SITTING DOWN WITH THE KIDS
OFTEN, WITH CANDLELIGHT, AND
ACTUALLY MAKING DINNER TOGETHER
AND --
THEY'RE OUT OF THE HOUSE NOW,
BUT THAT'S IMPORTANT TO US.
SO, WE LOVE TO --
[ APPLAUSE ]
WE LOVE TO EAT, BE TOGETHER,
TALK, HANG OUT WHILE WE'RE
COOKING AS WELL.
>> SO, WELL IT'S EASY TO GET
CARRIED AWAY, AND EVERYBODY'S
ALWAYS MAKING SURE THEY'RE
STAYING UP TO DATE ON THEIR
INSTAGRAM, OR MAKING SURE YOU
TAKE THE CALL --
WHETHER IT'S YOUR AGENT, YOUR
NEXT DOOR NEIGHBOR, OR SOMEBODY
ELSE.
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT FOR ME
THAT WE TURN ALL THE PHONES OFF
AND PUT THEM ALL AWAY WHEN YOU
SIT DOWN FOR DINNER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
BECAUSE YOU CAN REALLY TAKE A
FULL HOUR.
>> AND I THINK, OUR HOUSE, WHAT
WE LOVE TO DO IS MAKE SURE WE
DON'T DO THE DISHES THE MOMENT
WE'RE DONE EATING.
>> THAT'S A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
>> LET THEM SIT THERE FOR A
LITTLE WHILE.
>> LET THEM SIT THERE.
I KNOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I JUST KIND OF CAME TO THAT
RECENTLY, THAT IT'S OKAY TO JUST
LOOK AT THAT TABLE WITH
EVERYTHING THERE.
AND YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENS
SOMETIMES --
SOMETIMES YOU GO, "YOU KNOW, I
THINK I'M GOING TO HAVE ANOTHER
BITE."
[ LAUGHTER ]
I DO THIS WEIRD THING, I DON'T
KNOW IF ANYBODY ELSE DOES IT,
BUT MY KIDS ALWAYS MAKE FUN OF
IT.
AND, I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE IT
WAS A THING, BUT "THERE GOES DAD
WITH THE FINAL BITE."
WHICH IS, AFTER WE'VE CLEARED.
>> RIGHT.
>> EVERYTHING IS BACK IN THE
KITCHEN.
THAT'S WHEN I HAVE TO HAVE ONE
MORE BITE.
>> WELL, YEAH.
>> YEAH, YEAH.
>> ONE MORE RAVIOLI OFF THE
PLATE BEFORE WE GO TO THE
CLEANING FACTOR.
>> DOES ANYBODY ELSE DO THAT?
>> YES.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> OKAY, SO I'M NOT SPECIAL.
>> NO, YOU'RE SPECIAL!
YOU'RE SPECIAL, YOU'RE SPECIAL,
YOU'RE SPECIAL.
SO, TELL US ABOUT THIS NEW SHOW.
I WATCHED IT, AND I'VE GOT TO
SAY I THINK IT'S GOING TO CHANGE
TV.
>> YOU'RE SO SWEET TO SAY THAT.
>> THIS IS SOMETHING SO AMAZING.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IT'S ON AMAZON PRIME.
IT STARTS THIS FRIDAY.
AND, IT IS A CRAZY STORY.
TELL US ABOUT YOUR CHARACTER.
YOU'RE KIND OF LIKE THE MOGUL
MAN.
WELL, THERE'S A PICTURE OF YOU
RIGHT THERE.
>> YEAH.
>> SO YOU'RE, LIKE, A PROFESSOR
AT THIS CRAZY INSTITUTE IN
MARFA, TEXAS, RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
MARFA, TEXAS, IT'S A SMALL TOWN
IN WEST TEXAS JUST THAT,
ACTUALLY, IS A REAL PLACE AND
HAS --
YOU KNOW IS A REAL, CLASSIC
TRADITIONAL TEXAS TOWN, BUT ALSO
HAS A VERY BIG ARTS PROGRAM.
AND, A LOT OF REALLY COOL FOOD
TRUCKS, BY THE WAY.
AND, A LOT OF VERY, VERY HIP
SORT OF PEOPLE LIVING THERE A
LOT OF THE TIME.
>> IT'S SUPER COOL!
>> YEAH, IT'S A COOL --
>> HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?
>> I HAVE, YEAH.
IT'S A VERY COOL PLACE.
>> YEAH, RIGHT ALONGSIDE YOU
KNOW, LIKE, COWBOYS AND BORDER
PATROL, AND STUFF.
>> RIGHT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> AND, THIS GUY IS, YOU KNOW,
RUNNING THIS ARTS INSTITUTE DOWN
THERE.
HE'S A SCULPTOR.
AND THIS COUPLE, KATHRYN HAHN
AND GRIFFIN DUNNE, COME TO TOWN
AND THEY ARE KIND OF, LOST A
LITTLE BIT OF THE FLAME IN THEIR
RELATIONSHIP.
>> RIGHT.
>> AND, THEIR OBSESSION,
STARTING WITH HER OBSESSION FOR
THIS MAN, DICK, WHICH I PLAY,
REIGNITES THE PASSION IN THEIR
LOVE LIFE.
SO, THE SHOW IS VERY --
>> IN AN ELECTRIC WAY!
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, IT IS SO
SEXY.
>> IT'S A SEXY SHOW.
>> AND, SO BEAUTIFUL.
IT IS SO AMAZING.
AND THE ACTING IS SO FANTASTIC.
>> THANK YOU.
>> I MEAN, YOU SHOULD BE REALLY
PROUD.
[ APPLAUSE ]
I FEEL VERY STRONGLY THAT IT'S
GOING TO CHANGE TV.
AND, I'VE GOT TO SAY, THAT THE
MUSIC, AND THE BACKGROUND, AND
THE DIRECTION AND THE WHOLE
THING IS JUST, SOMETHING CRAZY.
GUYS, YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THIS
SHOW.
[ APPLAUSE ]
IN ANY CASE, WHY DON'T WE START
COOKING?
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO, WE'RE GOING TO
MAKE AN ORECCHIETTE DISH, WHICH
IS THE PASTA TRADITIONAL TO
APULIA.
WE'VE ALREADY MADE THE NOODLES,
AND WE'VE SET THEM ASIDE.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE RAPINI,
WHICH IS BROCCOLI RABE AND
SAUSAGE.
AND, TRADITIONALLY YOU JUST,
KIND OF, CHOP THEM UP.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE IT INTO A
PESTO.
SO, WOULD YOU LIKE TO HELP?
>> I WOULD!
>> SO, WE BLANCH THEM UP, AND
YOU THROW IT ALL IN.
AND THEN, WHAT WE DID WAS, WE
ROASTED A HEAD OF GARLIC.
WE WERE DISCUSSING GARLIC
EARLIER.
>> YEAH.
>> WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS ABOUT
ROASTED, VERSUS NON ROASTED?
>> YEAH, SO, I LOVE GARLIC.
BUT I FIND, LIKE, IF IT'S IN
LIKE THIS KIND OF SAUCE, OR A
PESTO SAUCE, IT'S A LITTLE BIT
MUCH.
ESPECIALLY IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
DAY.
BUT IF YOU ROAST IT FIRST, IT
JUST TAKES A LITTLE BIT OF THE
BITE OUT OF IT.
IT MAKES IT SWEETER.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THAT'S WHAT WE WERE HOPING.
>> LITERALLY, WHEN THIS, I WAS
LITERALLY JUST TALKING ABOUT
THIS IN THE DRESSING ROOM.
AND, THEN SOMEONE WHO WAS WITH
ME SAITHEY SOMETIMES DO IT
WITH BLACK GARLIC.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WHAT BLACK
GARLIC WAS.
>> YEAH, IT'S A FERMENTED
GARLIC!
>> OH.
>> IT STARTED IN KOREA!
AND NOW YOU CAN BUY IT IN
GROCERY STORES AND IT'S ALREADY
READY.
IT'S DELICIOUS, IT'S SWEET, A
LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED.
>> I LOVE THAT THERE'S ALMONDS
IN THERE.
>> YEAH, SO WE HAVE SOME
ALMONDS.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A PINCH OF
CHILI.
YOU WANT TO GRATE A LITTLE
PARMESAN INTO THERE?
>> YEAH.
>> AND, I'M GOING TO SLOW ABOUT
A QUARTER TO A HALF CUP OF EXTRA
VIRGIN OLIVE OIL.
OVER HERE, I TOOK SOME REALLY
NICE, OUT OF CASING, SAUSAGE.
YOU CAN JUST TAKE YOUR OWN
GROUND TURKEY OR GROUND PORK OR
GROUND BEEF.
AND SEASON IT LIKE SAUSAGE.
>> TELL ME WHEN IT'S DONE.
>> THAT'S THE RIGHT AMOUNT.
PERFECT.
AND THEN, WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO
IS, I ALREADY PINCHED SOME SALT
IN IT.
GO AHEAD AND PULSE IT UNTIL IT
BECOMES NICE AND SMOOTH.
I'M GOING TO ADD JUST A LITTLE
MORE OIL IN THERE.
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT!
NOW, THAT COULD BE A DIP, THAT
COULD BE A PASTA SAUCE.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WOW, BRAVO.
>> YOU JUST ADD SOME CHILI AND
TOASTED ALMONDS, BECAUSE I LIKE
THE TEXTURE THAT'S GOING TO GIVE
IT.
>> MHMM.
>> WE'RE GOING TO DROP OUR
NOODLES INTO THE PASTA WATER.
WE'RE GOING TO SEASON IT TO THE
TASTE OF --
>> THE SEA!
>> AH!
>> MY FANS ARE PAYING ATTENTION!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> IS THAT WHAT IT IS?
>> YEAH, SO WE DROP THE
ORECCHIETTE AND THAT'LL TAKE
ABOUT FOUR TO FIVE MINUTES TO
COOK.
WE ALWAYS COOK IT ONE MINUTE
LESS THAN THE PACKAGE SAYS.
WE'LL TAKE IT OUT, WE'LL DRAIN
IT, WE'LL TOSS IT IN HERE.
WE'LL ADD ALL THAT.
MORE WITH KEVIN BACON WHEN WE
COME BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
Ouch!
SKIN-FLEX™, Anna!
Sit!
New BAND-AID® Brand SKIN-FLEX™
Bandages.
Our best bandage yet!
It moves like a second skin.
♪
Dries almost instantly.
Better?
Yeah.
Go!
Good thing because stopping
never crosses your mind.
BAND-AID® Brand.
Stick With It™
♪
So soft, thin,
and two times more absorbent
you hardly know it's there.
Carefree®.
Free to be You™.
No matter who was in
there last. Protection.
New Lysol Power & Fresh 6 goes
to work flush after flush
for a just-cleaned feeling that
lasts up to 4 weeks.
LYSOL. What it takes to protect.
(JOHNNY VO) Xanthan is...
a small alien.
He lives on Xanthan.
He loves to conquer planets.
(ANNOUNCER VO) Actually, Xathan
Gum is an additive
found in some cream cheese.
But it's not in Arla.
Arla. Live unprocessed.
♪
You know how painful heartburn
can be.
For fast-acting, long-lasting
relief,
try doctor recommended Gaviscon.
It quickly neutralizes stomach
acid
and helps keep acid down for
hours.
Relieve heartburn with fast-
acting, long-lasting Gaviscon.
(Nathan) Secondhand smoke
caused me to have
and helps keep acid down for
hours.
asthma attacks,
infections and
lung damage.
And I never smoked.
(Announcer) If you or someone
you know wants free help
to quit smoking,
call 1-800-QUIT-NOW.
What's the best way to get
two servings of veggies?
V8 or a fancy juice store?
Ready, go!
Hi, Juice Universe?
One large rutabaga,
with eggplant...
Done!
That's not fair.
Glad I had a V8.
The original way to
fuel your day.
>>> IS IT POSSIBLE I SAW YOU ON
A HORSE YESTERDAY?
>> YEAH, I HAVE A RANCH JUST
OUTSIDE OF TOWN.
>> OH.
HOW BIG?
>> YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW BIG --
MY RANCH IS?
NO MORE POLITE TO ASK A RANCHER
THE SIZE OF HIS ACREAGE THAN A
LADY HER AGE.
>> DULY NOTED.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WELCOME BACK!
THAT WAS A SNEAK PEEK ON THE
VERY CALM SIDE OF OUR VERY
TALENTED GUEST, KEVIN BACON FROM
THE ELECTRIFYING NEW SERIES --
TELL US A LITTLE ABOUT THAT.
>> WELL, THE SERIES IS CALLED "I
LOVE DICK."
[ LAUGHTER ]
AND THAT WAS A SCENE, JUST
WANTED TO REMIND EVERYBODY.
THAT'S A SCENE WHERE I AM
MEETING KATHERINE HAHN'S
CHARACTER FOR THE FIRST TIME,
AND THERE IS SUPPOSE TO BE A
CONNECTION THAT'S IMMEDIATELY
MADE BETWEEN THE TWO OF US.
>> YES.
>> UNTIL I FIND OUT SHE'S
MARRIED AND THAT HER HUSBAND IS
NOW A FELLOW AT THE INSTITUTE,
THEN I TRY TO STEP BACK AND SAY
"NO, I AM NOT GOING THERE."
>> RIGHT.
WISE CHOICE.
>> WISE CHOICE, YEAH.
>> ALTHOUGH SOON TO LEAD TO MUCH
MORE MISCHIEF.
>> OH, THERE'S A LOT OF
MISCHIEF.
>> IT'S FANTASTIC.
>> MISCHIEF IS GOOD WAY OF
PUTTING IT!
>> YEAH!
>> SO HERE IT IS COMING OUT.
I TOSSED THE PESTO RIGHT OUT OF
THE FOOD PROCESSOR INTO HERE.
THEN WHAT YOU DO IS TOSS IT
GENTLY.
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF THE PASTA
WATER TO BRING IT TO THE EXACT
RIGHT TEXTURE.
THEN YOU TAKE IT TO THE FABULOUS
BOWL LIKE SO.
AND THEN WE GIVE IT A QUICK
LITTLE TASTE, BECAUSE WE'RE
PROFESSIONALS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THERE'S SOMETHING TO SERVING
CHEESE LIKE THAT MAKES EVERYONE
REALLY HAPPY.
TAKE A BITE AND THEN WE'LL
DISCUSS A COUPLE OTHER THINGS.
NOW I'VE HEARD IT SAYS, THAT YOU
SAY YOU LEARNED EVERYTHING YOU
NEED TO KNOW ABOUT ACTING --
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?
>> THAT'S AMAZING!
[ APPLAUSE ]
THAT IS REALLY GOOD.
>> AND EASY TO MAKE, AND IF YOU
COULDN'T FIND BROCCOLI RABE YOU
COULD JUST USE BROCCOLI, IT'S
ALL RIGHT AMERICA.
SO I HEARD THAT YOU SAID THAT
COULD LEARN EVERYTHING YOU NEED
TO LEARN ABOUT ACTING FROM
RIDING ON THE SUBWAY IN NEW YORK
CITY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
TELL US WHAT THAT MEANS!
>> WELL, WHEN I FIRST MOVED TO
NEW YORK, I GREW UP IN
PHILADELPHIA, ONE OF THE THINGS
I LOVE ABOUT THIS PLACE WAS THAT
YOU KNOW JUST THE AMAZING KIND
OF DIVERSITY.
THE KIND OF PEOPLE THAT LIVE
HERE AND EVERYONE GETS TOGETHER
AND HAS TO RIDE THE SUBWAY
TOGETHER.
I STILL RIDE THE SUBWAY PROBABLY
ONCE OR TWICE A DAY.
>> MM-HMM.
>> I THINK THAT I AM CALLED UPON
OFTEN TO JUST PLAY REAL PEOPLE.
SO I THINK YOU HAVE TO BE WITH
REAL PEOPLE, IF YOU WANT TO BE
REAL PEOPLE.
>> RIGHT.
BRAVO.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> SO THAT'S JUST BEEN A GREAT
ACTING LESSON.
>> I AGREE.
I MEAN THERE'S JUST SO MUCH
STUFF TO LOOK AT AND IT'S SO
MUCH FUN.
SO NOW OFF A LITTLE BIT TO THAT
TOPIC, WHAT ABOUT THE BACON
BROTHERS, MAN?
WHAT ABOUT MY BAND?
WHEN IS THE MUSIC COMING BACK TO
ME?
>> WE'RE DOING WELL, I MEAN --
>> ARE YOU GOING TO TOUR?
>> MM-HMM.
>> FANTASTIC!
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> WE'RE GOING OUT, RIGHT AFTER
MEMORIAL DAY.
WE'RE ACTUALLY PLAYING, SPEAKING
OF TEXAS, BECAUSE WE SHOT "I
LOVE DICK" IN TEXAS, BUT I AM
DOING A LOT OF TEXAS.
>> OH FANTASTIC!
>> I KIND OF LIKE SOUTHERN --
AND THEN LATER ON UP IN THE --
>> NORTHERN MICHIGAN?
>> NO, WE'RE NOT GETTING
MICHIGAN.
>> DANG!
>> RIGHT OUTSIDE OF TEXAS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> RIGHT, THAT WOULD BE WHAT
THEY CALL BAD ROUTING.
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT THAT!
>> WELL, IT'S REALLY NICE TO
HAVE YOU HERE.
>> SO GREAT.
>> BUT WE CAN'T LET YOU LEAVE
WITHOUT A LITTLE SOMETHING --
IT'S TIME TO "CHEWSE" YOUR GIFT.
>> OH REALLY?
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> ALSO KNOWN AS STUFF WE FOUND
LYING AROUND THE STUDIO.
GIVE IT A TRY!
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YES.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> THE SELFIE STICK!
>> A SELFIE STICK, I COULD USE
ONE OF THESE!
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT'S A NICE SELFIE STICK,
WOW!
>> YOU CAN JOIN THE CROWD OF
PEOPLE THAT CONSTANTLY GO LIKE
THIS.
NOW YOU CAN DO IT EVEN FURTHER.
>> NOW I AM GOING TO TAKE MY
SHIRT OFF AND START COOKING!
>> THAT'S RIGHT!
GET SOME EGGS GOING ON THERE!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THANKS TO KEVIN BACON FOR
STOPPING BY.
HE'S CURRENTLY IN HIS NEW SERIES
"I LOVE DICK" STREAMING ON
AMAZON PRIME THIS FRIDAY.
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> Announcer: COMING UP,
MOTHER'S DAY IS RIGHT AROUND THE
CORNER, AND CLINTON'S GOT A
MUST-SEE TIP YOU WON'T FIND
ANYWHERE ELSE.
FIND OUT WHAT IT IS, IN A
MOMENT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Allergy symptoms
distracting you?
Doctors recommend taking
Claritin every day
of your allergy season
for continuous relief.
Claritin provides powerful,
non-drowsy, 24-hour relief.
For fewer interruptions from the
amazing things you do every day.
Live Claritin Clear.
Every day.
♪ ♪ ♪
THE BEST WAY TO GET TOGETHER
IS WITH A TREAT
YOU MAKE TOGETHER.
♪ ♪ ♪
UN-Stop right there!
I'm about to pop a cap of
“mmm fresh” in that washer
with Unstopables In-Wash
Scent Boosters by Downy.
Because this scent lasts
up to 12 weeks,
which is longer than any
relationship I've ever been in.
Freshness for weeks!
>> Announcer: "THE CHEW" WILL
RETURN IN A MOMENT, HERE ON ABC.
We're trying to turn screen
time into active time...
here goes!
We're dolphins!
We're making our local park
a safe place for families.
We're in super hero training!
We're having more water
and fewer sugary drinks.
And we feel stronger.
I'm doing better in school.
We feel happier.
Small changes you make today
can make a big difference in how
you feel....
and may help prevent obesity,
high blood pressure,
and type 2 diabetes.
Start now to turn
today into a better day.
We're still going,
and we feel better!
♪
>> Announcer: WELCOME BACK TO
"THE CHEW'S" WEEKNIGHT WOWS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> HEY, EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK
TO "THE CHEW."
NOW, ALL WEEK, YOU GUYS ARE
CALLING THE SHOTS TO REQUEST A
RECIPE.
TODAY'S ASK COMES FROM JANINE ON
FACEBOOK.
SHE WROTE, "STUFFED PEPPERS.
[ LAUGHTER ]
MY MOTHER USED TO MAKE THESE A
LOT, BUT I DON'T HAVE HER
RECIPE."
SO JANINE, I GOT YOU.
I'M GOING TO MAKE A STUFFED
PEPPER, THE KIND I GREW UP
EATING.
IT'S A MEDITERRANEAN VERSION OF
A STUFFED PEPPER.
AND IT IS TOPPED WITH A LITTLE
BIT OF FETA CHEESE.
>> OH, THAT LOOKS GOOD.
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING ABOUT
THAT?
>> I FEEL GOOD ABOUT IT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> NOW, I USED TO LOVE EATING
STUFFED PEPPERS AS A KID.
AND THEN AS I BECAME AN ADULT,
IT'S THE REASON THAT WE DID
THEM.
IT'S A GREAT WAY TO STRETCH MEAT
A LITTLE BIT AND GET YOUR KIDS
TO EAT VEGETABLES ALL WRAPPED IN
ONE.
>> WELL, LET'S DO IT.
>> SO YOU ONLY HAD TO USE HALF
THE MEAT AND YOU GET A VEGGIE.
SO I'M GOING TO START --
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A BECHAMEL,
BUT THEN FINISH IT WITH FETA.
SO IT'S GOING TO HAVE THAT NICE
SALTINESS IN THE CREAMY SAUCE.
>> CREAMY, SALTY SAUCE.
>> SO YOU'RE GOING TO START WITH
EQUAL PARTS OF BUTTER AND FLOUR.
SO TWO TEASPOONS OF BUTTER, TWO
TEASPOONS OF FLOUR.
>> TABLESPOONS.
>> TABLESPOONS, I'M SORRY.
THERE YOU GO.
THAT MUCH.
WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT WHEN
YOU'RE COOKING THIS, YOU KIND OF
WANT EQUAL PARTS BUTTER AND
FLOUR, AND YOU WANT A WET SAND
CONSISTENCY.
IF IT GETS A LITTLE BIT TOO DRY,
YOU COULD ADD A LITTLE BIT MORE.
IT SHOULD LOOK LIKE SAND ON THE
BEACH IN THE MORNING AFTER THE
WAVES ARE RIGHT THERE.
>> OH, YEAH, JUST LIKE THAT,
OKAY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SAND ON A BEACH.
AND THEN --
CLINTON LIKES HIS SAND A LITTLE
WETTER, APPARENTLY.
>> NO, I FELT LIKE IT NEEDED A
LITTLE MORE.
>> YEAH, THAT'S PERFECT.
AND THEN, FOR EVERY TWO OUNCES
OF THE ROUX THAT YOU MAKE,
YOU'RE JUST MAKING A ROUX.
THAT'S GOING TO THICKEN ABOUT
16 OUNCES OF LIQUID.
SO YOU HAVE ABOUT AN OUNCE OF
ROUX HERE.
YOU'RE GOING TO THICKEN
16 OUNCES OF LIQUID.
>> OKAY, GOT IT.
>> KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> YEAH, I GOT YOU RIGHT HERE.
OH.
SPLATTERED A LITTLE FAT ON ME
THERE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> ON YOUR FAVORITE COAT.
>> ON MY FAVORITE, IT WAS REALLY
ON MY HAND.
IT'S OKAY.
I'M FINE.
>> JUST KEEP WHISKING, BUDDY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> IT WAS JUST STARTLING.
IT STARTLED ME, HOT FAT ON MY
HAND.
STARTLED ME.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> I GET ALL JUMPY.
>> SEE HOW THAT'S STARTING TO
THICKEN UP?
NOW GRATE THE NUTMEG.
>> GRATE THE NUTMEG.
>> AND THEN YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE
THAT OFF THE HEAT AND ADD THE
FETA.
ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE, I HAVE
ABOUT THREE QUARTERS OF A POUND,
A POUND OF GROUND BEEF.
I'VE TOASTED THAT UP IN A LITTLE
BIT OF OLIVE OIL.
TO THIS I'M GOING TO ADD SOME
PINE NUTS.
I'M GOING TO ADD --
COULD YOU DICE THAT ONION?
>> DICING, DICING.
HOW SMALL, SYMON?
>> OH, HERE YOU GO.
I'M GOING TO ADD SOME SLICED
GARLIC.
AND THEN I'M GOING TO ADD A
WHOLE BUNCH OF FRESH HERBS AND A
LITTLE BIT OF CORIANDER.
AND THIS IS WHERE YOU COULD
REALLY HAVE FUN WITH IT.
I'M DOING IT WITH GROUND BEEF
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I GREW UP
EATING.
YOU COULD CERTAINLY DO IT WITH
GROUND TURKEY OR ANY GROUND MEAT
THAT YOU KIND OF LIKE.
AND I HAVE FRESH OREGANO, FRESH
PARSLEY.
>> SO NOW LET ME ASK YOU THIS,
SYMON.
>> YES, CHEF.
>> STUFFED CABBAGE AND STUFFED
PEPPERS.
SAME FILLING?
>> YOU COULD USE THE SAME
FILLING.
OH, YES, YOU COULD.
AND WHEN I GREW UP, IT WAS
FUNNY.
STUFFED PEPPERS, FOR SOME
REASON, TOOK MORE OF A GREEK
SPIN.
AND STUFFED CABBAGE WAS VERY
EASTERN EURO.
BUT THEY WOULD BOTH WORK
TOGETHER.
ALL RIGHT, SO NOW WE ADD OUR
ONION.
AND WE ADD A LITTLE BIT MORE FAT
TO THIS.
I'M GOING TO ADD SOME FRESH
OREGANO.
SOME FRESH PARSLEY.
SOMETIMES I'D EVEN PUT MINT IN
HERE IF I'M FEELING UNBELIEVABLY
CRAZY.
>> HOW ABOUT HOT PEPPERS?
>> I WOULD PUT HOT PEPPERS IN.
SOME SALT.
>> WOULD YOU WITH A GOAT?
ON A BOAT?
>> I WILL NOT EAT GREEN EGGS AND
HAM.
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> AND A LITTLE BIT OF CORIANDER
SEED.
AND SOME CRACKED BLACK PEPPER.
NOW, M.B. IF YOU COULD TAKE THAT
PEPPER, CUT THE TOP OFF AND
HOLLOW IT FOR ME.
CLINTON, YOU HAVE DONE A
FABULOUS JOB WITH THIS.
>> FEELING GOOD ABOUT THAT?
>> I NEED A LITTLE MORE MILK.
>> YOU WENT --
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> MILK.
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF ROUX.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> DID YOUR MOTHER STOP TELLING
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF ROUX.
YOU TO YELL IN THE HOUSE?
>> DID YOUR MOTHER STOP TELLING
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO FLATTEN IT
YOU TO YELL IN THE HOUSE?
OR LEAVE IT THERE?
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO FLATTEN IT
>> YOU CAN COVER IT JUST A
OR LEAVE IT THERE?
LITTLE BIT.
>> YOU CAN COVER IT JUST A
>> DON'T WANT TO CHALLENGE IT.
LITTLE BIT.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE.
>> DON'T WANT TO CHALLENGE IT.
LOOK AT THIS.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE.
>> OH, MIRACULOUSLY.
LOOK AT THIS.
>> SO WE HAVE A COUPLE THAT
>> OH, MIRACULOUSLY.
WE'VE ALREADY STUFFED.
>> SO WE HAVE A COUPLE THAT
IN THE BASE OF THIS WE HAVE --
WE'VE ALREADY STUFFED.
>> I'M BACK.
IN THE BASE OF THIS WE HAVE --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I'M BACK.
>> I STOLE THIS FROM A CAT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> DUMP IT IN, DUMP IT IN BEFORE
>> I STOLE THIS FROM A CAT.
THAT CAT --
>> DUMP IT IN, DUMP IT IN BEFORE
[ AUDIENCE OOHS ]
THAT CAT --
>> YOU KNOCKED IT.
[ AUDIENCE OOHS ]
BATALI.
>> YOU KNOCKED IT.
>> I DIDN'T DO IT.
BATALI.
>> YOU HIT THE WHISK.
>> I DIDN'T DO IT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> BUT THIS IS A GOOD STUDY IN
RATIO.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE RATIO, YOU
ALWAYS KNOW WHAT IT IS.
IT'S OKAY IF YOU HAVE A LITTLE
EXTRA, NO REASON TO PANIC.
I DON'T KNOW WHO'S GOING TO
CLEAN UP THE STOVE.
MAYBE GO FIND THAT CAT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SO THE MILK DOESN'T GO IN
HERE.
>> OH, YOU JUST WAIT.
>> I AM SO WAITING.
>> I WANT YOU TO STUFF THESE
TWO.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO.
>> OH, THE RICE.
>> OH, MY GOD, THE MILK GOT ME
ALL SIDETRACKED.
ALL RIGHT.
>> I'M JUST GOING TO STAND OVER
HERE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> IT ALL STARTED WITH A LITTLE
FAT SPLATTER, AND THEN THINGS
WENT TO HELL.
>> WELL, I WAS WATCHING YOU SAY
16 OUNCES, AND I'M LOOKING AT
THAT LITTLE THING OVER THERE AND
I'M LIKE, THAT IS NOT 16 OUNCES.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO THEN WE TAKE
THIS BECHAMEL.
WE PUT IT ON TOP.
AND IT'S GOING TO SLOWLY OOZE
AND BAKE DOWN INTO OUR STUFFED
PEPPERS AND GIVE IT A LITTLE BIT
OF CARAMELLY, SALTY GOODNESS ON
TOP.
I'M GOING TO STICK THIS IN THE
OVEN.
IT'S GOING TO GO TO ABOUT
375 DEGREES UNTIL IT'S GOLDEN
AND COOKED THROUGH.
OH, GOD, WHEN WE COME BACK,
CLINTON'S GOING TO SHOW YOU HIS
MOTHER'S DAY GIFT AND I'M GOING
TO MESS HIM ALL UP.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
Your body was made for better
things than
rheumatoid arthritis.
Before you and your
rheumatologist move to another
treatment, ask if XELJANZ is
right for you.
XELJANZ is a small pill for
adults with
moderate to severe RA for whom
methotrexate did not work well.
XELJANZ can reduce joint pain
and swelling in as little as
two weeks, and help stop further
joint damage.
XELJANZ can lower your ability
to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal
infections, lymphoma and other
cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ if you have
an infection.
Tears in the stomach or
intestines, low blood cell
counts and higher liver tests
and cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood
tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ,
and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you were in
a region where fungal
infections are common and if you
have had TB,
hepatitis B or C, or are prone
to infections.
XELJANZ can reduce the symptoms
of RA,
even without methotrexate, and
is also available
in a once-daily pill.
Ask about XELJANZ XR.
Now you can squeeze
a dollop of Daisy.
With Daisy squeeze sour cream.
Daisy is different than
other sour creams.
Only simple ingredients,
so it's simply pure.
Squeeze it on your favorite
dishes.
♪ Do a dollop of Daisy. ♪
Honey Nut Cheerios...
Are made with delicious honey
and real oats.
[kissing sound]
Ahhh!! Hey little guy.
I try hard to get a great shape.
This I can do, easily.
Benefiber® Healthy Shape is
a clear, taste-free,
100% natural daily fiber...
that's clinically proven to help
me feel fuller longer.
Benefiber® Healthy Shape.
This I Can Do!
Millions of you are
online right now,
searching one topic.
That will generate over
600 million results.
And if you've been
diagnosed with cancer,
searching for answers
like where to treat,
can feel even more
overwhelming.
So start your search
with a specialist
at Cancer Treatment
Centers of America.
Start with teams of
cancer treatment
experts under one roof.
Start where specialists
use advanced genomic
testing to guide precision
cancer treatment...
...that may lead to
targeted therapies
and more treatment
options.
Start where there's a
commitment to analyzing
the latest research and
conducting clinical
trials-to help each
patient get the
personalized cancer
care they deserve.
Start at one of the
Cancer Treatment
Centers of America
hospitals near you.
The evolution of
cancer care is here.
Learn more at
cancercenter.com/experts
Appointments available now.
♪
>> Announcer: WE'RE SERVING UP
WEEKNIGHT WOWS, TODAY ON "THE
CHEW."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> HEY EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK
TO "THE CHEW."
IT IS REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK, SO
I AM ANSWERING A VIEWER'S PLEA
WITH MY MEDITERRANEAN STUFFED
PEPPERS WITH A LITTLE BIT OF
FETA.
SO HERE'S WHAT WE DID, WE
MADE -- JUST TO BE CLEAR -- FOUR
OUNCES OF ROUX.
LOOK AT IT AS A RATIO.
FOUR OUNCES OF ROUX, TWO AND TWO
ALWAYS WILL THICKEN 32 OUNCES OF
LIQUID.
SO IF YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT AS A
RATIO -- JUST LOOK AT IT AS THE
RATIO.
YOU CAN BREAK IT DOWN OR UP ANY
WAY YOU WANT.
>> 2, 2, 32.
[ APPLAUSE ]
THEN WE TOOK THE GROUND BEEF, WE
TOOK THE PINE NUTS, THE ONIONS,
THE GARLIC, FRESH OREGANO,
PARSLEY, A LITTLE BIT OF COOKED
RICE, WE MIX IT ALL TOGETHER.
WE STUFF THOSE BEAUTIFUL RED
PEPPERS WITH IT.
A LITTLE BIT OF "CHEW" TOMATO
SAUCE ON THE BOTTOM, AND THEN WE
TOPPED IT WITH THAT FETA
BECHAMEL.
WE PUT THEM IN THE OVEN,
375 DEGREES FOR ABOUT 35 MINUTES
SO THEY GOT GOLDEN BROWN AND
DELICIOUS.
>> CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THEM.
DU, NA NA NA!
[ CHEERS ]
>> THERE YOU GO.
>> WOW.
>> WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT,
CLINTON?
>> SYMON, THOSE ARE BEAUTIFUL.
YOUR STOVETOP, HOWEVER, IS
FILTHY.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> WELL, I COULDN'T FIND THAT
DAMN CAT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
PASS THESE DOWN, TELL ME WHAT
YOU THINK.
>> CARLA HALL.
>> THANK YOU.
>> LET'S HAVE A LITTLE TASTE.
>> THE THING THAT I LOVE ABOUT
STUFFED PEPPERS AS I WAS SAYING
EARLIER IS YOU CAN REALLY
CUSTOMIZE THEM AND MAKE THEM
YOURSELF.
YOU CAN USE ANY KIND OF GROUND
MEAT.
SOMETIMES I MAKE THEM WITH LIZ
WITH QUINOA, YOU KNOW, AND TAKE
THE MEAT OUT.
>> OH, YOU DO?
>> OH, YEAH.
>> DON'T DO THAT.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> IT'S DELICIOUS.
>> DON'T DO THAT.
>> NO, IT'S LIKE A -- YOU CAN
MAKE A TUBULE STUFFED PEPPER
WHICH I THINK IS FANTASTIC.
>> CAN I HAVE SOME OF THE "CHEW"
SAUCE, PLEASE?
>> YEAH, YOU CAN HAVE A LITTLE
"CHEW" SAUCE STRAIGHT FROM THE
GARDEN OF MARIO BATALI.
>> FANTASTIC.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> SEE, NOW THIS LOOKS LIKE A
WEEKNIGHT MEAL AT MY HOUSE.
LIKE, THE KIDS HAD TO COOK
SOMETIMES, AND THIS WOULD BE THE
KIND OF DISH THAT WE COULD MAKE
BECAUSE YOU COULD PUT IT
TOGETHER VERY EASY, VERY
QUICKLY, RIGHT?
AND HOW'S IT TASTING, AMERICA?
>> FABULOUS.
>> IT'S DELICIOUS.
>> THIS IS REALLY GREAT.
IT'S REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> I LOVE PINE NUTS.
RICE.
MEAT.
>> IT'S REALLY HOT, SYMON.
>> OH, YOU KNOW, WE DON'T SERVE
ANYTHING COLD IN MARIO BATALI'S
HOT FOOD CAFE.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> WELL, ON THE TOPIC OF
EARTH --
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> I JUST WANTED TO WATCH YOU DO
THAT.
IT WAS CUTE.
ALL RIGHT, I HAVE AN IDEA
INSPIRED BY MY FAVORITE THING
FOR ME TO DO FOR MY MOM ON
MOTHER'S DAY.
WANT TO COME OVER HERE?
>> I WOULD LOVE TO.
>> OKAY, GREAT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OH, THAT'S ME AND MY MOM,
TERRY.
HEY, TERRY.
>> HI, TERRY.
>> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
SHE'S AWESOME.
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT I DO WITH MY
MOM EVERY MOTHER'S DAY -- EXCEPT
NOT THIS YEAR, BECAUSE SHE DID
IT ALREADY -- IS I GO TO HER
HOUSE, I HELP HER DO ALL THE
PLANTING IN HER BACKYARD FOR ALL
THE FLOWERS AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
AND, YOU KNOW, WE TALK A LOT
ON THIS SHOW ABOUT FRESH HERBS
AND HOW THEY REALLY DO MAKE A
DIFFERENCE IN YOUR FOOD.
SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE AN INDOOR
HERB GARDEN WITH A CAKE STAND
AND SOME TEACUPS.
>> OH, MY GOD, IT'S SO CUTE.
>> IT'S REALLY CUTE WHEN IT ALL
COMES TOGETHER.
SO IF YOU GO TO THE LOCAL FLEA
MARKET OR MAYBE YOU HAVE SOME OF
THESE IN YOUR GARAGE ALREADY,
MIX AND MATCHED TEACUPS AND
SAUCERS.
ALL YOU DO IS YOU TAKE SOME
PEBBLES, OR EVEN ONE BIG ROCK
WOULD BE FINE.
YOU PUT THEM AT THE BOTTOM,
BECAUSE THERE'S NO DRAINAGE IN
THE TEACUPS, SO YOU NEED A
LITTLE BIT --
>> YOU HAVE THE NICEST PEBBLES
I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> THEY'RE SO SHINY.
I PUT THEM IN MY ROCK TUMBLER.
[ LAUGHTER ]
>> OH, MY GOD, I HAD A ROCK
TUMBLER AS A KID.
>> I STILL HAVE ONE.
ALL RIGHT, SO THEN YOU BUY THESE
AT THE LOCAL NURSERY.
HERBS AT THIS STAGE COST ABOUT
$2.99, $3.99.
>> WHICH IS THE SAME PRICE AS
THE PACKAGE THAT YOU GET IN THE
STORE.
>> YES, WHICH IS A ONE USE
PACKAGE, BASICALLY.
>> EXACTLY.
>> AND THEN WHAT I'M GOING TO DO
IS SORT OF BREAK IT UP A LITTLE
BIT.
BREAK UP AT ROOT BALL, TAKE AWAY
ANY EXCESS SOIL RIGHT HERE.
AND THEN WHAT YOU CAN DO IS PUT
THAT RIGHT IN THE TEACUPS, AND
THEN REPLACE SOME OF THAT SOIL
AROUND THE SIDE.
OBVIOUSLY, I'LL DO IT A LITTLE
BIT NEATER AT HOME FOR MOM.
>> THANKS, ALL CLEAN.
OKAY AND THEN, SO YOU CAN DO --
THIS IS SAGE, OBVIOUSLY.
AND HERE WE HAVE SOME THYME.
THOSE GROW REALLY, REALLY WELL
INDOORS AS WELL AS OREGANO.
SO THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU HAVE
YOUR MIX AND MATCH TEACUPS, YOU
PUT THEM ON A CAKE STAND THAT
YOU MIGHT ALREADY OWN OR YOU CAN
FIND AT THE FLEA MARKET FOR LIKE
FIVE BUCKS.
AND THEN, IF YOUR MOM DOESN'T
HAVE ANY OUTDOOR SPACE, SHE CAN
PUT THIS IN A WELL LIT AREA OF
THE HOUSE.
OR IF THEY START TO GROW, SHE
CAN TRANSPLANT THEM OUTSIDE.
>> LOVE THAT.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> THE THYME, THE OREGANO, THE
SAGE, ALL WORK REALLY WELL
INDOORS.
YOU MIGHT HAVE TO PLANT YOUR
BASIL AND YOUR PARSLEY AND YOUR
ROSEMARY OUTSIDE, BECAUSE THOSE
GET A LITTLE BIT BIGGER.
SO ANYWAY, IT'S A NICE IDEA FOR
YOURSELF AS WELL.
HAPPY EARLY MOTHER'S DAY TO ALL
THE MOMS OUT THERE.
UP NEXT, CARLA IS COOKING WITH
"SCANDAL'S" DARBY STANCHFIELD.
DON'T GO AWAY.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
If You've Got A Life,
You Gotta Swiffer
Type 2 diabetes, listen up.
We're not professional athletes.
But that doesn't
mean we're giving up.
I'm in this for me.
For me.
Along with diet and exercise,
FARXIGA helps
lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by
up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if
allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms of
a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing
or swallowing,
stop taking and seek
medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA if you
have severe kidney problems,
are on dialysis, or
have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or
red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause
serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections
in women and men,
serious urinary
tract infections,
low blood sugar,
and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and call
your doctor right away
if you have signs
of ketoacidosis,
which is serious and
may lead to death.
I'm in this for my family.
I'm in this for me.
Ask your doctor about FARXIGA
and learn how you can
get it for FREE.
If you can't afford
your medication,
AstraZeneca may be able to help.
Americans - 83% try
to eat healthy.
Yet up 90% fall short in getting
key nutrients from food alone.
Let's do more.
Add One A Day Women's
complete with key
nutrients we may need.
Plus it supports
bone health
with calcium
and vitamin D.
One A Day Women's in
gummies and tablets.
Come.
Explore a place where you can
fly on the back of a banshee.
Walk under floating mountains.
And navigate a mystical river.
Welcome to a
world - beyond belief.
Pandora - The World of Avatar.
Only at the Walt Disney
World Resort.
♪"Good To Be Alive"♪
by Andy Grammer
♪
100% whole grains, real
chocolate chips. Quaker Chewy.
Break out the good.
>> Announcer: WE'VE GOT
WEEKNIGHT WOWS, RIGHT NOW ON
"THE CHEW."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> WELCOME BACK TO "THE CHEW."
AND YOU KNOW OUR NEXT GUEST AS
ONE OF THE AMAZING ACTORS IN THE
HIT ABC SHOW "SCANDAL," BUT DID
YOU KNOW SHE'S ALSO AMAZING IN
THE KITCHEN?
SHE'S ABOUT TO SHOW OFF HER
SKILLS HERE.
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME,
FINALLY, PLEASE WELCOME THE
TALENTED DARBY STANCHFIELD.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
FINALLY.
>> FINALLY GOT YOU.
WELCOME TO "THE CHEW."
>> I'M SUCH A FAN.
>> THIS IS SO AWESOME TO HAVE
YOU HERE.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
>> I MEAN, WE'VE HAD SO PEOPLE.
WELL, FIRST OFF, CONGRATS ON THE
100th EPISODE OF "SCANDAL."
AND WE'VE HAD SO MANY OF YOUR
GLADIATORS AS WELL AS THE
PRESIDENT OF THE SHOW.
>> I KNOW, IT'S MY FIRST TIME.
>> I KNOW.
>> SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
I KNOW, AND I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE
>> I KNOW.
SO MUCH IN COMMON.
I KNOW, AND I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE
>> YES.
SO MUCH IN COMMON.
>> YOU KNOW, WE BOTH LOVE
>> YES.
SOMETHING -- TEA.
>> YOU KNOW, WE BOTH LOVE
I'M A TEA LOVER.
SOMETHING -- TEA.
>> YOU HAVE TO SEE THE
I'M A TEA LOVER.
DOCUMENTARY THAT I JUST SHOT
>> YOU HAVE TO SEE THE
WITH PURE LEAF.
DOCUMENTARY THAT I JUST SHOT
IT'S ON PURELEAF.COM WEBSITE,
WITH PURE LEAF.
AND IT'S ALL ABOUT -- WE WENT TO
IT'S ON PURELEAF.COM WEBSITE,
A TEA ESTATE IN INDONESIA AND I
AND IT'S ALL ABOUT -- WE WENT TO
LEARNED HOW TO PICK TEA AND
A TEA ESTATE IN INDONESIA AND I
DISCOVERED THAT BEAUTIFUL ART OF
LEARNED HOW TO PICK TEA AND
CRAFTING PURE LEAF TEA.
DISCOVERED THAT BEAUTIFUL ART OF
THE DEDICATION AND THE CARE THAT
CRAFTING PURE LEAF TEA.
GOES INTO IT.
THE DEDICATION AND THE CARE THAT
>> WAS IT YOUR FIRST TIME IN
GOES INTO IT.
INDONESIA?
>> WAS IT YOUR FIRST TIME IN
>> IT WAS MY FIRST TIME.
INDONESIA?
MY FIRST TIME THROUGH A TEA
>> IT WAS MY FIRST TIME.
ESTATE.
MY FIRST TIME THROUGH A TEA
>> OH, MY GOD.
ESTATE.
>> AMAZING.
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> AND I CAN JUST PICTURE THERE
>> AMAZING.
LIKE ROLLING HILLS, A LUSH GREEN
>> AND I CAN JUST PICTURE THERE
AND --
LIKE ROLLING HILLS, A LUSH GREEN
>> THE RAIN, THE PEOPLE, THE
AND --
PEOPLE IN THE VILLAGE.
>> THE RAIN, THE PEOPLE, THE
IT WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
PEOPLE IN THE VILLAGE.
EXPERIENCE.
IT WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
>> WHEN YOU BROUGHT SOMETHING
EXPERIENCE.
BACK WITH YOU, YOU BROUGHT A
>> WHEN YOU BROUGHT SOMETHING
RECIPE THAT I'M REALLY EXCITED
BACK WITH YOU, YOU BROUGHT A
TO TRY.
RECIPE THAT I'M REALLY EXCITED
TELL ME WHAT WE'RE MAKING.
TO TRY.
>> NASI GORENG.
TELL ME WHAT WE'RE MAKING.
>> IT'S BASICALLY CHICKEN FRIED
>> NASI GORENG.
RICE.
>> IT'S BASICALLY CHICKEN FRIED
IT'S A TRADITION INDONESIAN
RICE.
DISH, AND BECAUSE I LOVE PURE
IT'S A TRADITION INDONESIAN
LEAF TEA SO MUCH, I AM -- I'M
DISH, AND BECAUSE I LOVE PURE
USING PURE LEAF AS ONE
LEAF TEA SO MUCH, I AM -- I'M
INGREDIENT.
USING PURE LEAF AS ONE
>> OKAY.
INGREDIENT.
>> IT'S A VERSATILE INGREDIENT.
>> OKAY.
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S A VERSATILE INGREDIENT.
SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE THE RICE
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
FIRST?
SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE THE RICE
>> YES, WE'RE MAKING THE RICE
FIRST?
FIRST.
>> YES, WE'RE MAKING THE RICE
>> OKAY.
FIRST.
SO, WE HAVE OUR RICE, AND THEN
>> OKAY.
YOU'RE GOING TO USE THE TEA.
SO, WE HAVE OUR RICE, AND THEN
>> PURE LEAF, YES.
YOU'RE GOING TO USE THE TEA.
TWO CUPS OF TEA TO GO WITH THE
>> PURE LEAF, YES.
RICE.
TWO CUPS OF TEA TO GO WITH THE
>> SO, ONE PART OF RICE?
RICE.
OKAY, SO JUST TALK ABOUT RATIOS.
>> SO, ONE PART OF RICE?
IT'S TWO TO ONE.
OKAY, SO JUST TALK ABOUT RATIOS.
SO, TWO PARTS LIQUID --
IT'S TWO TO ONE.
>> AND YOU CAN FIND THE RECIPE
SO, TWO PARTS LIQUID --
ON PURELEAF.COM
>> AND YOU CAN FIND THE RECIPE
>> OKAY.
ON PURELEAF.COM
>> YES.
>> OKAY.
>> MARIO, YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE
>> YES.
THIS.
>> MARIO, YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE
IT'S SPICY.
THIS.
IT'S SO --
IT'S SPICY.
>> IT'S SO SPICY.
IT'S SO --
ARE YOU READY, MARIO?
>> IT'S SO SPICY.
>> BRING IT ON.
ARE YOU READY, MARIO?
>> HE'S ALWAYS READY FOR SPICE.
>> BRING IT ON.
>> OKAY, AND YOU LET THAT SIMMER
>> HE'S ALWAYS READY FOR SPICE.
FOR ABOUT 15 MINUTES.
>> OKAY, AND YOU LET THAT SIMMER
>> OKAY.
FOR ABOUT 15 MINUTES.
>> AND SO THAT'S THE FIRST STEP.
>> OKAY.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> AND SO THAT'S THE FIRST STEP.
SO, OKAY.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.
THIS DISH OBVIOUSLY, SORT OF,
SO, OKAY.
INSPIRED YOU.
THIS DISH OBVIOUSLY, SORT OF,
HAS TRAVEL ALWAYS INSPIRED YOUR
INSPIRED YOU.
COOKING?
HAS TRAVEL ALWAYS INSPIRED YOUR
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY MY
COOKING?
ENVIRONMENT THAT I'M IN THAT
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY MY
INSPIRES ME.
ENVIRONMENT THAT I'M IN THAT
NOW, WE CHOP UP THE CHICKEN.
INSPIRES ME.
IT'S BEEN MARINATED IN CURRY AND
NOW, WE CHOP UP THE CHICKEN.
COCONUT OIL, AND WE'LL ADD
IT'S BEEN MARINATED IN CURRY AND
SHALLOTS AND CELERY.
COCONUT OIL, AND WE'LL ADD
>> IT SMELLS AMAZING.
SHALLOTS AND CELERY.
>> DOESN'T IT?
>> IT SMELLS AMAZING.
SPICY, JUST LIKE I LIKE IT.
>> DOESN'T IT?
>> SPICES.
SPICY, JUST LIKE I LIKE IT.
>> BUT I MET THE GARDENER AND
>> SPICES.
I -- SO TRAVEL AS WELL, BUT ALSO
>> BUT I MET THE GARDENER AND
JUST LIKE MY NATURAL
I -- SO TRAVEL AS WELL, BUT ALSO
ENVIRONMENT, WHATEVER'S AROUND
JUST LIKE MY NATURAL
ME.
ENVIRONMENT, WHATEVER'S AROUND
WHATEVER I CAN PLANT AND GROW.
ME.
>> LOVE THAT.
WHATEVER I CAN PLANT AND GROW.
>> JUST LIKE YOUR GUYS' HERBAL
>> LOVE THAT.
GARDEN.
>> JUST LIKE YOUR GUYS' HERBAL
>> I KNOW, WHICH IS SO CUTE.
GARDEN.
WELL, I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING YOU ON
>> I KNOW, WHICH IS SO CUTE.
INSTAGRAM.
WELL, I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING YOU ON
HAVE TO TELL YOU.
INSTAGRAM.
IN ADDITION TO YOUR AMAZING,
HAVE TO TELL YOU.
CUTE OUTFIT.
IN ADDITION TO YOUR AMAZING,
SO MANY CUTE THINGS.
CUTE OUTFIT.
>> THANK YOU.
SO MANY CUTE THINGS.
>> BUT ALSO, I MEAN, YOU
>> THANK YOU.
ACTUALLY COOK AND YOU HAVE SOME
>> BUT ALSO, I MEAN, YOU
WONDERFUL DISHES AND YOU HAD
ACTUALLY COOK AND YOU HAVE SOME
THAT BROCCOLI AND --
WONDERFUL DISHES AND YOU HAD
>> YES.
THAT BROCCOLI AND --
WITH THE SAUCE.
>> YES.
OKAY, AND THEN WE ADD SOME
WITH THE SAUCE.
CHILI.
OKAY, AND THEN WE ADD SOME
>> OKAY.
CHILI.
>> SOME CHILI SAUCE.
>> OKAY.
>> CHILI SAUCE.
>> SOME CHILI SAUCE.
>> TO THE CHICKEN, ONCE IT'S ALL
>> CHILI SAUCE.
SAUTEED, IT SMELLS -- YOU KNOW
>> TO THE CHICKEN, ONCE IT'S ALL
WHAT?
SAUTEED, IT SMELLS -- YOU KNOW
EVERYBODY WILL BE IMPRESSED JUST
WHAT?
BY THE SMELL OF YOUR CHICKEN.
EVERYBODY WILL BE IMPRESSED JUST
YOU KNOW HOW THAT IS.
BY THE SMELL OF YOUR CHICKEN.
>> YEAH.
YOU KNOW HOW THAT IS.
>> IT'S A NICE --
>> YEAH.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S A NICE --
AND THEN SOME NUTMEG?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SOME NUTMEG.
AND THEN SOME NUTMEG?
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> SOME NUTMEG.
WE GET THAT IN THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.
>> AND WE REALLY -- WE'VE
WE GET THAT IN THERE.
CHOPPED UP THE CHICKEN, MAKE
>> AND WE REALLY -- WE'VE
SURE IT'S THOROUGHLY COOKED.
CHOPPED UP THE CHICKEN, MAKE
>> OH, THIS JUST LOOKS SO GOOD.
SURE IT'S THOROUGHLY COOKED.
SO, SO GOOD.
>> OH, THIS JUST LOOKS SO GOOD.
>> FLAVORS INFUSED.
SO, SO GOOD.
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT THIS
>> FLAVORS INFUSED.
DISH, TOO?
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT THIS
IT'S GOOD LEFTOVER.
DISH, TOO?
YOU KNOW, THE DISHES WHERE IT'S
IT'S GOOD LEFTOVER.
LIKE IT GETS BETTER WITH --
YOU KNOW, THE DISHES WHERE IT'S
>> I KNOW.
LIKE IT GETS BETTER WITH --
IT'S LIKE OVERNIGHT --
>> I KNOW.
>> YEAH, OVERNIGHT THING.
IT'S LIKE OVERNIGHT --
WHAT IS THAT?
>> YEAH, OVERNIGHT THING.
OKAY.
WHAT IS THAT?
>> THAT IS LIKE EVERYTHING
OKAY.
GETTING -- SO, YOU'RE NO
>> THAT IS LIKE EVERYTHING
STRANGER TO ADVENTURES.
GETTING -- SO, YOU'RE NO
I MEAN, YOU'VE HAD THE ADVENTURE
STRANGER TO ADVENTURES.
IN INDONESIA.
I MEAN, YOU'VE HAD THE ADVENTURE
I UNDERSTAND YOUR DAD WAS, LIKE,
IN INDONESIA.
A CRAB FISHERMAN.
I UNDERSTAND YOUR DAD WAS, LIKE,
>> YES, HE'S LIKE THE "DEADLIEST
A CRAB FISHERMAN.
CATCH" GUY.
>> YES, HE'S LIKE THE "DEADLIEST
>> REALLY?
CATCH" GUY.
>> SERIOUSLY, LOOK AT YOU.
>> REALLY?
>> YEAH, THAT'S US FISHING, AND
>> SERIOUSLY, LOOK AT YOU.
OF COURSE, HE CATCHES THE BIGGER
>> YEAH, THAT'S US FISHING, AND
HALIBUT, BUT YEAH.
OF COURSE, HE CATCHES THE BIGGER
THAT'S OUR TRIP TO ALASKA.
HALIBUT, BUT YEAH.
>> YOURS AS WELL.
THAT'S OUR TRIP TO ALASKA.
YOURS AS WELL.
>> YOURS AS WELL.
>> IT'S ALSO -- YEAH.
YOURS AS WELL.
ALSO PRETTY GOOD SIZE FISH,
>> IT'S ALSO -- YEAH.
RIGHT?
ALSO PRETTY GOOD SIZE FISH,
>> SO THIS IS YOUR RICE?
RIGHT?
>> THE RICE.
>> SO THIS IS YOUR RICE?
>> LET ME -- I WANT TO TASTE IT.
>> THE RICE.
>> YES.
>> LET ME -- I WANT TO TASTE IT.
ISN'T THAT NICE?
>> YES.
>> RIGHT?
ISN'T THAT NICE?
>> YES, AND SO WE ADD THE RICE.
>> RIGHT?
>> YEAH.
>> YES, AND SO WE ADD THE RICE.
>> BECAUSE IT IS CHICKEN FRIED
>> YEAH.
RICE.
>> BECAUSE IT IS CHICKEN FRIED
SO IT ALSO PUTS A LITTLE BIT OF
RICE.
A CRISP TO THE RICE.
SO IT ALSO PUTS A LITTLE BIT OF
>> OKAY.
A CRISP TO THE RICE.
>> AND GET THAT IN THERE.
>> OKAY.
>> SO, WE'RE GOING TO GET IN
>> AND GET THAT IN THERE.
THERE.
>> SO, WE'RE GOING TO GET IN
WE'RE GOING TO STIR THIS UP AND
THERE.
WE'RE GOING TO LET THE RICE
WE'RE GOING TO STIR THIS UP AND
COOK.
WE'RE GOING TO LET THE RICE
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO COOK,
COOK.
PLUS MORE FUN WITH DARBY WHEN WE
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO COOK,
COME BACK.
PLUS MORE FUN WITH DARBY WHEN WE
DON'T GO AWAY.
COME BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DON'T GO AWAY.
>> TOMORROW, WE'RE PACKING UP
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THE STATION WAGON AND
>> TOMORROW, WE'RE PACKING UP
CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS.
THE STATION WAGON AND
CLINTON'S HANGING WITH THE
CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS.
FABULOUS CYNTHIA NIXON.
CLINTON'S HANGING WITH THE
AND "GREY'S ANATOMY" STAR
FABULOUS CYNTHIA NIXON.
JAMES PICKENS JR IS SHARING ONE
AND "GREY'S ANATOMY" STAR
OF HIS FAVORITE SOUTHERN
JAMES PICKENS JR IS SHARING ONE
RECIPES.
OF HIS FAVORITE SOUTHERN
IT'S THE CULINARY ADVENTURE OF A
RECIPES.
LIFETIME, TOMORROW ON AN ALL-NEW
IT'S THE CULINARY ADVENTURE OF A
"CHEW."
LIFETIME, TOMORROW ON AN ALL-NEW
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
"CHEW."
♪
What's going on here?
Our insurance company may not
have a Name Your Price Tool
[ shouting ]
but we got disses for days!
Your mother is so lame,
she never put any notes
in your lunch bag.
Sandwiches o-o-only.
Yeah!
Yeah, well if you use
Progressive's Name Your
Price Tool, maybe you
could use the savings
to buy a decent suit.
I got this Jaime.
♪ You could throw
shade all day ♪
♪ But it'll never land ♪
♪ 'Cause we got the
Name Your Price Tool ♪
♪ In the palm
of our h-a-a-and ♪
Mic drop.
Mime: Ouch.
What? It was a sweet burn.
Progressive's Name
Your Price Tool.
Word to your wallet.
(AVO) Did you know two areas
of your brain can make it hard
to lose weight?
CONTRAVE is an FDA-approved
weight-loss medicine that may
help adults who are overweight
or struggle with obesity
lose weight and keep it off.
CONTRAVE is believed to work on
two areas of the brain:
Your hunger center...
(Woman) I'm so hungry.
(AVO) To reduce hunger. And your
reward system...
(Woman) Ice cream.
French fries.
(AVO) To help control cravings.
Across three long-term studies,
CONTRAVE patients lost
approximately 2-4x more weight
than with
diet and exercise alone.
CONTRAVE is not for everyone.
One ingredient in CONTRAVE may
increase suicidal thoughts or
actions in some children, teens,
and young adults within the
first few months.
Other serious side effects
include seizures, increase in
blood pressure or heart rate,
liver damage, manic episodes,
glaucoma and allergic reactions.
Do not take with opioids.
Reduce hunger, help control
cravings.
CONTRAVE. The #1 prescribed
weight-loss brand.
Go to CONTRAVE.com.
For millions of people who
suffer from lower back pain
finding relief can seem
almost as painful.
Finally the search is over.
Drug-free Aleve
Direct Therapy®.
A TENS device with
high intensity power
that uses chnology
once only available in
doctors' offices.
Its smart wireless design
lets you control its intensity
for deep penetrating
relief at the source.
The power of relief
is in your hands.
Aleve Direct Therapy.
Find yours in the
pain relief aisle.
>>> IT'S NOT EASY BEING A
MILLENNIAL.
>> YOU YOUNG WHIPPERSNAPPER, YOU
CAN'T POSSIBLY BE BUYING A
HOUSE.
>> THE STRUGGLE IS REAL AND SO
ARE HIS RHYMES.
>> KEEP DREAMING, BUDDY.
KEEP DREAMING.
>> NEXT "RIGHT THIS MINUTE."
This is Violet.
She's been waiting for
this moment for awhile.
A moment other kids
wouldn't think twice about.
Her first bowl of Cheerios.
Because now that Cheerios are
gluten free,
Violet, and many others
are enjoying their first
bowl today.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>>> WELCOME BACK.
WE'RE IN THE KITCHEN WITH THE
STAR OF ABC'S "SCANDAL,"
DARBY STANCHFIELD!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
OKAY, SO BEFORE THE BREAK, WE
STARTED ON ONE OF HER RECIPES
THAT LOOKS AND SMELLS SO GOOD!
IT'S NASI GORENG, OR FRIED RICE
WITH CHICKEN.
AND, SO DARBY, YOU FINISHED IT
WITH DRIED CHILI AND CAYENNE
PEPPER.
>> CAYENNE, YES.
>> OKAY.
>> JUST TO FINISH IT OFF.
SO LET'S HAVE A TASTE.
>> AND, WE'VE BEEN TALKING --
WE'VE BEEN GABBING ABOUT TEA THE
ENTIRE BREAK.
>> YES.
I LOVE TEA.
>> I KNEW YOU WOULD LOVE THIS,
MARIO.
>> I HAVE SUCH A DEEPER
APPRECIATION FOR TEA AFTER GOING
TO INDONESIA, THE TEA STATE.
>> IT'S SO GOOD!
>> OH, MY GOD.
>> THAT'S NICE.
>> RIGHT?
>> IT'S RIGHT UP MY GAME.
>> YES, MA'AM.
[ APPLAUSE ]
>> YOU TASTE EVERYTHING.
>> YES, RIGHT?
ARE YOU SWEATING YET?
>> AND COLD, WITH AN EGG ON TOP.
COULD YOU IMAGINE?
>> THAT'S RIGHT.
IN THE MORNING.
VERY VERSITILE.
>> OH, MY GOD.
I LOVE IT.
GOING HOME TO MAKE THIS.
>> WHEN WE WERE IN INDONESIA,
SHOOTING THE DOCUMENTARY, WE HAD
THIS.
BREAKFAST, NOON AND DINNER.
BECAUSE, IT'S JUST A VERY
POPULAR DISH.
IT'S A WAY TO BE PURPOSEFUL, YOU
KNOW, WITH LEFTOVERS.
>> YES.
>> RIGHT.
>> OF COURSE.
>> AND, IT'S A REALLY NICE WAY
TO SERVE FAMILIES.
LIKE, GROUPS OF FAMILIES.
LIKE OUR CREW.
SO I LIKE MAKING IT FOR MY
FAMILY.
[ APPLAUSE ]
YOU KNOW?
>> THIS IS JUST THE RIGHT AMOUNT
OF SPICE.
>> YEAH!
>> DARBY, THANK YOU!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
GUYS, MAKE SURE TO CATCH DARBY
IN "SCANDAL" EVERY THURSDAY
NIGHT.
9:00 P.M. EASTERN, RIGHT HERE ON
ABC!
>> UNFORTUNATELY WE'RE OUT OF
TIME.
A BIG THANKS TO DARBY, ALSO A
BIG THANKS TO KEVIN BACON FOR
STOPPING BY.
COME BACK TOMORROW, WE'RE
CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS
WITH CYNTHIA NIXON AND
JAMES PICKENS JR.
GO TO THECHEW.COM FOR ALL THINGS
"CHEW."
AND HAVE A FABULOUS DAY,
EVERYBODY!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
♪
>> Hey, everybody.
I'm hoping to make some people
very rich today.
Maybe million-dollar-rich.
Man, I love my job.
Let's play "Who Wants To Be
A Millionaire."
[cheers and applause]
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
Hey, everybody.
Welcome to the show.
You guys ready to play
"Millionaire" today?
[cheers and applause]
Let's do it.
Whether she's arm wrestling or
playing checkers, our first
contestant is always ready
to compete.
From Spirit Lake, Iowa,
please welcome Katrina Ross.
[cheers and applause]
Hi, Katrina.
How you doing?
>> Wonderful.
>> Welcome.
>> Whoo!
[dramatic music]
>> Welcome to "Millionaire."
>> Thank you.
It's so good to be here.
>> You are competitive?
>> I am so competitive.
>> Almost to a fault?
>> To a fault.
To a fault, I'm passing it on
to my next generation.
>> Okay, you have a
ten-month-old son?
>> I do, Luke, yes.
>> Luke.
>> Yes, and he's starting
to crawl.
>> Yes.
>> And we actually just entered
him in a crawl-off competition.
>> Where would one find a
crawl-off competition?
>> You know, it was during
halftime of a basketball game.
>> Okay.
>> Uh-huh.
>> And they said, "Bring your
babies out..."
>> Said, "Bring your babies out,
we're gonna have them crawl."
We practiced the week ahead
of time.
He was ready to go.
>> You practiced?
I mean, they just do
that, anyway.
I mean, he just crawls.
>> They do, but they
get distracted.
>> That's not practice.
>> They get distracted, so I
wanted to make sure he was
focused, he was fast,
ready to go.
>> I hate it when ten-month-olds
don't focus.
>> I know, it's the worst.
>> Like, "Come on."
>> It's the worst.
Exactly, right?
>> "Act your age."
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Wait, never mind.
Anyway, well, hopefully you can
focus today, because we have
a big objective ahead.
That is $1 million.
Let me tell ya...
Let me tell ya what you're
up against.
14 questions.
The money values growing from
$500 all the way up to that
$1 million.
[cheers and applause]
Every question you answer
correctly moves you one step
closer to that top prize.
Remember, at any time you can
walk away with the money you've
earned up to that point.
If you give me an incorrect
answer, you walk away
with nothing.
That is, until you get to those
two thresholds: $5,000,
then again at $50,000.
Also, you have your
three lifelines.
"Ask the Audience," they can
help you out on a question.
There's the "50/50," we'll take
away two incorrect answers.
And your "Plus One," which
you're gonna tell me about.
Who's here to help you today?
>> I brought my dad here to
help me, Dave.
[cheers and applause]
>> Sometimes a girl just needs
her dad.
>> Sometimes a girl needs
He is my secret weapon.
And I also have my wife,
Kristy, here.
>> Good to have you both.
Dave, good to have you.
Well, hopefully they're just
gonna sit there and watch you
win $1 million.
>> That's what I'm hoping.
>> Are you ready to go?
>> Oh, I think so, let's do it.
>> Let's do it.
Good luck.
Let's play "Who Wants To Be
A Millionaire."
[cheers and applause]
[dramatic musical flourish]
♪ ♪
We start with the $500 question.
>> All right.
>> A fundamental principle of
medical ethics,
"primum non nocere" is a Latin
phrase meaning that first and
foremost, doctors should what?
>> Whew, okay, so...
I know part of the oath that
doctors take includes
"do no harm," so I'm going to
say B, final answer.
>> And they really shouldn't
giggle, either.
>> I hope not.
>> But you're right.
Do no harm.
>> Whoo!
Whoo-hoo!
>> Just like that, you're on
the board, $500.
>> That's the most money I've
ever won in my life, so...
>> That's it.
>> Whew, I'm good.
>> We should be done.
We're gonna take a timeout,
and we'll be back--no.
>> No, let's keep going.
>> You know what?
Let's keep going.
We're here.
>> That's right.
>> $1,000 question, here you go.
A tourism site for the
South Pacific's Cook Islands
credits the locale's beautiful
views to its unofficial ban on
buildings taller than a what?
>> Buildings can be no taller
than a coconut tree.
D, final answer.
>> Makes sense, you're right.
[cheers and applause]
There you go.
>> All right.
>> $1,000 in the bank.
Now a chance to get to $2,000
with this question.
Noting that the latter type
spares "furniture and guests
from unintended blows,"
Party City's website offers
a selection of "traditional"
and "pull string" what?
>> Only one that you are trying
to hit--besides clowns,
'cause I hate clowns--would be
C, piñatas, final answer.
>> 100% correct.
>> Whew!
[cheers and applause]
>> $2,000.
$3,000 question.
>> Okay, whew.
>> The infamous Sony hack of
2014 revealed that which
celebrity once used
batmansenior@mac.com
as his email address?