♪                                >> Announcer: TODAY --           WE'RE MAKING YOUR WEEKNIGHTS
>> Announcer: TODAY --           WE'RE MAKING YOUR WEEKNIGHTS     EASY WITH DELICIOUS DISHES THAT
WE'RE MAKING YOUR WEEKNIGHTS     EASY WITH DELICIOUS DISHES THAT  PACK A PUNCH!
EASY WITH DELICIOUS DISHES THAT  PACK A PUNCH!                    IT'S TIME FOR "THE CHEW'S"
PACK A PUNCH!                    IT'S TIME FOR "THE CHEW'S"       WEEKNIGHT WOWS!
IT'S TIME FOR "THE CHEW'S"       WEEKNIGHT WOWS!                  MARIO'S CUTTIN' FOOTLOOSE IN THE
WEEKNIGHT WOWS!                  MARIO'S CUTTIN' FOOTLOOSE IN THE KITCHEN WITH THE
MARIO'S CUTTIN' FOOTLOOSE IN THE KITCHEN WITH THE                 INCREDIBLE KEVIN BACON!
KITCHEN WITH THE                 INCREDIBLE KEVIN BACON!          THEN -- REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK
INCREDIBLE KEVIN BACON!          THEN -- REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK    CONTINUES -- AND CLINTON'S
THEN -- REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK    CONTINUES -- AND CLINTON'S       TEAMING UP WITH MICHAEL TO MAKE
CONTINUES -- AND CLINTON'S       TEAMING UP WITH MICHAEL TO MAKE  A MEDITERRANEAN FAVORITE THAT'LL
TEAMING UP WITH MICHAEL TO MAKE  A MEDITERRANEAN FAVORITE THAT'LL LEAVE YOU STUFFED!
A MEDITERRANEAN FAVORITE THAT'LL LEAVE YOU STUFFED!               PLUS CARLA'S HANGING WITH THE
LEAVE YOU STUFFED!               PLUS CARLA'S HANGING WITH THE    STAR OF "SCANDAL" --
PLUS CARLA'S HANGING WITH THE    STAR OF "SCANDAL" --             DARBY STANCHFIELD!
STAR OF "SCANDAL" --             DARBY STANCHFIELD!               WE'RE GETTING WOWED, RIGHT NOW,
DARBY STANCHFIELD!               WE'RE GETTING WOWED, RIGHT NOW,  ON "THE CHEW"!
WE'RE GETTING WOWED, RIGHT NOW,  ON "THE CHEW"!                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
ON "THE CHEW"!                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
>>> HELLO AND WELCOME TO "THE    CHEW"!                           THANK YOU, GUYS!
CHEW"!                           THANK YOU, GUYS!                 YOU KNOW, IF YOUR MONDAY WAS
THANK YOU, GUYS!                 YOU KNOW, IF YOUR MONDAY WAS     "MEH" AND YOUR TUESDAY WAS
YOU KNOW, IF YOUR MONDAY WAS     "MEH" AND YOUR TUESDAY WAS       "TIRED" -- THEN GET READY TO
"MEH" AND YOUR TUESDAY WAS       "TIRED" -- THEN GET READY TO     HAVE YOUR WEEK SHAKEN UP!
"TIRED" -- THEN GET READY TO     HAVE YOUR WEEK SHAKEN UP!        OUR DISHES TODAY ALL PACK A
HAVE YOUR WEEK SHAKEN UP!        OUR DISHES TODAY ALL PACK A      "POW" AND WILL MAKE YOU SAY --
OUR DISHES TODAY ALL PACK A      "POW" AND WILL MAKE YOU SAY --   >> Audience: WOW!
"POW" AND WILL MAKE YOU SAY --   >> Audience: WOW!                >> WOW!
>> Audience: WOW!                >> WOW!                          IT'S AN HOUR OF QUICK AND EASY
>> WOW!                          IT'S AN HOUR OF QUICK AND EASY   "WEEKNIGHT WOWS"!
IT'S AN HOUR OF QUICK AND EASY   "WEEKNIGHT WOWS"!                [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
"WEEKNIGHT WOWS"!                [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> WOWSER!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> WOWSER!                       >> HOW YOU GUYS DOIN'?
>> WOWSER!                       >> HOW YOU GUYS DOIN'?           >> FANTASTIC!
>> HOW YOU GUYS DOIN'?           >> FANTASTIC!                    >> GREAT!
>> FANTASTIC!                    >> GREAT!                        >> HUMP DAY!
>> GREAT!                        >> HUMP DAY!                     HAVE YOU HAD ANY "WEEKNIGHT
>> HUMP DAY!                     HAVE YOU HAD ANY "WEEKNIGHT      WOWS" LATELY -- MEAL-WISE?
HAVE YOU HAD ANY "WEEKNIGHT      WOWS" LATELY -- MEAL-WISE?       [ LAUGHTER ]
WOWS" LATELY -- MEAL-WISE?       [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> I WAS LIKE, "YES."
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> I WAS LIKE, "YES."            >> OH, REALLY?
>> I WAS LIKE, "YES."            >> OH, REALLY?                   OKAY.
>> OH, REALLY?                   OKAY.                            [ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY.                            [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> LYING!
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> LYING!                        >> LYING.
>> LYING!                        >> LYING.                        >> LYING.
>> LYING.                        >> LYING.                        >> OH, I HAD ONE.
>> LYING.                        >> OH, I HAD ONE.                >> NO, HE WAS TALKING ABOUT LIKE
>> OH, I HAD ONE.                >> NO, HE WAS TALKING ABOUT LIKE WITH -- YOURSELF.
>> NO, HE WAS TALKING ABOUT LIKE WITH -- YOURSELF.                >> OH!
WITH -- YOURSELF.                >> OH!                           >> WE SAY "WOW."
>> OH!                           >> WE SAY "WOW."                 YES.
>> WE SAY "WOW."                 YES.                             >> OKAY, GO ON.
YES.                             >> OKAY, GO ON.                  [ LAUGHTER ]
>> OKAY, GO ON.                  [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING --
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING --      >> THINK ABOUT IT.
>> I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING --      >> THINK ABOUT IT.               >> I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.
>> THINK ABOUT IT.               >> I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.        >> CARLA HALL LIVE FROM THE
>> I DON'T HAVE ANYTHING.        >> CARLA HALL LIVE FROM THE      BEDROOM.
>> CARLA HALL LIVE FROM THE      BEDROOM.                         "I'M TAKIN' A NAP!"
BEDROOM.                         "I'M TAKIN' A NAP!"              >> NO, BUT IN TERMS OF FOOD, I
"I'M TAKIN' A NAP!"              >> NO, BUT IN TERMS OF FOOD, I   HAVE.
>> NO, BUT IN TERMS OF FOOD, I   HAVE.                            >> WHAT'D YOU COOK?
HAVE.                            >> WHAT'D YOU COOK?              >> I COOKED A MOROCCAN BEAN
>> WHAT'D YOU COOK?              >> I COOKED A MOROCCAN BEAN      SALAD AND INSPIRATION WAS
>> I COOKED A MOROCCAN BEAN      SALAD AND INSPIRATION WAS        FROM --
SALAD AND INSPIRATION WAS        FROM --                          MORRIS CHESTNUT CAME TO THE
FROM --                          MORRIS CHESTNUT CAME TO THE      SHOW.
MORRIS CHESTNUT CAME TO THE      SHOW.                            >> OH, YEAH.
SHOW.                            >> OH, YEAH.                     >> AND HE HAD HIS BOOK, "THE
>> OH, YEAH.                     >> AND HE HAD HIS BOOK, "THE     CUT."
>> AND HE HAD HIS BOOK, "THE     CUT."                            AND SO ONE OF THE RECIPES --
CUT."                            AND SO ONE OF THE RECIPES --     THIS BEAN SALAD IS NOT YOUR
AND SO ONE OF THE RECIPES --     THIS BEAN SALAD IS NOT YOUR      MOMMA'S, NOT YOUR SOUTHERN "AT A
THIS BEAN SALAD IS NOT YOUR      MOMMA'S, NOT YOUR SOUTHERN "AT A PICNIC", THREE BEAN, SLOPPY
MOMMA'S, NOT YOUR SOUTHERN "AT A PICNIC", THREE BEAN, SLOPPY      SALAD.
PICNIC", THREE BEAN, SLOPPY      SALAD.                           THIS IS A SPICY --
SALAD.                           THIS IS A SPICY --               IT IS DELICIOUS.
THIS IS A SPICY --               IT IS DELICIOUS.                 IT HAS HARISSA AND ONIONS AND
IT IS DELICIOUS.                 IT HAS HARISSA AND ONIONS AND    CARROTS AND HERBS.
IT HAS HARISSA AND ONIONS AND    CARROTS AND HERBS.               >> IT LOOKS GOOD.
CARROTS AND HERBS.               >> IT LOOKS GOOD.                >> IT IS SO FREAKIN' GOOD!
>> IT LOOKS GOOD.                >> IT IS SO FREAKIN' GOOD!       >> DID YOU HAVE THAT AS YOUR
>> IT IS SO FREAKIN' GOOD!       >> DID YOU HAVE THAT AS YOUR     MAIN COURSE?
>> DID YOU HAVE THAT AS YOUR     MAIN COURSE?                     >> I DID.
MAIN COURSE?                     >> I DID.                        >> YOU DID?
>> I DID.                        >> YOU DID?                      >> I DID.
>> YOU DID?                      >> I DID.                        >> WHAT ELSE DID YOU SERVE WITH
>> I DID.                        >> WHAT ELSE DID YOU SERVE WITH  IT?
>> WHAT ELSE DID YOU SERVE WITH  IT?                              >> THAT WAS IT.
IT?                              >> THAT WAS IT.                  [ LAUGHTER ]
>> THAT WAS IT.                  [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> OH.
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> OH.                           >> OH, MY GOD.
>> OH.                           >> OH, MY GOD.                   YEAH, THESE ELECTRIC KISSES --
>> OH, MY GOD.                   YEAH, THESE ELECTRIC KISSES --   [ LAUGHTER ]
YEAH, THESE ELECTRIC KISSES --   [ LAUGHTER ]                     THEY HAD MY EARRINGS POPPING
[ LAUGHTER ]                     THEY HAD MY EARRINGS POPPING     OFF!
THEY HAD MY EARRINGS POPPING     OFF!                             >> HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS?
OFF!                             >> HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS?           COOK ANYTHING GOOD THIS WEEK?
>> HOW ABOUT YOU GUYS?           COOK ANYTHING GOOD THIS WEEK?    >> I MADE A LITTLE, YOU KNOW --
COOK ANYTHING GOOD THIS WEEK?    >> I MADE A LITTLE, YOU KNOW --  BEEN A LITTLE BIT CRAZY AT THE
>> I MADE A LITTLE, YOU KNOW --  BEEN A LITTLE BIT CRAZY AT THE   RESTAURANT, BUT LIZ AND I STILL
BEEN A LITTLE BIT CRAZY AT THE   RESTAURANT, BUT LIZ AND I STILL  TRY TO SIT DOWN FOR DINNER
RESTAURANT, BUT LIZ AND I STILL  TRY TO SIT DOWN FOR DINNER       BEFORE A SHIFT.
TRY TO SIT DOWN FOR DINNER       BEFORE A SHIFT.                  SO, WE MADE SOME RICOTTA RAVIOLI
BEFORE A SHIFT.                  SO, WE MADE SOME RICOTTA RAVIOLI WITH A LITTLE BIT OF SAGE AND
SO, WE MADE SOME RICOTTA RAVIOLI WITH A LITTLE BIT OF SAGE AND    BROWN BUTTER.
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF SAGE AND    BROWN BUTTER.                    >> OH, THAT'S MY FAVORITE SAUCE
BROWN BUTTER.                    >> OH, THAT'S MY FAVORITE SAUCE  IN --
>> OH, THAT'S MY FAVORITE SAUCE  IN --                            >> I KNOW.
IN --                            >> I KNOW.                       >> OH, MY GOD!
>> I KNOW.                       >> OH, MY GOD!                   THAT LOOKS SO GOOD.
>> OH, MY GOD!                   THAT LOOKS SO GOOD.              >> PLASTIC, PUT THE -- AND READY
THAT LOOKS SO GOOD.              >> PLASTIC, PUT THE -- AND READY COOKIE --
>> PLASTIC, PUT THE -- AND READY COOKIE --                        >> I AM A GENIUS.
COOKIE --                        >> I AM A GENIUS.                >> STOLE THAT ONE RIGHT FROM --
>> I AM A GENIUS.                >> STOLE THAT ONE RIGHT FROM --  >> YEAH, BUT I STOLE -- RIGHT,
>> STOLE THAT ONE RIGHT FROM --  >> YEAH, BUT I STOLE -- RIGHT,   EXACTLY.
>> YEAH, BUT I STOLE -- RIGHT,   EXACTLY.                         I STOLE THAT FROM MOLDOVAN
EXACTLY.                         I STOLE THAT FROM MOLDOVAN       CULTURE FROM 200 YEARS AGO.
I STOLE THAT FROM MOLDOVAN       CULTURE FROM 200 YEARS AGO.      >> I KNOW.
CULTURE FROM 200 YEARS AGO.      >> I KNOW.                       IT'S SO GOOD THOUGH.
>> I KNOW.                       IT'S SO GOOD THOUGH.             THAT COOKIE JUST MAKES ALL THE
IT'S SO GOOD THOUGH.             THAT COOKIE JUST MAKES ALL THE   DIFFERENCE.
THAT COOKIE JUST MAKES ALL THE   DIFFERENCE.                      >> IT REALLY TURNS IT UP.
DIFFERENCE.                      >> IT REALLY TURNS IT UP.        >> YEAH.
>> IT REALLY TURNS IT UP.        >> YEAH.                         >> BUT WE COOK -- I COOK A LOT
>> YEAH.                         >> BUT WE COOK -- I COOK A LOT   ON THE WEEKDAYS JUST 'CAUSE IT'S
>> BUT WE COOK -- I COOK A LOT   ON THE WEEKDAYS JUST 'CAUSE IT'S SIMPLE AND FASTER.
ON THE WEEKDAYS JUST 'CAUSE IT'S SIMPLE AND FASTER.               AND I'VE BEEN ROASTING CHICKENS
SIMPLE AND FASTER.               AND I'VE BEEN ROASTING CHICKENS  FOR
AND I'VE BEEN ROASTING CHICKENS  FOR                              A LONG TIME.
FOR                              A LONG TIME.                     MY WIFE, HOWEVER, DOESN'T LIKE
A LONG TIME.                     MY WIFE, HOWEVER, DOESN'T LIKE   IT WHEN IT'S A LITTLE PINK ON
MY WIFE, HOWEVER, DOESN'T LIKE   IT WHEN IT'S A LITTLE PINK ON    THE THIGH BONE, SO I'VE
IT WHEN IT'S A LITTLE PINK ON    THE THIGH BONE, SO I'VE          SPATCHCOCKED THE CHICKEN --
THE THIGH BONE, SO I'VE          SPATCHCOCKED THE CHICKEN --      >> OH, YOU'RE A SPATCHCOCK.
SPATCHCOCKED THE CHICKEN --      >> OH, YOU'RE A SPATCHCOCK.      >> AND THERE'S A PICTURE RIGHT
>> OH, YOU'RE A SPATCHCOCK.      >> AND THERE'S A PICTURE RIGHT   THERE.
>> AND THERE'S A PICTURE RIGHT   THERE.                           >> YES!
THERE.                           >> YES!                          >> SPATCHCOCKED.
>> YES!                          >> SPATCHCOCKED.                 I LOVE IT OVER VEGETABLES THAT
>> SPATCHCOCKED.                 I LOVE IT OVER VEGETABLES THAT   GIVE THE LITTLE GREASY CHICKEN
I LOVE IT OVER VEGETABLES THAT   GIVE THE LITTLE GREASY CHICKEN   BITS DOWN BELOW.
GIVE THE LITTLE GREASY CHICKEN   BITS DOWN BELOW.                 AND THEN IT'S RAMP SEASON RIGHT
BITS DOWN BELOW.                 AND THEN IT'S RAMP SEASON RIGHT  NOW ALL OVER THE EAST COAST AND
AND THEN IT'S RAMP SEASON RIGHT  NOW ALL OVER THE EAST COAST AND  SOMETIMES IN THE MIDWEST, AND
NOW ALL OVER THE EAST COAST AND  SOMETIMES IN THE MIDWEST, AND    EVEN ON THE WEST COAST.
SOMETIMES IN THE MIDWEST, AND    EVEN ON THE WEST COAST.          SO, JUST SAUTEED RAMPS WHICH
EVEN ON THE WEST COAST.          SO, JUST SAUTEED RAMPS WHICH     WERE KIND OF LIKE GARLICKY
SO, JUST SAUTEED RAMPS WHICH     WERE KIND OF LIKE GARLICKY       ONIONS THAT YOU JUST SERVE ON
WERE KIND OF LIKE GARLICKY       ONIONS THAT YOU JUST SERVE ON    THE SIDE.
ONIONS THAT YOU JUST SERVE ON    THE SIDE.                        AND AS LONG AS YOU MAKE THE SAME
THE SIDE.                        AND AS LONG AS YOU MAKE THE SAME AMOUNT, THEN YOU CAN MAKE ALL --
AND AS LONG AS YOU MAKE THE SAME AMOUNT, THEN YOU CAN MAKE ALL -- [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
AMOUNT, THEN YOU CAN MAKE ALL -- [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> I WANNA BRING UP A POINT REAL
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> I WANNA BRING UP A POINT REAL FAST.
>> I WANNA BRING UP A POINT REAL FAST.                            THE EAST COASTERS THINK THEY
FAST.                            THE EAST COASTERS THINK THEY     INVENTED RAMPS, BUT THEY'VE BEEN
THE EAST COASTERS THINK THEY     INVENTED RAMPS, BUT THEY'VE BEEN A MIDWESTERN STAPLE FOR A LONG
INVENTED RAMPS, BUT THEY'VE BEEN A MIDWESTERN STAPLE FOR A LONG   TIME.
A MIDWESTERN STAPLE FOR A LONG   TIME.                            >> FIRST OF ALL, I AGREE WITH
TIME.                            >> FIRST OF ALL, I AGREE WITH    YOU.
>> FIRST OF ALL, I AGREE WITH    YOU.                             IT'S ONLY THE EAST COAST, BUT WE
YOU.                             IT'S ONLY THE EAST COAST, BUT WE CHARGE $20.
IT'S ONLY THE EAST COAST, BUT WE CHARGE $20.                      [ LAUGHTER ]
CHARGE $20.                      [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WILL THAT JUST COVER IT?
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WILL THAT JUST COVER IT?      >> IN THE MIDWEST YOU GO INTO
>> WILL THAT JUST COVER IT?      >> IN THE MIDWEST YOU GO INTO    THE WOODS AND YOU JUST --
>> IN THE MIDWEST YOU GO INTO    THE WOODS AND YOU JUST --        >> CARLA, SAME AS HERE.
THE WOODS AND YOU JUST --        >> CARLA, SAME AS HERE.          HOW ABOUT YOU, CLINTON?
>> CARLA, SAME AS HERE.          HOW ABOUT YOU, CLINTON?          >> I MADE A DELICIOUS --
HOW ABOUT YOU, CLINTON?          >> I MADE A DELICIOUS --         ON MONDAY NIGHT, I MADE MY
>> I MADE A DELICIOUS --         ON MONDAY NIGHT, I MADE MY       FAMOUS BUTTERMILK CHICKEN AND MY
ON MONDAY NIGHT, I MADE MY       FAMOUS BUTTERMILK CHICKEN AND MY ALL-TIME FAVORITE SALAD.
FAMOUS BUTTERMILK CHICKEN AND MY ALL-TIME FAVORITE SALAD.         IT'S THE SAME THAT I MADE
ALL-TIME FAVORITE SALAD.         IT'S THE SAME THAT I MADE        WITH --
IT'S THE SAME THAT I MADE        WITH --                          >> OH, YES!
WITH --                          >> OH, YES!                      >> WHEN SHE WAS HERE.
>> OH, YES!                      >> WHEN SHE WAS HERE.            I GOT TO TELL YOU, THAT SALAD IS
>> WHEN SHE WAS HERE.            I GOT TO TELL YOU, THAT SALAD IS THE BEST SALAD IN THE WORLD!
I GOT TO TELL YOU, THAT SALAD IS THE BEST SALAD IN THE WORLD!     >> IT'S SO GOOD!
THE BEST SALAD IN THE WORLD!     >> IT'S SO GOOD!                 >> SO GOOD, RIGHT?
>> IT'S SO GOOD!                 >> SO GOOD, RIGHT?               >> YES!
>> SO GOOD, RIGHT?               >> YES!                          >> IT'S GOT WALNUTS AND BLUE
>> YES!                          >> IT'S GOT WALNUTS AND BLUE     CHEESE.
>> IT'S GOT WALNUTS AND BLUE     CHEESE.                          >> OH, MY GOD!
CHEESE.                          >> OH, MY GOD!                   >> AND AVOCADO AND BABY ARUGULA.
>> OH, MY GOD!                   >> AND AVOCADO AND BABY ARUGULA. >> MMM.
>> AND AVOCADO AND BABY ARUGULA. >> MMM.                          >> A REAL -— AN EASY
>> MMM.                          >> A REAL -— AN EASY             VINAIGRETTE.
>> A REAL -— AN EASY             VINAIGRETTE.                     SO, THAT WAS MY --
VINAIGRETTE.                     SO, THAT WAS MY --               >> LOOK AT US COOKING ON A --
SO, THAT WAS MY --               >> LOOK AT US COOKING ON A --    >> I KNOW!
>> LOOK AT US COOKING ON A --    >> I KNOW!                       >> IMAGINE THAT.
>> I KNOW!                       >> IMAGINE THAT.                 WE CAN COOK WHEN WE GO HOME.
>> IMAGINE THAT.                 WE CAN COOK WHEN WE GO HOME.     >> YES!
WE CAN COOK WHEN WE GO HOME.     >> YES!                          >> RIGHT?
>> YES!                          >> RIGHT?                        ALL RIGHT.
>> RIGHT?                        ALL RIGHT.                       SO, MOTHER'S DAY IS AROUND THE
ALL RIGHT.                       SO, MOTHER'S DAY IS AROUND THE   CORNER, SO I THOUGHT --
SO, MOTHER'S DAY IS AROUND THE   CORNER, SO I THOUGHT --          [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
CORNER, SO I THOUGHT --          [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          HEY, MOM!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          HEY, MOM!                        >> HEY, MOMMA!
HEY, MOM!                        >> HEY, MOMMA!                   >> WHO HERE HAS A MOTHER?
>> HEY, MOMMA!                   >> WHO HERE HAS A MOTHER?        YAY!
>> WHO HERE HAS A MOTHER?        YAY!                             >> I BELIEVE THIS IS THE MOST
YAY!                             >> I BELIEVE THIS IS THE MOST    IMPORTANT DAY OF THE YEAR.
>> I BELIEVE THIS IS THE MOST    IMPORTANT DAY OF THE YEAR.       >> YOU LOVE ANGEL.
IMPORTANT DAY OF THE YEAR.       >> YOU LOVE ANGEL.               >> I LOVE ANGEL AND LIZ --
>> YOU LOVE ANGEL.               >> I LOVE ANGEL AND LIZ --       YOU KNOW, I LOVE MOTHER'S DAY.
>> I LOVE ANGEL AND LIZ --       YOU KNOW, I LOVE MOTHER'S DAY.   >> I DO, TOO!
YOU KNOW, I LOVE MOTHER'S DAY.   >> I DO, TOO!                    >> MY DAD ALWAYS GETS --
>> I DO, TOO!                    >> MY DAD ALWAYS GETS --         HE'S ALWAYS, "WHAT ABOUT -- YOU
>> MY DAD ALWAYS GETS --         HE'S ALWAYS, "WHAT ABOUT -- YOU  GET ME A SLEEVE OF GOLF BALLS?"
HE'S ALWAYS, "WHAT ABOUT -- YOU  GET ME A SLEEVE OF GOLF BALLS?"  I'M LIKE, "OH, WE CELEBRATE --"
GET ME A SLEEVE OF GOLF BALLS?"  I'M LIKE, "OH, WE CELEBRATE --"  [ LAUGHTER ]
I'M LIKE, "OH, WE CELEBRATE --"  [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WELL, WE HAVE A MOTHER'S DAY
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WELL, WE HAVE A MOTHER'S DAY  INSPIRED TASTING HERE.
>> WELL, WE HAVE A MOTHER'S DAY  INSPIRED TASTING HERE.           THESE ARE FROM THE RESTAURANT
INSPIRED TASTING HERE.           THESE ARE FROM THE RESTAURANT    AREPERA --
THESE ARE FROM THE RESTAURANT    AREPERA --                       NO, I MESSED IT UP!
AREPERA --                       NO, I MESSED IT UP!              AREPERA --
NO, I MESSED IT UP!              AREPERA --                       >> A PERA?
AREPERA --                       >> A PERA?                       >> AREPERA GUACUCO.
>> A PERA?                       >> AREPERA GUACUCO.              I HAD IT BEFORE!
>> AREPERA GUACUCO.              I HAD IT BEFORE!                 [ LAUGHTER ]
I HAD IT BEFORE!                 [ LAUGHTER ]                     WHY DIDN'T I TAKE FRENCH IN HIGH
[ LAUGHTER ]                     WHY DIDN'T I TAKE FRENCH IN HIGH SCHOOL?
WHY DIDN'T I TAKE FRENCH IN HIGH SCHOOL?                          HOW DO YOU SAY THAT RESTAURANT
SCHOOL?                          HOW DO YOU SAY THAT RESTAURANT   NAME?
HOW DO YOU SAY THAT RESTAURANT   NAME?                            >> AREPERA GUACUCO.
NAME?                            >> AREPERA GUACUCO.              >> THERE YOU GO.
>> AREPERA GUACUCO.              >> THERE YOU GO.                 AND THAT WAS A TOUGH --
>> THERE YOU GO.                 AND THAT WAS A TOUGH --          >> AREPERA GUACUCO.
AND THAT WAS A TOUGH --          >> AREPERA GUACUCO.              SAY IT.
>> AREPERA GUACUCO.              SAY IT.                          >> NO.
SAY IT.                          >> NO.                           IT'S IN BROOKLYN, NEW YORK.
>> NO.                           IT'S IN BROOKLYN, NEW YORK.      BUT THESE ARE AREPAS WHICH ARE
IT'S IN BROOKLYN, NEW YORK.      BUT THESE ARE AREPAS WHICH ARE   "REINA PEPIADA" AREPAS.
BUT THESE ARE AREPAS WHICH ARE   "REINA PEPIADA" AREPAS.          THEY'VE GOT SHREDDED CHICKEN AND
"REINA PEPIADA" AREPAS.          THEY'VE GOT SHREDDED CHICKEN AND AVOCADO IN THEM.
THEY'VE GOT SHREDDED CHICKEN AND AVOCADO IN THEM.                 AND THEY ARE A MOTHER'S DAY
AVOCADO IN THEM.                 AND THEY ARE A MOTHER'S DAY      INSPIRED TASTING BECAUSE
AND THEY ARE A MOTHER'S DAY      INSPIRED TASTING BECAUSE         LEONARDO MOLINA NAMED THE
INSPIRED TASTING BECAUSE         LEONARDO MOLINA NAMED THE        RESTAURANT AFTER THE BEACH IN
LEONARDO MOLINA NAMED THE        RESTAURANT AFTER THE BEACH IN    VENEZUELA WHERE IT WAS BORN AND
RESTAURANT AFTER THE BEACH IN    VENEZUELA WHERE IT WAS BORN AND  HIS MOTHER, CARMEN, COOKS ALL
VENEZUELA WHERE IT WAS BORN AND  HIS MOTHER, CARMEN, COOKS ALL    THE FOOD AND IS KNOWN FOR HER
HIS MOTHER, CARMEN, COOKS ALL    THE FOOD AND IS KNOWN FOR HER    INCREDIBLE AREPAS, WHICH SHE
THE FOOD AND IS KNOWN FOR HER    INCREDIBLE AREPAS, WHICH SHE     MAKES FRESH.
INCREDIBLE AREPAS, WHICH SHE     MAKES FRESH.                     >> MMM.
MAKES FRESH.                     >> MMM.                          >> THESE ARE DELICIOUS.
>> MMM.                          >> THESE ARE DELICIOUS.          >> THEY'RE DELICIOUS.
>> THESE ARE DELICIOUS.          >> THEY'RE DELICIOUS.            >> MMM.
>> THEY'RE DELICIOUS.            >> MMM.                          >> MMM!
>> MMM.                          >> MMM!                          >> DELICIOUS.
>> MMM!                          >> DELICIOUS.                    NOT TRADITIONAL THIS WAY, BUT
>> DELICIOUS.                    NOT TRADITIONAL THIS WAY, BUT    EXCELLENT.
NOT TRADITIONAL THIS WAY, BUT    EXCELLENT.                       >> I KNOW!
EXCELLENT.                       >> I KNOW!                       AND THE AREPA IS SO TENDER.
>> I KNOW!                       AND THE AREPA IS SO TENDER.      >> MMM.
AND THE AREPA IS SO TENDER.      >> MMM.                          >> DELICIOUS.
>> MMM.                          >> DELICIOUS.                    >> WHAT'S NEXT, CLINTON?
>> DELICIOUS.                    >> WHAT'S NEXT, CLINTON?         WHAT'S NEXT?
>> WHAT'S NEXT, CLINTON?         WHAT'S NEXT?                     >> WELL, WE'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT
WHAT'S NEXT?                     >> WELL, WE'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT  CELEBRITIES WITH THEIR SHIRTS
>> WELL, WE'RE GONNA TALK ABOUT  CELEBRITIES WITH THEIR SHIRTS    OFF.
CELEBRITIES WITH THEIR SHIRTS    OFF.                             >> OH.
OFF.                             >> OH.                           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OH.                           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> I LOVE A GOOD -- CELEBRITIES
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> I LOVE A GOOD -- CELEBRITIES  WITH THEIR SHIRTS OFF.
>> I LOVE A GOOD -- CELEBRITIES  WITH THEIR SHIRTS OFF.           >> YEAH.
WITH THEIR SHIRTS OFF.           >> YEAH.                         WELL, THIS IS THE THING.
>> YEAH.                         WELL, THIS IS THE THING.         THERE'S A NEW TREND HAPPENING
WELL, THIS IS THE THING.         THERE'S A NEW TREND HAPPENING    RIGHT NOW.
THERE'S A NEW TREND HAPPENING    RIGHT NOW.                       IF YOU WANT TO GO VIRAL IN THE
RIGHT NOW.                       IF YOU WANT TO GO VIRAL IN THE   KITCHEN, THE BEST WAY TO DO IT
IF YOU WANT TO GO VIRAL IN THE   KITCHEN, THE BEST WAY TO DO IT   IS TAKE OFF YOUR SHIRT AND COOK
KITCHEN, THE BEST WAY TO DO IT   IS TAKE OFF YOUR SHIRT AND COOK  AN EGG.
IS TAKE OFF YOUR SHIRT AND COOK  AN EGG.                          >> YES!
AN EGG.                          >> YES!                          >> HOLD ON!
>> YES!                          >> HOLD ON!                      HOLD ON!
>> HOLD ON!                      HOLD ON!                         >> I WOULD SAY "SUPER TREND."
HOLD ON!                         >> I WOULD SAY "SUPER TREND."    >> WELL, NO.
>> I WOULD SAY "SUPER TREND."    >> WELL, NO.                     WHAT IF IT'S NICOLE KIDMAN?
>> WELL, NO.                     WHAT IF IT'S NICOLE KIDMAN?      [ LAUGHTER ]
WHAT IF IT'S NICOLE KIDMAN?      [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> THESE ARE ALL MEN.
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> THESE ARE ALL MEN.            >> OH.
>> THESE ARE ALL MEN.            >> OH.                           >> YEAH, YEAH.
>> OH.                           >> YEAH, YEAH.                   >> I WAS THINKING ABOUT DOING
>> YEAH, YEAH.                   >> I WAS THINKING ABOUT DOING    IT, BUT OH WELL.
>> I WAS THINKING ABOUT DOING    IT, BUT OH WELL.                 >> YOU KNOW NICK VIALL FROM "THE
IT, BUT OH WELL.                 >> YOU KNOW NICK VIALL FROM "THE BACHELOR", RIGHT?
>> YOU KNOW NICK VIALL FROM "THE BACHELOR", RIGHT?                WELL, HIS FIANCE, VANESSA, JUST
BACHELOR", RIGHT?                WELL, HIS FIANCE, VANESSA, JUST  SHARED A PHOTO OF HIM --
WELL, HIS FIANCE, VANESSA, JUST  SHARED A PHOTO OF HIM --         [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
SHARED A PHOTO OF HIM --         [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          COOKING TOPLESS.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          COOKING TOPLESS.                 >> I'M SORRY.
COOKING TOPLESS.                 >> I'M SORRY.                    HE DID LIKE 60 PUSH-UPS AND THEN
>> I'M SORRY.                    HE DID LIKE 60 PUSH-UPS AND THEN SAID, "HONEY, TAKE A PICTURE."
HE DID LIKE 60 PUSH-UPS AND THEN SAID, "HONEY, TAKE A PICTURE."   >> I KNOW.
SAID, "HONEY, TAKE A PICTURE."   >> I KNOW.                       YOU CAN TELL BY THE FACT THAT
>> I KNOW.                       YOU CAN TELL BY THE FACT THAT    HIS ARMS ARE LIKE LITERALLY
YOU CAN TELL BY THE FACT THAT    HIS ARMS ARE LIKE LITERALLY      BULGING OUT RIGHT THEN.
HIS ARMS ARE LIKE LITERALLY      BULGING OUT RIGHT THEN.          >> I JUST DON'T FEEL THAT YOU
BULGING OUT RIGHT THEN.          >> I JUST DON'T FEEL THAT YOU    SHOULD BE --
>> I JUST DON'T FEEL THAT YOU    SHOULD BE --                     YOU KNOW, AS SOMEONE WHO'S
SHOULD BE --                     YOU KNOW, AS SOMEONE WHO'S       COOKED FOR A LIVING FOR THE
YOU KNOW, AS SOMEONE WHO'S       COOKED FOR A LIVING FOR THE      MAJORITY OF THEIR LIFE, TO GET
COOKED FOR A LIVING FOR THE      MAJORITY OF THEIR LIFE, TO GET   IN FRONT OF A STOVE WHERE HOT
MAJORITY OF THEIR LIFE, TO GET   IN FRONT OF A STOVE WHERE HOT    FAT IS SPLASHING AROUND.
IN FRONT OF A STOVE WHERE HOT    FAT IS SPLASHING AROUND.         >> YEAH.
FAT IS SPLASHING AROUND.         >> YEAH.                         >> WHEN YOU'RE 27, WHO CARES!
>> YEAH.                         >> WHEN YOU'RE 27, WHO CARES!    >> WHO CARES!
>> WHEN YOU'RE 27, WHO CARES!    >> WHO CARES!                    >> STILL BUBBLIN' AROUND.
>> WHO CARES!                    >> STILL BUBBLIN' AROUND.        ALL RIGHT.
>> STILL BUBBLIN' AROUND.        ALL RIGHT.                       WELL, HE'S NOT THE FIRST.
ALL RIGHT.                       WELL, HE'S NOT THE FIRST.        USHER ALSO MADE BREAKFAST IN
WELL, HE'S NOT THE FIRST.        USHER ALSO MADE BREAKFAST IN     NOTHING BUT UNDERWEAR.
USHER ALSO MADE BREAKFAST IN     NOTHING BUT UNDERWEAR.           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
NOTHING BUT UNDERWEAR.           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          I GOT TO TELL YOU, USHER --
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          I GOT TO TELL YOU, USHER --      ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE IN GOOD SHAPE,
I GOT TO TELL YOU, USHER --      ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE IN GOOD SHAPE, MAN, BUT YOU'RE KILLIN' THAT
ALL RIGHT, YOU'RE IN GOOD SHAPE, MAN, BUT YOU'RE KILLIN' THAT     EGG.
MAN, BUT YOU'RE KILLIN' THAT     EGG.                             >> KILLIN' AN EGG!
EGG.                             >> KILLIN' AN EGG!               >> I LOOKED AT THAT EGG UP
>> KILLIN' AN EGG!               >> I LOOKED AT THAT EGG UP       CLOSE, IT IS BEING --
>> I LOOKED AT THAT EGG UP       CLOSE, IT IS BEING --            >> THAT EGG LOOKS --
CLOSE, IT IS BEING --            >> THAT EGG LOOKS --             THAT EGG IS DEAD.
>> THAT EGG LOOKS --             THAT EGG IS DEAD.                >> USHER, YOU MAY HAVE IT ALL,
THAT EGG IS DEAD.                >> USHER, YOU MAY HAVE IT ALL,   BUT WE GOT THE EGG.
>> USHER, YOU MAY HAVE IT ALL,   BUT WE GOT THE EGG.              >> WE GOT THE EGG.
BUT WE GOT THE EGG.              >> WE GOT THE EGG.               >> WE GOT THE EGG, USHER.
>> WE GOT THE EGG.               >> WE GOT THE EGG, USHER.        >> I'M NEVER GONNA MAKE FUN OF
>> WE GOT THE EGG, USHER.        >> I'M NEVER GONNA MAKE FUN OF   USHER BECAUSE HE'S PART OWNER OF
>> I'M NEVER GONNA MAKE FUN OF   USHER BECAUSE HE'S PART OWNER OF THE CLEVELAND CAVALIERS, SO I
USHER BECAUSE HE'S PART OWNER OF THE CLEVELAND CAVALIERS, SO I    GOT TO RESPECT THAT.
THE CLEVELAND CAVALIERS, SO I    GOT TO RESPECT THAT.             >> I'M NOT MAKING FUN OF USHER.
GOT TO RESPECT THAT.             >> I'M NOT MAKING FUN OF USHER.  >> KEVIN HART ALSO TENDS TO
>> I'M NOT MAKING FUN OF USHER.  >> KEVIN HART ALSO TENDS TO      GRILL TOPLESS.
>> KEVIN HART ALSO TENDS TO      GRILL TOPLESS.                   HERE'S OUR GRATUITOUS
GRILL TOPLESS.                   HERE'S OUR GRATUITOUS            KEVIN HART --
HERE'S OUR GRATUITOUS            KEVIN HART --                    >> LOOK AT KEVIN.
KEVIN HART --                    >> LOOK AT KEVIN.                >> I FIND THE GRILL MORE
>> LOOK AT KEVIN.                >> I FIND THE GRILL MORE         ACCEPTABLE THAN BEING INDOORS
>> I FIND THE GRILL MORE         ACCEPTABLE THAN BEING INDOORS    AND DOING IT.
ACCEPTABLE THAN BEING INDOORS    AND DOING IT.                    >> REALLY?
AND DOING IT.                    >> REALLY?                       I'D FEEL LIKE THERE'S A LIVE
>> REALLY?                       I'D FEEL LIKE THERE'S A LIVE     FIRE THAT COULD JUMP OUT.
I'D FEEL LIKE THERE'S A LIVE     FIRE THAT COULD JUMP OUT.        >> IT COULD OF CAME FROM THE
FIRE THAT COULD JUMP OUT.        >> IT COULD OF CAME FROM THE     POOL AND YOU'RE JUST WHIPPIN'
>> IT COULD OF CAME FROM THE     POOL AND YOU'RE JUST WHIPPIN'    SOMETHING UP ON THE GRILL.
POOL AND YOU'RE JUST WHIPPIN'    SOMETHING UP ON THE GRILL.       >> SO THAT COULD HAPPEN.
SOMETHING UP ON THE GRILL.       >> SO THAT COULD HAPPEN.         STRANGER THINGS HAVE HAPPENED.
>> SO THAT COULD HAPPEN.         STRANGER THINGS HAVE HAPPENED.   ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO YOU GUYS HAVE
STRANGER THINGS HAVE HAPPENED.   ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO YOU GUYS HAVE COMING UP IN THIS HOUR?
ALL RIGHT, WHAT DO YOU GUYS HAVE COMING UP IN THIS HOUR?          MICHAEL, WHY DON'T YOU GO FIRST.
COMING UP IN THIS HOUR?          MICHAEL, WHY DON'T YOU GO FIRST. >> WELL, I THINK I WILL,
MICHAEL, WHY DON'T YOU GO FIRST. >> WELL, I THINK I WILL,         CLINTON.
>> WELL, I THINK I WILL,         CLINTON.                         [ LAUGHTER ]
CLINTON.                         [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IT'S REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK,
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IT'S REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK,   SO I'M ANSWERING A VIEWER BY
>> IT'S REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK,   SO I'M ANSWERING A VIEWER BY     MAKING MEDITERRANEAN STUFFED
SO I'M ANSWERING A VIEWER BY     MAKING MEDITERRANEAN STUFFED     PEPPERS WITH FETA!
MAKING MEDITERRANEAN STUFFED     PEPPERS WITH FETA!               >> YUM!
PEPPERS WITH FETA!               >> YUM!                          >> AND I'M GONNA SHARE A GREAT
>> YUM!                          >> AND I'M GONNA SHARE A GREAT   MOTHER'S DAY GIFT IDEA FOR THIS
>> AND I'M GONNA SHARE A GREAT   MOTHER'S DAY GIFT IDEA FOR THIS  WEEKEND!
MOTHER'S DAY GIFT IDEA FOR THIS  WEEKEND!                         >> WELL, SHE'S FINALLY HERE.
WEEKEND!                         >> WELL, SHE'S FINALLY HERE.     FINALLY, FINALLY, FINALLY!
>> WELL, SHE'S FINALLY HERE.     FINALLY, FINALLY, FINALLY!       I'M COOKIN' WITH
FINALLY, FINALLY, FINALLY!       I'M COOKIN' WITH                 DARBY STANCHFIELD FROM
I'M COOKIN' WITH                 DARBY STANCHFIELD FROM           "SCANDAL"!
DARBY STANCHFIELD FROM           "SCANDAL"!                       I'M SO EXCITED!
"SCANDAL"!                       I'M SO EXCITED!                  >> BUT FIRST, WE'RE JOINED BY
I'M SO EXCITED!                  >> BUT FIRST, WE'RE JOINED BY    OUR GUEST WHO DEFINITELY HAS
>> BUT FIRST, WE'RE JOINED BY    OUR GUEST WHO DEFINITELY HAS     THAT "WOW" FACTOR.
OUR GUEST WHO DEFINITELY HAS     THAT "WOW" FACTOR.               HE'S A TALENTED ACTOR.
THAT "WOW" FACTOR.               HE'S A TALENTED ACTOR.           ONE OF HOLLYWOOD'S FAVORITES,
HE'S A TALENTED ACTOR.           ONE OF HOLLYWOOD'S FAVORITES,    AND NOW HE'S STARRING IN AMAZON
ONE OF HOLLYWOOD'S FAVORITES,    AND NOW HE'S STARRING IN AMAZON  PRIME'S CAPTIVATING NEW SERIES,
AND NOW HE'S STARRING IN AMAZON  PRIME'S CAPTIVATING NEW SERIES,  "I LOVE DICK."
PRIME'S CAPTIVATING NEW SERIES,  "I LOVE DICK."                   PLEASE WELCOME BACK,
"I LOVE DICK."                   PLEASE WELCOME BACK,             KEVIN BACON!
PLEASE WELCOME BACK,             KEVIN BACON!                     [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
KEVIN BACON!                     [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪                                >> WHOO!
♪                                >> WHOO!                         >> HAPPY TO HAVE YOU HERE!
>> WHOO!                         >> HAPPY TO HAVE YOU HERE!       >> HI!
>> HAPPY TO HAVE YOU HERE!       >> HI!                           >> HOW ARE YOU, KEVIN?
>> HI!                           >> HOW ARE YOU, KEVIN?           GOOD TO SEE YOU!
>> HOW ARE YOU, KEVIN?           GOOD TO SEE YOU!                 >> KEVIN AND I ARE IN THE
GOOD TO SEE YOU!                 >> KEVIN AND I ARE IN THE        KITCHEN TOGETHER WHEN WE COME
>> KEVIN AND I ARE IN THE        KITCHEN TOGETHER WHEN WE COME    BACK!
KITCHEN TOGETHER WHEN WE COME    BACK!                            DON'T GO AWAY!
BACK!                            DON'T GO AWAY!                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DON'T GO AWAY!                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
Allergy symptoms                 distracting you?
Doctors recommend            taking Claritin every day
of your allergy season           for continuous relief.
Claritin provides powerful,
non-drowsy, 24-hour relief.
For fewer interruptions from
the amazing things               you do every day.
Live Claritin Clear.
Every day.
When you have allergies,
it can seem like triggers            pop up everywhere.
Luckily there's Powerful,                24-hour,
non-drowsy Claritin.
It provides relief                of symptoms that
can be triggered by over         200 different allergens.
Live Claritin Clear.
At KFC, we choose to make...
spicy, crispy                 chicken sandwiches.
Not because it is easy...
but because it is hard.
We choose not only to launch
KFC's new Zinger sandwich
and a $5 dollar fill up...
but to take it to space.              Will it be easy?
No.
Will it be hard? Yes.
We've already covered that.
But when we succeed...
we will lick our fingers good!
Space sandwich! Yeah!
Try the Zinger sandwich          before it goes to space.
All eyes are on Olay Ultimate              Eye Cream.
Allure Best of Beauty and Marie       Claire's Most Wanted.
Eyes show emotion, not your age.
Olay Eyes. Ageless.
Shake up your routine with a     completely new way to clean.
New Colgate Total Advanced       Health Mouthwash.
Shake to activate a powerf       cleaning action
that removes twenty four times   more bacteria.
Improve the health of your mouth
with new Colgate Total Advanced  Health Mouthwash.
Shake to clean.
Tonight, they've got                a full house.
So this quick ranch pasta
primavera is the perfect dish.
Sprinkle in a packet of
Hidden Valley Ranch,
add some veggies, and you've got
a meal that's sure to please.
It's time to Ranch Out
with the original,
Hidden Valley Ranch.
>>> Announcer: IT'S AN HOUR OF   "WEEKNIGHT WOWS" TODAY, ON "THE  CHEW!"
"WEEKNIGHT WOWS" TODAY, ON "THE  CHEW!"                           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
CHEW!"                           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪                                >> WELCOME BACK, TO "THE CHEW!"
♪                                >> WELCOME BACK, TO "THE CHEW!"  WE'RE JOINED BY OUR FANTASTIC
>> WELCOME BACK, TO "THE CHEW!"  WE'RE JOINED BY OUR FANTASTIC    GUEST, THE STAR OF MANY
WE'RE JOINED BY OUR FANTASTIC    GUEST, THE STAR OF MANY          MEMORABLE MOVIES AND A NEW HIT
GUEST, THE STAR OF MANY          MEMORABLE MOVIES AND A NEW HIT   SERIES --
MEMORABLE MOVIES AND A NEW HIT   SERIES --                        KEVIN BACON!
SERIES --                        KEVIN BACON!                     [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
KEVIN BACON!                     [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          SO, WHAT'S A TYPICAL WEEKNIGHT
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          SO, WHAT'S A TYPICAL WEEKNIGHT   AROUND YOUR GUYS' HOUSE?
SO, WHAT'S A TYPICAL WEEKNIGHT   AROUND YOUR GUYS' HOUSE?         ARE YOU A COOKER?
AROUND YOUR GUYS' HOUSE?         ARE YOU A COOKER?                >> YEAH, WE ARE COOKERS.
ARE YOU A COOKER?                >> YEAH, WE ARE COOKERS.         YEAH, WE'RE BOTH COOKERS.
>> YEAH, WE ARE COOKERS.         YEAH, WE'RE BOTH COOKERS.        THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN US IS
YEAH, WE'RE BOTH COOKERS.        THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN US IS     SHE'S A RECIPE FOLLOWER, AND I'M
THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN US IS     SHE'S A RECIPE FOLLOWER, AND I'M A RECIPE IGNORER.
SHE'S A RECIPE FOLLOWER, AND I'M A RECIPE IGNORER.                [ LAUGHTER ]
A RECIPE IGNORER.                [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> AH!
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> AH!                           >> I MEAN, I GET --
>> AH!                           >> I MEAN, I GET --              >> THERE'S THE BEAUTIFUL COUPLE.
>> I MEAN, I GET --              >> THERE'S THE BEAUTIFUL COUPLE. I THINK, EVERYONE IN AMERICA CAN
>> THERE'S THE BEAUTIFUL COUPLE. I THINK, EVERYONE IN AMERICA CAN SEE.
I THINK, EVERYONE IN AMERICA CAN SEE.                             >> YES.
SEE.                             >> YES.                          >> MAYBE THAT'S WHY WE GET
>> YES.                          >> MAYBE THAT'S WHY WE GET       ALONG.
>> MAYBE THAT'S WHY WE GET       ALONG.                           >> RIGHT.
ALONG.                           >> RIGHT.                        >> BUT, YEAH WE COOK.
>> RIGHT.                        >> BUT, YEAH WE COOK.            WE HAVE A TRADITION, CERTAINLY
>> BUT, YEAH WE COOK.            WE HAVE A TRADITION, CERTAINLY   AROUND DINNER IN OUR HOUSE, WITH
WE HAVE A TRADITION, CERTAINLY   AROUND DINNER IN OUR HOUSE, WITH SITTING DOWN WITH THE KIDS
AROUND DINNER IN OUR HOUSE, WITH SITTING DOWN WITH THE KIDS       OFTEN, WITH CANDLELIGHT, AND
SITTING DOWN WITH THE KIDS       OFTEN, WITH CANDLELIGHT, AND     ACTUALLY MAKING DINNER TOGETHER
OFTEN, WITH CANDLELIGHT, AND     ACTUALLY MAKING DINNER TOGETHER  AND --
ACTUALLY MAKING DINNER TOGETHER  AND --                           THEY'RE OUT OF THE HOUSE NOW,
AND --                           THEY'RE OUT OF THE HOUSE NOW,    BUT THAT'S IMPORTANT TO US.
THEY'RE OUT OF THE HOUSE NOW,    BUT THAT'S IMPORTANT TO US.      SO, WE LOVE TO --
BUT THAT'S IMPORTANT TO US.      SO, WE LOVE TO --                [ APPLAUSE ]
SO, WE LOVE TO --                [ APPLAUSE ]                     WE LOVE TO EAT, BE TOGETHER,
[ APPLAUSE ]                     WE LOVE TO EAT, BE TOGETHER,     TALK, HANG OUT WHILE WE'RE
WE LOVE TO EAT, BE TOGETHER,     TALK, HANG OUT WHILE WE'RE       COOKING AS WELL.
TALK, HANG OUT WHILE WE'RE       COOKING AS WELL.                 >> SO, WELL IT'S EASY TO GET
COOKING AS WELL.                 >> SO, WELL IT'S EASY TO GET     CARRIED AWAY, AND EVERYBODY'S
>> SO, WELL IT'S EASY TO GET     CARRIED AWAY, AND EVERYBODY'S    ALWAYS MAKING SURE THEY'RE
CARRIED AWAY, AND EVERYBODY'S    ALWAYS MAKING SURE THEY'RE       STAYING UP TO DATE ON THEIR
ALWAYS MAKING SURE THEY'RE       STAYING UP TO DATE ON THEIR      INSTAGRAM, OR MAKING SURE YOU
STAYING UP TO DATE ON THEIR      INSTAGRAM, OR MAKING SURE YOU    TAKE THE CALL --
INSTAGRAM, OR MAKING SURE YOU    TAKE THE CALL --                 WHETHER IT'S YOUR AGENT, YOUR
TAKE THE CALL --                 WHETHER IT'S YOUR AGENT, YOUR    NEXT DOOR NEIGHBOR, OR SOMEBODY
WHETHER IT'S YOUR AGENT, YOUR    NEXT DOOR NEIGHBOR, OR SOMEBODY  ELSE.
NEXT DOOR NEIGHBOR, OR SOMEBODY  ELSE.                            IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT FOR ME
ELSE.                            IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT FOR ME     THAT WE TURN ALL THE PHONES OFF
IT'S REALLY IMPORTANT FOR ME     THAT WE TURN ALL THE PHONES OFF  AND PUT THEM ALL AWAY WHEN YOU
THAT WE TURN ALL THE PHONES OFF  AND PUT THEM ALL AWAY WHEN YOU   SIT DOWN FOR DINNER.
AND PUT THEM ALL AWAY WHEN YOU   SIT DOWN FOR DINNER.             [ APPLAUSE ]
SIT DOWN FOR DINNER.             [ APPLAUSE ]                     BECAUSE YOU CAN REALLY TAKE A
[ APPLAUSE ]                     BECAUSE YOU CAN REALLY TAKE A    FULL HOUR.
BECAUSE YOU CAN REALLY TAKE A    FULL HOUR.                       >> AND I THINK, OUR HOUSE, WHAT
FULL HOUR.                       >> AND I THINK, OUR HOUSE, WHAT  WE LOVE TO DO IS MAKE SURE WE
>> AND I THINK, OUR HOUSE, WHAT  WE LOVE TO DO IS MAKE SURE WE    DON'T DO THE DISHES THE MOMENT
WE LOVE TO DO IS MAKE SURE WE    DON'T DO THE DISHES THE MOMENT   WE'RE DONE EATING.
DON'T DO THE DISHES THE MOMENT   WE'RE DONE EATING.               >> THAT'S A REALLY GOOD IDEA.
WE'RE DONE EATING.               >> THAT'S A REALLY GOOD IDEA.    >> LET THEM SIT THERE FOR A
>> THAT'S A REALLY GOOD IDEA.    >> LET THEM SIT THERE FOR A      LITTLE WHILE.
>> LET THEM SIT THERE FOR A      LITTLE WHILE.                    >> LET THEM SIT THERE.
LITTLE WHILE.                    >> LET THEM SIT THERE.           I KNOW.
>> LET THEM SIT THERE.           I KNOW.                          [ APPLAUSE ]
I KNOW.                          [ APPLAUSE ]                     I JUST KIND OF CAME TO THAT
[ APPLAUSE ]                     I JUST KIND OF CAME TO THAT      RECENTLY, THAT IT'S OKAY TO JUST
I JUST KIND OF CAME TO THAT      RECENTLY, THAT IT'S OKAY TO JUST LOOK AT THAT TABLE WITH
RECENTLY, THAT IT'S OKAY TO JUST LOOK AT THAT TABLE WITH          EVERYTHING THERE.
LOOK AT THAT TABLE WITH          EVERYTHING THERE.                AND YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENS
EVERYTHING THERE.                AND YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENS       SOMETIMES --
AND YOU KNOW, WHAT HAPPENS       SOMETIMES --                     SOMETIMES YOU GO, "YOU KNOW, I
SOMETIMES --                     SOMETIMES YOU GO, "YOU KNOW, I   THINK I'M GOING TO HAVE ANOTHER
SOMETIMES YOU GO, "YOU KNOW, I   THINK I'M GOING TO HAVE ANOTHER  BITE."
THINK I'M GOING TO HAVE ANOTHER  BITE."                           [ LAUGHTER ]
BITE."                           [ LAUGHTER ]                     I DO THIS WEIRD THING, I DON'T
[ LAUGHTER ]                     I DO THIS WEIRD THING, I DON'T   KNOW IF ANYBODY ELSE DOES IT,
I DO THIS WEIRD THING, I DON'T   KNOW IF ANYBODY ELSE DOES IT,    BUT MY KIDS ALWAYS MAKE FUN OF
KNOW IF ANYBODY ELSE DOES IT,    BUT MY KIDS ALWAYS MAKE FUN OF   IT.
BUT MY KIDS ALWAYS MAKE FUN OF   IT.                              AND, I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE IT
IT.                              AND, I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE IT    WAS A THING, BUT "THERE GOES DAD
AND, I DIDN'T EVEN REALIZE IT    WAS A THING, BUT "THERE GOES DAD WITH THE FINAL BITE."
WAS A THING, BUT "THERE GOES DAD WITH THE FINAL BITE."            WHICH IS, AFTER WE'VE CLEARED.
WITH THE FINAL BITE."            WHICH IS, AFTER WE'VE CLEARED.   >> RIGHT.
WHICH IS, AFTER WE'VE CLEARED.   >> RIGHT.                        >> EVERYTHING IS BACK IN THE
>> RIGHT.                        >> EVERYTHING IS BACK IN THE     KITCHEN.
>> EVERYTHING IS BACK IN THE     KITCHEN.                         THAT'S WHEN I HAVE TO HAVE ONE
KITCHEN.                         THAT'S WHEN I HAVE TO HAVE ONE   MORE BITE.
THAT'S WHEN I HAVE TO HAVE ONE   MORE BITE.                       >> WELL, YEAH.
MORE BITE.                       >> WELL, YEAH.                   >> YEAH, YEAH.
>> WELL, YEAH.                   >> YEAH, YEAH.                   >> ONE MORE RAVIOLI OFF THE
>> YEAH, YEAH.                   >> ONE MORE RAVIOLI OFF THE      PLATE BEFORE WE GO TO THE
>> ONE MORE RAVIOLI OFF THE      PLATE BEFORE WE GO TO THE        CLEANING FACTOR.
PLATE BEFORE WE GO TO THE        CLEANING FACTOR.                 >> DOES ANYBODY ELSE DO THAT?
CLEANING FACTOR.                 >> DOES ANYBODY ELSE DO THAT?    >> YES.
>> DOES ANYBODY ELSE DO THAT?    >> YES.                          [ APPLAUSE ]
>> YES.                          [ APPLAUSE ]                     >> OKAY, SO I'M NOT SPECIAL.
[ APPLAUSE ]                     >> OKAY, SO I'M NOT SPECIAL.     >> NO, YOU'RE SPECIAL!
>> OKAY, SO I'M NOT SPECIAL.     >> NO, YOU'RE SPECIAL!           YOU'RE SPECIAL, YOU'RE SPECIAL,
>> NO, YOU'RE SPECIAL!           YOU'RE SPECIAL, YOU'RE SPECIAL,  YOU'RE SPECIAL.
YOU'RE SPECIAL, YOU'RE SPECIAL,  YOU'RE SPECIAL.                  SO, TELL US ABOUT THIS NEW SHOW.
YOU'RE SPECIAL.                  SO, TELL US ABOUT THIS NEW SHOW. I WATCHED IT, AND I'VE GOT TO
SO, TELL US ABOUT THIS NEW SHOW. I WATCHED IT, AND I'VE GOT TO    SAY I THINK IT'S GOING TO CHANGE
I WATCHED IT, AND I'VE GOT TO    SAY I THINK IT'S GOING TO CHANGE TV.
SAY I THINK IT'S GOING TO CHANGE TV.                              >> YOU'RE SO SWEET TO SAY THAT.
TV.                              >> YOU'RE SO SWEET TO SAY THAT.  >> THIS IS SOMETHING SO AMAZING.
>> YOU'RE SO SWEET TO SAY THAT.  >> THIS IS SOMETHING SO AMAZING. [ APPLAUSE ]
>> THIS IS SOMETHING SO AMAZING. [ APPLAUSE ]                     IT'S ON AMAZON PRIME.
[ APPLAUSE ]                     IT'S ON AMAZON PRIME.            IT STARTS THIS FRIDAY.
IT'S ON AMAZON PRIME.            IT STARTS THIS FRIDAY.           AND, IT IS A CRAZY STORY.
IT STARTS THIS FRIDAY.           AND, IT IS A CRAZY STORY.        TELL US ABOUT YOUR CHARACTER.
AND, IT IS A CRAZY STORY.        TELL US ABOUT YOUR CHARACTER.    YOU'RE KIND OF LIKE THE MOGUL
TELL US ABOUT YOUR CHARACTER.    YOU'RE KIND OF LIKE THE MOGUL    MAN.
YOU'RE KIND OF LIKE THE MOGUL    MAN.                             WELL, THERE'S A PICTURE OF YOU
MAN.                             WELL, THERE'S A PICTURE OF YOU   RIGHT THERE.
WELL, THERE'S A PICTURE OF YOU   RIGHT THERE.                     >> YEAH.
RIGHT THERE.                     >> YEAH.                         >> SO YOU'RE, LIKE, A PROFESSOR
>> YEAH.                         >> SO YOU'RE, LIKE, A PROFESSOR  AT THIS CRAZY INSTITUTE IN
>> SO YOU'RE, LIKE, A PROFESSOR  AT THIS CRAZY INSTITUTE IN       MARFA, TEXAS, RIGHT?
AT THIS CRAZY INSTITUTE IN       MARFA, TEXAS, RIGHT?             >> YEAH.
MARFA, TEXAS, RIGHT?             >> YEAH.                         MARFA, TEXAS, IT'S A SMALL TOWN
>> YEAH.                         MARFA, TEXAS, IT'S A SMALL TOWN  IN WEST TEXAS JUST THAT,
MARFA, TEXAS, IT'S A SMALL TOWN  IN WEST TEXAS JUST THAT,         ACTUALLY, IS A REAL PLACE AND
IN WEST TEXAS JUST THAT,         ACTUALLY, IS A REAL PLACE AND    HAS --
ACTUALLY, IS A REAL PLACE AND    HAS --                           YOU KNOW IS A REAL, CLASSIC
HAS --                           YOU KNOW IS A REAL, CLASSIC      TRADITIONAL TEXAS TOWN, BUT ALSO
YOU KNOW IS A REAL, CLASSIC      TRADITIONAL TEXAS TOWN, BUT ALSO HAS A VERY BIG ARTS PROGRAM.
TRADITIONAL TEXAS TOWN, BUT ALSO HAS A VERY BIG ARTS PROGRAM.     AND, A LOT OF REALLY COOL FOOD
HAS A VERY BIG ARTS PROGRAM.     AND, A LOT OF REALLY COOL FOOD   TRUCKS, BY THE WAY.
AND, A LOT OF REALLY COOL FOOD   TRUCKS, BY THE WAY.              AND, A LOT OF VERY, VERY HIP
TRUCKS, BY THE WAY.              AND, A LOT OF VERY, VERY HIP     SORT OF PEOPLE LIVING THERE A
AND, A LOT OF VERY, VERY HIP     SORT OF PEOPLE LIVING THERE A    LOT OF THE TIME.
SORT OF PEOPLE LIVING THERE A    LOT OF THE TIME.                 >> IT'S SUPER COOL!
LOT OF THE TIME.                 >> IT'S SUPER COOL!              >> YEAH, IT'S A COOL --
>> IT'S SUPER COOL!              >> YEAH, IT'S A COOL --          >> HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?
>> YEAH, IT'S A COOL --          >> HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?          >> I HAVE, YEAH.
>> HAVE YOU BEEN THERE?          >> I HAVE, YEAH.                 IT'S A VERY COOL PLACE.
>> I HAVE, YEAH.                 IT'S A VERY COOL PLACE.          >> YEAH, RIGHT ALONGSIDE YOU
IT'S A VERY COOL PLACE.          >> YEAH, RIGHT ALONGSIDE YOU     KNOW, LIKE, COWBOYS AND BORDER
>> YEAH, RIGHT ALONGSIDE YOU     KNOW, LIKE, COWBOYS AND BORDER   PATROL, AND STUFF.
KNOW, LIKE, COWBOYS AND BORDER   PATROL, AND STUFF.               >> RIGHT.
PATROL, AND STUFF.               >> RIGHT.                        [ LAUGHTER ]
>> RIGHT.                        [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> AND, THIS GUY IS, YOU KNOW,
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> AND, THIS GUY IS, YOU KNOW,   RUNNING THIS ARTS INSTITUTE DOWN
>> AND, THIS GUY IS, YOU KNOW,   RUNNING THIS ARTS INSTITUTE DOWN THERE.
RUNNING THIS ARTS INSTITUTE DOWN THERE.                           HE'S A SCULPTOR.
THERE.                           HE'S A SCULPTOR.                 AND THIS COUPLE, KATHRYN HAHN
HE'S A SCULPTOR.                 AND THIS COUPLE, KATHRYN HAHN    AND GRIFFIN DUNNE, COME TO TOWN
AND THIS COUPLE, KATHRYN HAHN    AND GRIFFIN DUNNE, COME TO TOWN  AND THEY ARE KIND OF, LOST A
AND GRIFFIN DUNNE, COME TO TOWN  AND THEY ARE KIND OF, LOST A     LITTLE BIT OF THE FLAME IN THEIR
AND THEY ARE KIND OF, LOST A     LITTLE BIT OF THE FLAME IN THEIR RELATIONSHIP.
LITTLE BIT OF THE FLAME IN THEIR RELATIONSHIP.                    >> RIGHT.
RELATIONSHIP.                    >> RIGHT.                        >> AND, THEIR OBSESSION,
>> RIGHT.                        >> AND, THEIR OBSESSION,         STARTING WITH HER OBSESSION FOR
>> AND, THEIR OBSESSION,         STARTING WITH HER OBSESSION FOR  THIS MAN, DICK, WHICH I PLAY,
STARTING WITH HER OBSESSION FOR  THIS MAN, DICK, WHICH I PLAY,    REIGNITES THE PASSION IN THEIR
THIS MAN, DICK, WHICH I PLAY,    REIGNITES THE PASSION IN THEIR   LOVE LIFE.
REIGNITES THE PASSION IN THEIR   LOVE LIFE.                       SO, THE SHOW IS VERY --
LOVE LIFE.                       SO, THE SHOW IS VERY --          >> IN AN ELECTRIC WAY!
SO, THE SHOW IS VERY --          >> IN AN ELECTRIC WAY!           I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, IT IS SO
>> IN AN ELECTRIC WAY!           I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, IT IS SO   SEXY.
I'VE GOT TO TELL YOU, IT IS SO   SEXY.                            >> IT'S A SEXY SHOW.
SEXY.                            >> IT'S A SEXY SHOW.             >> AND, SO BEAUTIFUL.
>> IT'S A SEXY SHOW.             >> AND, SO BEAUTIFUL.            IT IS SO AMAZING.
>> AND, SO BEAUTIFUL.            IT IS SO AMAZING.                AND THE ACTING IS SO FANTASTIC.
IT IS SO AMAZING.                AND THE ACTING IS SO FANTASTIC.  >> THANK YOU.
AND THE ACTING IS SO FANTASTIC.  >> THANK YOU.                    >> I MEAN, YOU SHOULD BE REALLY
>> THANK YOU.                    >> I MEAN, YOU SHOULD BE REALLY  PROUD.
>> I MEAN, YOU SHOULD BE REALLY  PROUD.                           [ APPLAUSE ]
PROUD.                           [ APPLAUSE ]                     I FEEL VERY STRONGLY THAT IT'S
[ APPLAUSE ]                     I FEEL VERY STRONGLY THAT IT'S   GOING TO CHANGE TV.
I FEEL VERY STRONGLY THAT IT'S   GOING TO CHANGE TV.              AND, I'VE GOT TO SAY, THAT THE
GOING TO CHANGE TV.              AND, I'VE GOT TO SAY, THAT THE   MUSIC, AND THE BACKGROUND, AND
AND, I'VE GOT TO SAY, THAT THE   MUSIC, AND THE BACKGROUND, AND   THE DIRECTION AND THE WHOLE
MUSIC, AND THE BACKGROUND, AND   THE DIRECTION AND THE WHOLE      THING IS JUST, SOMETHING CRAZY.
THE DIRECTION AND THE WHOLE      THING IS JUST, SOMETHING CRAZY.  GUYS, YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THIS
THING IS JUST, SOMETHING CRAZY.  GUYS, YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THIS     SHOW.
GUYS, YOU'VE GOT TO SEE THIS     SHOW.                            [ APPLAUSE ]
SHOW.                            [ APPLAUSE ]                     IN ANY CASE, WHY DON'T WE START
[ APPLAUSE ]                     IN ANY CASE, WHY DON'T WE START  COOKING?
IN ANY CASE, WHY DON'T WE START  COOKING?                         >> ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.
COOKING?                         >> ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.       >> ALL RIGHT, SO, WE'RE GOING TO
>> ALL RIGHT, LET'S DO IT.       >> ALL RIGHT, SO, WE'RE GOING TO MAKE AN ORECCHIETTE DISH, WHICH
>> ALL RIGHT, SO, WE'RE GOING TO MAKE AN ORECCHIETTE DISH, WHICH  IS THE PASTA TRADITIONAL TO
MAKE AN ORECCHIETTE DISH, WHICH  IS THE PASTA TRADITIONAL TO      APULIA.
IS THE PASTA TRADITIONAL TO      APULIA.                          WE'VE ALREADY MADE THE NOODLES,
APULIA.                          WE'VE ALREADY MADE THE NOODLES,  AND WE'VE SET THEM ASIDE.
WE'VE ALREADY MADE THE NOODLES,  AND WE'VE SET THEM ASIDE.        WE'RE GOING TO TAKE RAPINI,
AND WE'VE SET THEM ASIDE.        WE'RE GOING TO TAKE RAPINI,      WHICH IS BROCCOLI RABE AND
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE RAPINI,      WHICH IS BROCCOLI RABE AND       SAUSAGE.
WHICH IS BROCCOLI RABE AND       SAUSAGE.                         AND, TRADITIONALLY YOU JUST,
SAUSAGE.                         AND, TRADITIONALLY YOU JUST,     KIND OF, CHOP THEM UP.
AND, TRADITIONALLY YOU JUST,     KIND OF, CHOP THEM UP.           WE'RE GOING TO MAKE IT INTO A
KIND OF, CHOP THEM UP.           WE'RE GOING TO MAKE IT INTO A    PESTO.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE IT INTO A    PESTO.                           SO, WOULD YOU LIKE TO HELP?
PESTO.                           SO, WOULD YOU LIKE TO HELP?      >> I WOULD!
SO, WOULD YOU LIKE TO HELP?      >> I WOULD!                      >> SO, WE BLANCH THEM UP, AND
>> I WOULD!                      >> SO, WE BLANCH THEM UP, AND    YOU THROW IT ALL IN.
>> SO, WE BLANCH THEM UP, AND    YOU THROW IT ALL IN.             AND THEN, WHAT WE DID WAS, WE
YOU THROW IT ALL IN.             AND THEN, WHAT WE DID WAS, WE    ROASTED A HEAD OF GARLIC.
AND THEN, WHAT WE DID WAS, WE    ROASTED A HEAD OF GARLIC.        WE WERE DISCUSSING GARLIC
ROASTED A HEAD OF GARLIC.        WE WERE DISCUSSING GARLIC        EARLIER.
WE WERE DISCUSSING GARLIC        EARLIER.                         >> YEAH.
EARLIER.                         >> YEAH.                         >> WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS ABOUT
>> YEAH.                         >> WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS ABOUT  ROASTED, VERSUS NON ROASTED?
>> WHAT ARE YOUR FEELINGS ABOUT  ROASTED, VERSUS NON ROASTED?     >> YEAH, SO, I LOVE GARLIC.
ROASTED, VERSUS NON ROASTED?     >> YEAH, SO, I LOVE GARLIC.      BUT I FIND, LIKE, IF IT'S IN
>> YEAH, SO, I LOVE GARLIC.      BUT I FIND, LIKE, IF IT'S IN     LIKE THIS KIND OF SAUCE, OR A
BUT I FIND, LIKE, IF IT'S IN     LIKE THIS KIND OF SAUCE, OR A    PESTO SAUCE, IT'S A LITTLE BIT
LIKE THIS KIND OF SAUCE, OR A    PESTO SAUCE, IT'S A LITTLE BIT   MUCH.
PESTO SAUCE, IT'S A LITTLE BIT   MUCH.                            ESPECIALLY IN THE MIDDLE OF THE
MUCH.                            ESPECIALLY IN THE MIDDLE OF THE  DAY.
ESPECIALLY IN THE MIDDLE OF THE  DAY.                             BUT IF YOU ROAST IT FIRST, IT
DAY.                             BUT IF YOU ROAST IT FIRST, IT    JUST TAKES A LITTLE BIT OF THE
BUT IF YOU ROAST IT FIRST, IT    JUST TAKES A LITTLE BIT OF THE   BITE OUT OF IT.
JUST TAKES A LITTLE BIT OF THE   BITE OUT OF IT.                  IT MAKES IT SWEETER.
BITE OUT OF IT.                  IT MAKES IT SWEETER.             [ APPLAUSE ]
IT MAKES IT SWEETER.             [ APPLAUSE ]                     >> THAT'S WHAT WE WERE HOPING.
[ APPLAUSE ]                     >> THAT'S WHAT WE WERE HOPING.   >> LITERALLY, WHEN THIS, I WAS
>> THAT'S WHAT WE WERE HOPING.   >> LITERALLY, WHEN THIS, I WAS   LITERALLY JUST TALKING ABOUT
>> LITERALLY, WHEN THIS, I WAS   LITERALLY JUST TALKING ABOUT     THIS IN THE DRESSING ROOM.
LITERALLY JUST TALKING ABOUT     THIS IN THE DRESSING ROOM.       AND, THEN SOMEONE WHO WAS WITH
THIS IN THE DRESSING ROOM.       AND, THEN SOMEONE WHO WAS WITH   ME SAITHEY SOMETIMES DO IT
AND, THEN SOMEONE WHO WAS WITH   ME SAITHEY SOMETIMES DO IT       WITH BLACK GARLIC.
ME SAITHEY SOMETIMES DO IT       WITH BLACK GARLIC.               I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WHAT BLACK
WITH BLACK GARLIC.               I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WHAT BLACK    GARLIC WAS.
I DIDN'T EVEN KNOW WHAT BLACK    GARLIC WAS.                      >> YEAH, IT'S A FERMENTED
GARLIC WAS.                      >> YEAH, IT'S A FERMENTED        GARLIC!
>> YEAH, IT'S A FERMENTED        GARLIC!                          >> OH.
GARLIC!                          >> OH.                           >> IT STARTED IN KOREA!
>> OH.                           >> IT STARTED IN KOREA!          AND NOW YOU CAN BUY IT IN
>> IT STARTED IN KOREA!          AND NOW YOU CAN BUY IT IN        GROCERY STORES AND IT'S ALREADY
AND NOW YOU CAN BUY IT IN        GROCERY STORES AND IT'S ALREADY  READY.
GROCERY STORES AND IT'S ALREADY  READY.                           IT'S DELICIOUS, IT'S SWEET, A
READY.                           IT'S DELICIOUS, IT'S SWEET, A    LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED.
IT'S DELICIOUS, IT'S SWEET, A    LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED.         >> I LOVE THAT THERE'S ALMONDS
LITTLE MORE COMPLICATED.         >> I LOVE THAT THERE'S ALMONDS   IN THERE.
>> I LOVE THAT THERE'S ALMONDS   IN THERE.                        >> YEAH, SO WE HAVE SOME
IN THERE.                        >> YEAH, SO WE HAVE SOME         ALMONDS.
>> YEAH, SO WE HAVE SOME         ALMONDS.                         WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A PINCH OF
ALMONDS.                         WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A PINCH OF   CHILI.
WE'RE GOING TO TAKE A PINCH OF   CHILI.                           YOU WANT TO GRATE A LITTLE
CHILI.                           YOU WANT TO GRATE A LITTLE       PARMESAN INTO THERE?
YOU WANT TO GRATE A LITTLE       PARMESAN INTO THERE?             >> YEAH.
PARMESAN INTO THERE?             >> YEAH.                         >> AND, I'M GOING TO SLOW ABOUT
>> YEAH.                         >> AND, I'M GOING TO SLOW ABOUT  A QUARTER TO A HALF CUP OF EXTRA
>> AND, I'M GOING TO SLOW ABOUT  A QUARTER TO A HALF CUP OF EXTRA VIRGIN OLIVE OIL.
A QUARTER TO A HALF CUP OF EXTRA VIRGIN OLIVE OIL.                OVER HERE, I TOOK SOME REALLY
VIRGIN OLIVE OIL.                OVER HERE, I TOOK SOME REALLY    NICE, OUT OF CASING, SAUSAGE.
OVER HERE, I TOOK SOME REALLY    NICE, OUT OF CASING, SAUSAGE.    YOU CAN JUST TAKE YOUR OWN
NICE, OUT OF CASING, SAUSAGE.    YOU CAN JUST TAKE YOUR OWN       GROUND TURKEY OR GROUND PORK OR
YOU CAN JUST TAKE YOUR OWN       GROUND TURKEY OR GROUND PORK OR  GROUND BEEF.
GROUND TURKEY OR GROUND PORK OR  GROUND BEEF.                     AND SEASON IT LIKE SAUSAGE.
GROUND BEEF.                     AND SEASON IT LIKE SAUSAGE.      >> TELL ME WHEN IT'S DONE.
AND SEASON IT LIKE SAUSAGE.      >> TELL ME WHEN IT'S DONE.       >> THAT'S THE RIGHT AMOUNT.
>> TELL ME WHEN IT'S DONE.       >> THAT'S THE RIGHT AMOUNT.      PERFECT.
>> THAT'S THE RIGHT AMOUNT.      PERFECT.                         AND THEN, WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO
PERFECT.                         AND THEN, WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS, I ALREADY PINCHED SOME SALT
AND THEN, WHAT WE'RE GOING TO DO IS, I ALREADY PINCHED SOME SALT  IN IT.
IS, I ALREADY PINCHED SOME SALT  IN IT.                           GO AHEAD AND PULSE IT UNTIL IT
IN IT.                           GO AHEAD AND PULSE IT UNTIL IT   BECOMES NICE AND SMOOTH.
GO AHEAD AND PULSE IT UNTIL IT   BECOMES NICE AND SMOOTH.         I'M GOING TO ADD JUST A LITTLE
BECOMES NICE AND SMOOTH.         I'M GOING TO ADD JUST A LITTLE   MORE OIL IN THERE.
I'M GOING TO ADD JUST A LITTLE   MORE OIL IN THERE.               AND THERE YOU HAVE IT!
MORE OIL IN THERE.               AND THERE YOU HAVE IT!           NOW, THAT COULD BE A DIP, THAT
AND THERE YOU HAVE IT!           NOW, THAT COULD BE A DIP, THAT   COULD BE A PASTA SAUCE.
NOW, THAT COULD BE A DIP, THAT   COULD BE A PASTA SAUCE.          [ APPLAUSE ]
COULD BE A PASTA SAUCE.          [ APPLAUSE ]                     >> WOW, BRAVO.
[ APPLAUSE ]                     >> WOW, BRAVO.                   >> YOU JUST ADD SOME CHILI AND
>> WOW, BRAVO.                   >> YOU JUST ADD SOME CHILI AND   TOASTED ALMONDS, BECAUSE I LIKE
>> YOU JUST ADD SOME CHILI AND   TOASTED ALMONDS, BECAUSE I LIKE  THE TEXTURE THAT'S GOING TO GIVE
TOASTED ALMONDS, BECAUSE I LIKE  THE TEXTURE THAT'S GOING TO GIVE IT.
THE TEXTURE THAT'S GOING TO GIVE IT.                              >> MHMM.
IT.                              >> MHMM.                         >> WE'RE GOING TO DROP OUR
>> MHMM.                         >> WE'RE GOING TO DROP OUR       NOODLES INTO THE PASTA WATER.
>> WE'RE GOING TO DROP OUR       NOODLES INTO THE PASTA WATER.    WE'RE GOING TO SEASON IT TO THE
NOODLES INTO THE PASTA WATER.    WE'RE GOING TO SEASON IT TO THE  TASTE OF --
WE'RE GOING TO SEASON IT TO THE  TASTE OF --                      >> THE SEA!
TASTE OF --                      >> THE SEA!                      >> AH!
>> THE SEA!                      >> AH!                           >> MY FANS ARE PAYING ATTENTION!
>> AH!                           >> MY FANS ARE PAYING ATTENTION! [ LAUGHTER ]
>> MY FANS ARE PAYING ATTENTION! [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IS THAT WHAT IT IS?
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IS THAT WHAT IT IS?           >> YEAH, SO WE DROP THE
>> IS THAT WHAT IT IS?           >> YEAH, SO WE DROP THE          ORECCHIETTE AND THAT'LL TAKE
>> YEAH, SO WE DROP THE          ORECCHIETTE AND THAT'LL TAKE     ABOUT FOUR TO FIVE MINUTES TO
ORECCHIETTE AND THAT'LL TAKE     ABOUT FOUR TO FIVE MINUTES TO    COOK.
ABOUT FOUR TO FIVE MINUTES TO    COOK.                            WE ALWAYS COOK IT ONE MINUTE
COOK.                            WE ALWAYS COOK IT ONE MINUTE     LESS THAN THE PACKAGE SAYS.
WE ALWAYS COOK IT ONE MINUTE     LESS THAN THE PACKAGE SAYS.      WE'LL TAKE IT OUT, WE'LL DRAIN
LESS THAN THE PACKAGE SAYS.      WE'LL TAKE IT OUT, WE'LL DRAIN   IT, WE'LL TOSS IT IN HERE.
WE'LL TAKE IT OUT, WE'LL DRAIN   IT, WE'LL TOSS IT IN HERE.       WE'LL ADD ALL THAT.
IT, WE'LL TOSS IT IN HERE.       WE'LL ADD ALL THAT.              MORE WITH KEVIN BACON WHEN WE
WE'LL ADD ALL THAT.              MORE WITH KEVIN BACON WHEN WE    COME BACK.
MORE WITH KEVIN BACON WHEN WE    COME BACK.                       [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
COME BACK.                       [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
♪
Ouch!
SKIN-FLEX™, Anna!
Sit!
New BAND-AID® Brand SKIN-FLEX™              Bandages.
Our best bandage yet!
It moves like a second skin.
♪
Dries almost instantly.
Better?
Yeah.
Go!
Good thing because stopping       never crosses your mind.
BAND-AID® Brand.
Stick With It™
♪
So soft, thin,            and two times more absorbent
you hardly know it's there.
Carefree®.
Free to be You™.
No matter who was in             there last. Protection.
New Lysol Power & Fresh 6 goes   to work flush after flush
for a just-cleaned feeling that  lasts up to 4 weeks.
LYSOL. What it takes to protect.
(JOHNNY VO) Xanthan is...
a small alien.
He lives on Xanthan.
He loves to conquer planets.
(ANNOUNCER VO) Actually, Xathan        Gum is an additive
found in some cream cheese.
But it's not in Arla.
Arla. Live unprocessed.
♪
You know how painful heartburn              can be.
For fast-acting, long-lasting               relief,
try doctor recommended Gaviscon.
It quickly neutralizes stomach                acid
and helps keep acid down for                hours.
Relieve heartburn with fast-    acting, long-lasting Gaviscon.
(Nathan) Secondhand smoke            caused me to have
and helps keep acid down for                hours.                           asthma attacks,
infections and                    lung damage.
And I never smoked.
(Announcer) If you or someone
you know wants free help
to quit smoking,
call 1-800-QUIT-NOW.
What's the best way to get        two servings of veggies?
V8 or a fancy juice store?
Ready, go!
Hi, Juice Universe?
One large rutabaga,                with eggplant...
Done!
That's not fair.
Glad I had a V8.
The original way to                 fuel your day.
>>> IS IT POSSIBLE I SAW YOU ON  A HORSE YESTERDAY?               >> YEAH, I HAVE A RANCH JUST
A HORSE YESTERDAY?               >> YEAH, I HAVE A RANCH JUST     OUTSIDE OF TOWN.
>> YEAH, I HAVE A RANCH JUST     OUTSIDE OF TOWN.                 >> OH.
OUTSIDE OF TOWN.                 >> OH.                           HOW BIG?
>> OH.                           HOW BIG?                         >> YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW BIG --
HOW BIG?                         >> YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW BIG --   MY RANCH IS?
>> YOU WANT TO KNOW HOW BIG --   MY RANCH IS?                     NO MORE POLITE TO ASK A RANCHER
MY RANCH IS?                     NO MORE POLITE TO ASK A RANCHER  THE SIZE OF HIS ACREAGE THAN A
NO MORE POLITE TO ASK A RANCHER  THE SIZE OF HIS ACREAGE THAN A   LADY HER AGE.
THE SIZE OF HIS ACREAGE THAN A   LADY HER AGE.                    >> DULY NOTED.
LADY HER AGE.                    >> DULY NOTED.                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> DULY NOTED.                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> WELCOME BACK!
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> WELCOME BACK!                 THAT WAS A SNEAK PEEK ON THE
>> WELCOME BACK!                 THAT WAS A SNEAK PEEK ON THE     VERY CALM SIDE OF OUR VERY
THAT WAS A SNEAK PEEK ON THE     VERY CALM SIDE OF OUR VERY       TALENTED GUEST, KEVIN BACON FROM
VERY CALM SIDE OF OUR VERY       TALENTED GUEST, KEVIN BACON FROM THE ELECTRIFYING NEW SERIES --
TALENTED GUEST, KEVIN BACON FROM THE ELECTRIFYING NEW SERIES --   TELL US A LITTLE ABOUT THAT.
THE ELECTRIFYING NEW SERIES --   TELL US A LITTLE ABOUT THAT.     >> WELL, THE SERIES IS CALLED "I
TELL US A LITTLE ABOUT THAT.     >> WELL, THE SERIES IS CALLED "I LOVE DICK."
>> WELL, THE SERIES IS CALLED "I LOVE DICK."                      [ LAUGHTER ]
LOVE DICK."                      [ LAUGHTER ]                     AND THAT WAS A SCENE, JUST
[ LAUGHTER ]                     AND THAT WAS A SCENE, JUST       WANTED TO REMIND EVERYBODY.
AND THAT WAS A SCENE, JUST       WANTED TO REMIND EVERYBODY.      THAT'S A SCENE WHERE I AM
WANTED TO REMIND EVERYBODY.      THAT'S A SCENE WHERE I AM        MEETING KATHERINE HAHN'S
THAT'S A SCENE WHERE I AM        MEETING KATHERINE HAHN'S         CHARACTER FOR THE FIRST TIME,
MEETING KATHERINE HAHN'S         CHARACTER FOR THE FIRST TIME,    AND THERE IS SUPPOSE TO BE A
CHARACTER FOR THE FIRST TIME,    AND THERE IS SUPPOSE TO BE A     CONNECTION THAT'S IMMEDIATELY
AND THERE IS SUPPOSE TO BE A     CONNECTION THAT'S IMMEDIATELY    MADE BETWEEN THE TWO OF US.
CONNECTION THAT'S IMMEDIATELY    MADE BETWEEN THE TWO OF US.      >> YES.
MADE BETWEEN THE TWO OF US.      >> YES.                          >> UNTIL I FIND OUT SHE'S
>> YES.                          >> UNTIL I FIND OUT SHE'S        MARRIED AND THAT HER HUSBAND IS
>> UNTIL I FIND OUT SHE'S        MARRIED AND THAT HER HUSBAND IS  NOW A FELLOW AT THE INSTITUTE,
MARRIED AND THAT HER HUSBAND IS  NOW A FELLOW AT THE INSTITUTE,   THEN I TRY TO STEP BACK AND SAY
NOW A FELLOW AT THE INSTITUTE,   THEN I TRY TO STEP BACK AND SAY  "NO, I AM NOT GOING THERE."
THEN I TRY TO STEP BACK AND SAY  "NO, I AM NOT GOING THERE."      >> RIGHT.
"NO, I AM NOT GOING THERE."      >> RIGHT.                        WISE CHOICE.
>> RIGHT.                        WISE CHOICE.                     >> WISE CHOICE, YEAH.
WISE CHOICE.                     >> WISE CHOICE, YEAH.            >> ALTHOUGH SOON TO LEAD TO MUCH
>> WISE CHOICE, YEAH.            >> ALTHOUGH SOON TO LEAD TO MUCH MORE MISCHIEF.
>> ALTHOUGH SOON TO LEAD TO MUCH MORE MISCHIEF.                   >> OH, THERE'S A LOT OF
MORE MISCHIEF.                   >> OH, THERE'S A LOT OF          MISCHIEF.
>> OH, THERE'S A LOT OF          MISCHIEF.                        >> IT'S FANTASTIC.
MISCHIEF.                        >> IT'S FANTASTIC.               >> MISCHIEF IS GOOD WAY OF
>> IT'S FANTASTIC.               >> MISCHIEF IS GOOD WAY OF       PUTTING IT!
>> MISCHIEF IS GOOD WAY OF       PUTTING IT!                      >> YEAH!
PUTTING IT!                      >> YEAH!                         >> SO HERE IT IS COMING OUT.
>> YEAH!                         >> SO HERE IT IS COMING OUT.     I TOSSED THE PESTO RIGHT OUT OF
>> SO HERE IT IS COMING OUT.     I TOSSED THE PESTO RIGHT OUT OF  THE FOOD PROCESSOR INTO HERE.
I TOSSED THE PESTO RIGHT OUT OF  THE FOOD PROCESSOR INTO HERE.    THEN WHAT YOU DO IS TOSS IT
THE FOOD PROCESSOR INTO HERE.    THEN WHAT YOU DO IS TOSS IT      GENTLY.
THEN WHAT YOU DO IS TOSS IT      GENTLY.                          WITH A LITTLE BIT OF THE PASTA
GENTLY.                          WITH A LITTLE BIT OF THE PASTA   WATER TO BRING IT TO THE EXACT
WITH A LITTLE BIT OF THE PASTA   WATER TO BRING IT TO THE EXACT   RIGHT TEXTURE.
WATER TO BRING IT TO THE EXACT   RIGHT TEXTURE.                   THEN YOU TAKE IT TO THE FABULOUS
RIGHT TEXTURE.                   THEN YOU TAKE IT TO THE FABULOUS BOWL LIKE SO.
THEN YOU TAKE IT TO THE FABULOUS BOWL LIKE SO.                    AND THEN WE GIVE IT A QUICK
BOWL LIKE SO.                    AND THEN WE GIVE IT A QUICK      LITTLE TASTE, BECAUSE WE'RE
AND THEN WE GIVE IT A QUICK      LITTLE TASTE, BECAUSE WE'RE      PROFESSIONALS.
LITTLE TASTE, BECAUSE WE'RE      PROFESSIONALS.                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
THERE'S SOMETHING TO SERVING     CHEESE LIKE THAT MAKES EVERYONE  REALLY HAPPY.
CHEESE LIKE THAT MAKES EVERYONE  REALLY HAPPY.                    TAKE A BITE AND THEN WE'LL
REALLY HAPPY.                    TAKE A BITE AND THEN WE'LL       DISCUSS A COUPLE OTHER THINGS.
TAKE A BITE AND THEN WE'LL       DISCUSS A COUPLE OTHER THINGS.   NOW I'VE HEARD IT SAYS, THAT YOU
DISCUSS A COUPLE OTHER THINGS.   NOW I'VE HEARD IT SAYS, THAT YOU SAY YOU LEARNED EVERYTHING YOU
NOW I'VE HEARD IT SAYS, THAT YOU SAY YOU LEARNED EVERYTHING YOU   NEED TO KNOW ABOUT ACTING --
SAY YOU LEARNED EVERYTHING YOU   NEED TO KNOW ABOUT ACTING --     WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?
NEED TO KNOW ABOUT ACTING --     WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?    >> THAT'S AMAZING!
WHAT DO YOU THINK ABOUT THAT?    >> THAT'S AMAZING!               [ APPLAUSE ]
>> THAT'S AMAZING!               [ APPLAUSE ]                     THAT IS REALLY GOOD.
[ APPLAUSE ]                     THAT IS REALLY GOOD.             >> AND EASY TO MAKE, AND IF YOU
THAT IS REALLY GOOD.             >> AND EASY TO MAKE, AND IF YOU  COULDN'T FIND BROCCOLI RABE YOU
>> AND EASY TO MAKE, AND IF YOU  COULDN'T FIND BROCCOLI RABE YOU  COULD JUST USE BROCCOLI, IT'S
COULDN'T FIND BROCCOLI RABE YOU  COULD JUST USE BROCCOLI, IT'S    ALL RIGHT AMERICA.
COULD JUST USE BROCCOLI, IT'S    ALL RIGHT AMERICA.               SO I HEARD THAT YOU SAID THAT
ALL RIGHT AMERICA.               SO I HEARD THAT YOU SAID THAT    COULD LEARN EVERYTHING YOU NEED
SO I HEARD THAT YOU SAID THAT    COULD LEARN EVERYTHING YOU NEED  TO LEARN ABOUT ACTING FROM
COULD LEARN EVERYTHING YOU NEED  TO LEARN ABOUT ACTING FROM       RIDING ON THE SUBWAY IN NEW YORK
TO LEARN ABOUT ACTING FROM       RIDING ON THE SUBWAY IN NEW YORK CITY.
RIDING ON THE SUBWAY IN NEW YORK CITY.                            [ LAUGHTER ]
CITY.                            [ LAUGHTER ]                     TELL US WHAT THAT MEANS!
[ LAUGHTER ]                     TELL US WHAT THAT MEANS!         >> WELL, WHEN I FIRST MOVED TO
TELL US WHAT THAT MEANS!         >> WELL, WHEN I FIRST MOVED TO   NEW YORK, I GREW UP IN
>> WELL, WHEN I FIRST MOVED TO   NEW YORK, I GREW UP IN           PHILADELPHIA, ONE OF THE THINGS
NEW YORK, I GREW UP IN           PHILADELPHIA, ONE OF THE THINGS  I LOVE ABOUT THIS PLACE WAS THAT
PHILADELPHIA, ONE OF THE THINGS  I LOVE ABOUT THIS PLACE WAS THAT YOU KNOW JUST THE AMAZING KIND
I LOVE ABOUT THIS PLACE WAS THAT YOU KNOW JUST THE AMAZING KIND   OF DIVERSITY.
YOU KNOW JUST THE AMAZING KIND   OF DIVERSITY.                    THE KIND OF PEOPLE THAT LIVE
OF DIVERSITY.                    THE KIND OF PEOPLE THAT LIVE     HERE AND EVERYONE GETS TOGETHER
THE KIND OF PEOPLE THAT LIVE     HERE AND EVERYONE GETS TOGETHER  AND HAS TO RIDE THE SUBWAY
HERE AND EVERYONE GETS TOGETHER  AND HAS TO RIDE THE SUBWAY       TOGETHER.
AND HAS TO RIDE THE SUBWAY       TOGETHER.                        I STILL RIDE THE SUBWAY PROBABLY
TOGETHER.                        I STILL RIDE THE SUBWAY PROBABLY ONCE OR TWICE A DAY.
I STILL RIDE THE SUBWAY PROBABLY ONCE OR TWICE A DAY.             >> MM-HMM.
ONCE OR TWICE A DAY.             >> MM-HMM.                       >> I THINK THAT I AM CALLED UPON
>> MM-HMM.                       >> I THINK THAT I AM CALLED UPON OFTEN TO JUST PLAY REAL PEOPLE.
>> I THINK THAT I AM CALLED UPON OFTEN TO JUST PLAY REAL PEOPLE.  SO I THINK YOU HAVE TO BE WITH
OFTEN TO JUST PLAY REAL PEOPLE.  SO I THINK YOU HAVE TO BE WITH   REAL PEOPLE, IF YOU WANT TO BE
SO I THINK YOU HAVE TO BE WITH   REAL PEOPLE, IF YOU WANT TO BE   REAL PEOPLE.
REAL PEOPLE, IF YOU WANT TO BE   REAL PEOPLE.                     >> RIGHT.
REAL PEOPLE.                     >> RIGHT.                        BRAVO.
>> RIGHT.                        BRAVO.                           [ APPLAUSE ]
BRAVO.                           [ APPLAUSE ]                     >> SO THAT'S JUST BEEN A GREAT
[ APPLAUSE ]                     >> SO THAT'S JUST BEEN A GREAT   ACTING LESSON.
>> SO THAT'S JUST BEEN A GREAT   ACTING LESSON.                   >> I AGREE.
ACTING LESSON.                   >> I AGREE.                      I MEAN THERE'S JUST SO MUCH
>> I AGREE.                      I MEAN THERE'S JUST SO MUCH      STUFF TO LOOK AT AND IT'S SO
I MEAN THERE'S JUST SO MUCH      STUFF TO LOOK AT AND IT'S SO     MUCH FUN.
STUFF TO LOOK AT AND IT'S SO     MUCH FUN.                        SO NOW OFF A LITTLE BIT TO THAT
MUCH FUN.                        SO NOW OFF A LITTLE BIT TO THAT  TOPIC, WHAT ABOUT THE BACON
SO NOW OFF A LITTLE BIT TO THAT  TOPIC, WHAT ABOUT THE BACON      BROTHERS, MAN?
TOPIC, WHAT ABOUT THE BACON      BROTHERS, MAN?                   WHAT ABOUT MY BAND?
BROTHERS, MAN?                   WHAT ABOUT MY BAND?              WHEN IS THE MUSIC COMING BACK TO
WHAT ABOUT MY BAND?              WHEN IS THE MUSIC COMING BACK TO ME?
WHEN IS THE MUSIC COMING BACK TO ME?                              >> WE'RE DOING WELL, I MEAN --
ME?                              >> WE'RE DOING WELL, I MEAN --   >> ARE YOU GOING TO TOUR?
>> WE'RE DOING WELL, I MEAN --   >> ARE YOU GOING TO TOUR?        >> MM-HMM.
>> ARE YOU GOING TO TOUR?        >> MM-HMM.                       >> FANTASTIC!
>> MM-HMM.                       >> FANTASTIC!                    [ APPLAUSE ]
>> FANTASTIC!                    [ APPLAUSE ]                     >> WE'RE GOING OUT, RIGHT AFTER
[ APPLAUSE ]                     >> WE'RE GOING OUT, RIGHT AFTER  MEMORIAL DAY.
>> WE'RE GOING OUT, RIGHT AFTER  MEMORIAL DAY.                    WE'RE ACTUALLY PLAYING, SPEAKING
MEMORIAL DAY.                    WE'RE ACTUALLY PLAYING, SPEAKING OF TEXAS, BECAUSE WE SHOT "I
WE'RE ACTUALLY PLAYING, SPEAKING OF TEXAS, BECAUSE WE SHOT "I     LOVE DICK" IN TEXAS, BUT I AM
OF TEXAS, BECAUSE WE SHOT "I     LOVE DICK" IN TEXAS, BUT I AM    DOING A LOT OF TEXAS.
LOVE DICK" IN TEXAS, BUT I AM    DOING A LOT OF TEXAS.            >> OH FANTASTIC!
DOING A LOT OF TEXAS.            >> OH FANTASTIC!                 >> I KIND OF LIKE SOUTHERN --
>> OH FANTASTIC!                 >> I KIND OF LIKE SOUTHERN --    AND THEN LATER ON UP IN THE --
>> I KIND OF LIKE SOUTHERN --    AND THEN LATER ON UP IN THE --   >> NORTHERN MICHIGAN?
AND THEN LATER ON UP IN THE --   >> NORTHERN MICHIGAN?            >> NO, WE'RE NOT GETTING
>> NORTHERN MICHIGAN?            >> NO, WE'RE NOT GETTING         MICHIGAN.
>> NO, WE'RE NOT GETTING         MICHIGAN.                        >> DANG!
MICHIGAN.                        >> DANG!                         >> RIGHT OUTSIDE OF TEXAS.
>> DANG!                         >> RIGHT OUTSIDE OF TEXAS.       [ LAUGHTER ]
>> RIGHT OUTSIDE OF TEXAS.       [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> RIGHT, THAT WOULD BE WHAT
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> RIGHT, THAT WOULD BE WHAT     THEY CALL BAD ROUTING.
>> RIGHT, THAT WOULD BE WHAT     THEY CALL BAD ROUTING.           >> YEAH, EXACTLY.
THEY CALL BAD ROUTING.           >> YEAH, EXACTLY.                [ LAUGHTER ]
>> YEAH, EXACTLY.                [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> I HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT THAT!
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> I HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT THAT!   >> WELL, IT'S REALLY NICE TO
>> I HEARD SO MUCH ABOUT THAT!   >> WELL, IT'S REALLY NICE TO     HAVE YOU HERE.
>> WELL, IT'S REALLY NICE TO     HAVE YOU HERE.                   >> SO GREAT.
HAVE YOU HERE.                   >> SO GREAT.                     >> BUT WE CAN'T LET YOU LEAVE
>> SO GREAT.                     >> BUT WE CAN'T LET YOU LEAVE    WITHOUT A LITTLE SOMETHING --
>> BUT WE CAN'T LET YOU LEAVE    WITHOUT A LITTLE SOMETHING --    IT'S TIME TO "CHEWSE" YOUR GIFT.
WITHOUT A LITTLE SOMETHING --    IT'S TIME TO "CHEWSE" YOUR GIFT. >> OH REALLY?
IT'S TIME TO "CHEWSE" YOUR GIFT. >> OH REALLY?                    [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OH REALLY?                    [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> ALSO KNOWN AS STUFF WE FOUND
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> ALSO KNOWN AS STUFF WE FOUND  LYING AROUND THE STUDIO.
>> ALSO KNOWN AS STUFF WE FOUND  LYING AROUND THE STUDIO.         GIVE IT A TRY!
LYING AROUND THE STUDIO.         GIVE IT A TRY!                   >> ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE --
GIVE IT A TRY!                   >> ALL RIGHT, LET'S SEE --       [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> YES.                          >> ALL RIGHT.                    >> THE SELFIE STICK!
>> ALL RIGHT.                    >> THE SELFIE STICK!             >> A SELFIE STICK, I COULD USE
>> THE SELFIE STICK!             >> A SELFIE STICK, I COULD USE   ONE OF THESE!
>> A SELFIE STICK, I COULD USE   ONE OF THESE!                    [ LAUGHTER ]
ONE OF THESE!                    [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> THAT'S A NICE SELFIE STICK,
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> THAT'S A NICE SELFIE STICK,   WOW!
>> THAT'S A NICE SELFIE STICK,   WOW!                             >> YOU CAN JOIN THE CROWD OF
WOW!                             >> YOU CAN JOIN THE CROWD OF     PEOPLE THAT CONSTANTLY GO LIKE
>> YOU CAN JOIN THE CROWD OF     PEOPLE THAT CONSTANTLY GO LIKE   THIS.
PEOPLE THAT CONSTANTLY GO LIKE   THIS.                            NOW YOU CAN DO IT EVEN FURTHER.
THIS.                            NOW YOU CAN DO IT EVEN FURTHER.  >> NOW I AM GOING TO TAKE MY
NOW YOU CAN DO IT EVEN FURTHER.  >> NOW I AM GOING TO TAKE MY     SHIRT OFF AND START COOKING!
>> NOW I AM GOING TO TAKE MY     SHIRT OFF AND START COOKING!     >> THAT'S RIGHT!
SHIRT OFF AND START COOKING!     >> THAT'S RIGHT!                 GET SOME EGGS GOING ON THERE!
>> THAT'S RIGHT!                 GET SOME EGGS GOING ON THERE!    [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
GET SOME EGGS GOING ON THERE!    [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          THANKS TO KEVIN BACON FOR
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          THANKS TO KEVIN BACON FOR        STOPPING BY.
THANKS TO KEVIN BACON FOR        STOPPING BY.                     HE'S CURRENTLY IN HIS NEW SERIES
STOPPING BY.                     HE'S CURRENTLY IN HIS NEW SERIES "I LOVE DICK" STREAMING ON
HE'S CURRENTLY IN HIS NEW SERIES "I LOVE DICK" STREAMING ON       AMAZON PRIME THIS FRIDAY.
"I LOVE DICK" STREAMING ON       AMAZON PRIME THIS FRIDAY.        WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!
AMAZON PRIME THIS FRIDAY.        WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
WE WILL BE RIGHT BACK!           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪                                >> Announcer: COMING UP,
♪                                >> Announcer: COMING UP,         MOTHER'S DAY IS RIGHT AROUND THE
>> Announcer: COMING UP,         MOTHER'S DAY IS RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER, AND CLINTON'S GOT A
MOTHER'S DAY IS RIGHT AROUND THE CORNER, AND CLINTON'S GOT A      MUST-SEE TIP YOU WON'T FIND
CORNER, AND CLINTON'S GOT A      MUST-SEE TIP YOU WON'T FIND      ANYWHERE ELSE.
MUST-SEE TIP YOU WON'T FIND      ANYWHERE ELSE.                   FIND OUT WHAT IT IS, IN A
ANYWHERE ELSE.                   FIND OUT WHAT IT IS, IN A        MOMENT.
FIND OUT WHAT IT IS, IN A        MOMENT.                          [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
Allergy symptoms                 distracting you?
Doctors recommend taking           Claritin every day
of your allergy season           for continuous relief.
Claritin provides powerful,      non-drowsy, 24-hour relief.
For fewer interruptions from the amazing things you do every day.
Live Claritin Clear.                  Every day.
♪ ♪ ♪
THE BEST WAY TO GET TOGETHER
IS WITH A TREAT
YOU MAKE TOGETHER.
♪ ♪ ♪
UN-Stop right there!
I'm about to pop a cap of        “mmm fresh” in that washer
with Unstopables In-Wash         Scent Boosters by Downy.
Because this scent lasts             up to 12 weeks,
which is longer than any     relationship I've ever been in.
Freshness for weeks!
>> Announcer: "THE CHEW" WILL    RETURN IN A MOMENT, HERE ON ABC.
We're trying to turn screen         time into active time...
here goes!
We're dolphins!
We're making our local park       a safe place for families.
We're in super hero training!
We're having more water          and fewer sugary drinks.
And we feel stronger.
I'm doing better in school.
We feel happier.
Small changes you make today
can make a big difference in how            you feel....
and may help prevent obesity,
high blood pressure,             and type 2 diabetes.
Start now to turn             today into a better day.
We're still going,              and we feel better!
♪                                >> Announcer: WELCOME BACK TO    "THE CHEW'S" WEEKNIGHT WOWS.
>> Announcer: WELCOME BACK TO    "THE CHEW'S" WEEKNIGHT WOWS.     [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
"THE CHEW'S" WEEKNIGHT WOWS.     [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> HEY, EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> HEY, EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK  TO "THE CHEW."
>> HEY, EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK  TO "THE CHEW."                   NOW, ALL WEEK, YOU GUYS ARE
TO "THE CHEW."                   NOW, ALL WEEK, YOU GUYS ARE      CALLING THE SHOTS TO REQUEST A
NOW, ALL WEEK, YOU GUYS ARE      CALLING THE SHOTS TO REQUEST A   RECIPE.
CALLING THE SHOTS TO REQUEST A   RECIPE.                          TODAY'S ASK COMES FROM JANINE ON
RECIPE.                          TODAY'S ASK COMES FROM JANINE ON FACEBOOK.
TODAY'S ASK COMES FROM JANINE ON FACEBOOK.                        SHE WROTE, "STUFFED PEPPERS.
FACEBOOK.                        SHE WROTE, "STUFFED PEPPERS.     [ LAUGHTER ]
SHE WROTE, "STUFFED PEPPERS.     [ LAUGHTER ]                     MY MOTHER USED TO MAKE THESE A
[ LAUGHTER ]                     MY MOTHER USED TO MAKE THESE A   LOT, BUT I DON'T HAVE HER
MY MOTHER USED TO MAKE THESE A   LOT, BUT I DON'T HAVE HER        RECIPE."
LOT, BUT I DON'T HAVE HER        RECIPE."                         SO JANINE, I GOT YOU.
RECIPE."                         SO JANINE, I GOT YOU.            I'M GOING TO MAKE A STUFFED
SO JANINE, I GOT YOU.            I'M GOING TO MAKE A STUFFED      PEPPER, THE KIND I GREW UP
I'M GOING TO MAKE A STUFFED      PEPPER, THE KIND I GREW UP       EATING.
PEPPER, THE KIND I GREW UP       EATING.                          IT'S A MEDITERRANEAN VERSION OF
EATING.                          IT'S A MEDITERRANEAN VERSION OF  A STUFFED PEPPER.
IT'S A MEDITERRANEAN VERSION OF  A STUFFED PEPPER.                AND IT IS TOPPED WITH A LITTLE
A STUFFED PEPPER.                AND IT IS TOPPED WITH A LITTLE   BIT OF FETA CHEESE.
AND IT IS TOPPED WITH A LITTLE   BIT OF FETA CHEESE.              >> OH, THAT LOOKS GOOD.
BIT OF FETA CHEESE.              >> OH, THAT LOOKS GOOD.          >> HOW ARE YOU FEELING ABOUT
>> OH, THAT LOOKS GOOD.          >> HOW ARE YOU FEELING ABOUT     THAT?
>> HOW ARE YOU FEELING ABOUT     THAT?                            >> I FEEL GOOD ABOUT IT.
THAT?                            >> I FEEL GOOD ABOUT IT.         [ LAUGHTER ]
>> I FEEL GOOD ABOUT IT.         [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> NOW, I USED TO LOVE EATING
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> NOW, I USED TO LOVE EATING    STUFFED PEPPERS AS A KID.
>> NOW, I USED TO LOVE EATING    STUFFED PEPPERS AS A KID.        AND THEN AS I BECAME AN ADULT,
STUFFED PEPPERS AS A KID.        AND THEN AS I BECAME AN ADULT,   IT'S THE REASON THAT WE DID
AND THEN AS I BECAME AN ADULT,   IT'S THE REASON THAT WE DID      THEM.
IT'S THE REASON THAT WE DID      THEM.                            IT'S A GREAT WAY TO STRETCH MEAT
THEM.                            IT'S A GREAT WAY TO STRETCH MEAT A LITTLE BIT AND GET YOUR KIDS
IT'S A GREAT WAY TO STRETCH MEAT A LITTLE BIT AND GET YOUR KIDS   TO EAT VEGETABLES ALL WRAPPED IN
A LITTLE BIT AND GET YOUR KIDS   TO EAT VEGETABLES ALL WRAPPED IN ONE.
TO EAT VEGETABLES ALL WRAPPED IN ONE.                             >> WELL, LET'S DO IT.
ONE.                             >> WELL, LET'S DO IT.            >> SO YOU ONLY HAD TO USE HALF
>> WELL, LET'S DO IT.            >> SO YOU ONLY HAD TO USE HALF   THE MEAT AND YOU GET A VEGGIE.
>> SO YOU ONLY HAD TO USE HALF   THE MEAT AND YOU GET A VEGGIE.   SO I'M GOING TO START --
THE MEAT AND YOU GET A VEGGIE.   SO I'M GOING TO START --         WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A BECHAMEL,
SO I'M GOING TO START --         WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A BECHAMEL,  BUT THEN FINISH IT WITH FETA.
WE'RE GOING TO MAKE A BECHAMEL,  BUT THEN FINISH IT WITH FETA.    SO IT'S GOING TO HAVE THAT NICE
BUT THEN FINISH IT WITH FETA.    SO IT'S GOING TO HAVE THAT NICE  SALTINESS IN THE CREAMY SAUCE.
SO IT'S GOING TO HAVE THAT NICE  SALTINESS IN THE CREAMY SAUCE.   >> CREAMY, SALTY SAUCE.
SALTINESS IN THE CREAMY SAUCE.   >> CREAMY, SALTY SAUCE.          >> SO YOU'RE GOING TO START WITH
>> CREAMY, SALTY SAUCE.          >> SO YOU'RE GOING TO START WITH EQUAL PARTS OF BUTTER AND FLOUR.
>> SO YOU'RE GOING TO START WITH EQUAL PARTS OF BUTTER AND FLOUR. SO TWO TEASPOONS OF BUTTER, TWO
EQUAL PARTS OF BUTTER AND FLOUR. SO TWO TEASPOONS OF BUTTER, TWO  TEASPOONS OF FLOUR.
SO TWO TEASPOONS OF BUTTER, TWO  TEASPOONS OF FLOUR.              >> TABLESPOONS.
TEASPOONS OF FLOUR.              >> TABLESPOONS.                  >> TABLESPOONS, I'M SORRY.
>> TABLESPOONS.                  >> TABLESPOONS, I'M SORRY.       THERE YOU GO.
>> TABLESPOONS, I'M SORRY.       THERE YOU GO.                    THAT MUCH.
THERE YOU GO.                    THAT MUCH.                       WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT WHEN
THAT MUCH.                       WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT WHEN   YOU'RE COOKING THIS, YOU KIND OF
WHEN YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT WHEN   YOU'RE COOKING THIS, YOU KIND OF WANT EQUAL PARTS BUTTER AND
YOU'RE COOKING THIS, YOU KIND OF WANT EQUAL PARTS BUTTER AND      FLOUR, AND YOU WANT A WET SAND
WANT EQUAL PARTS BUTTER AND      FLOUR, AND YOU WANT A WET SAND   CONSISTENCY.
FLOUR, AND YOU WANT A WET SAND   CONSISTENCY.                     IF IT GETS A LITTLE BIT TOO DRY,
CONSISTENCY.                     IF IT GETS A LITTLE BIT TOO DRY, YOU COULD ADD A LITTLE BIT MORE.
IF IT GETS A LITTLE BIT TOO DRY, YOU COULD ADD A LITTLE BIT MORE. IT SHOULD LOOK LIKE SAND ON THE
YOU COULD ADD A LITTLE BIT MORE. IT SHOULD LOOK LIKE SAND ON THE  BEACH IN THE MORNING AFTER THE
IT SHOULD LOOK LIKE SAND ON THE  BEACH IN THE MORNING AFTER THE   WAVES ARE RIGHT THERE.
BEACH IN THE MORNING AFTER THE   WAVES ARE RIGHT THERE.           >> OH, YEAH, JUST LIKE THAT,
WAVES ARE RIGHT THERE.           >> OH, YEAH, JUST LIKE THAT,     OKAY.
>> OH, YEAH, JUST LIKE THAT,     OKAY.                            [ LAUGHTER ]
OKAY.                            [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> SAND ON A BEACH.
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> SAND ON A BEACH.              AND THEN --
>> SAND ON A BEACH.              AND THEN --                      CLINTON LIKES HIS SAND A LITTLE
AND THEN --                      CLINTON LIKES HIS SAND A LITTLE  WETTER, APPARENTLY.
CLINTON LIKES HIS SAND A LITTLE  WETTER, APPARENTLY.              >> NO, I FELT LIKE IT NEEDED A
WETTER, APPARENTLY.              >> NO, I FELT LIKE IT NEEDED A   LITTLE MORE.
>> NO, I FELT LIKE IT NEEDED A   LITTLE MORE.                     >> YEAH, THAT'S PERFECT.
LITTLE MORE.                     >> YEAH, THAT'S PERFECT.         AND THEN, FOR EVERY TWO OUNCES
>> YEAH, THAT'S PERFECT.         AND THEN, FOR EVERY TWO OUNCES   OF THE ROUX THAT YOU MAKE,
AND THEN, FOR EVERY TWO OUNCES   OF THE ROUX THAT YOU MAKE,       YOU'RE JUST MAKING A ROUX.
OF THE ROUX THAT YOU MAKE,       YOU'RE JUST MAKING A ROUX.       THAT'S GOING TO THICKEN ABOUT
YOU'RE JUST MAKING A ROUX.       THAT'S GOING TO THICKEN ABOUT    16 OUNCES OF LIQUID.
THAT'S GOING TO THICKEN ABOUT    16 OUNCES OF LIQUID.             SO YOU HAVE ABOUT AN OUNCE OF
16 OUNCES OF LIQUID.             SO YOU HAVE ABOUT AN OUNCE OF    ROUX HERE.
SO YOU HAVE ABOUT AN OUNCE OF    ROUX HERE.                       YOU'RE GOING TO THICKEN
ROUX HERE.                       YOU'RE GOING TO THICKEN          16 OUNCES OF LIQUID.
YOU'RE GOING TO THICKEN          16 OUNCES OF LIQUID.             >> OKAY, GOT IT.
16 OUNCES OF LIQUID.             >> OKAY, GOT IT.                 >> KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?
>> OKAY, GOT IT.                 >> KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?         >> YEAH, I GOT YOU RIGHT HERE.
>> KNOW WHAT I'M SAYING?         >> YEAH, I GOT YOU RIGHT HERE.   OH.
>> YEAH, I GOT YOU RIGHT HERE.   OH.                              SPLATTERED A LITTLE FAT ON ME
OH.                              SPLATTERED A LITTLE FAT ON ME    THERE.
SPLATTERED A LITTLE FAT ON ME    THERE.                           [ LAUGHTER ]
THERE.                           [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> ON YOUR FAVORITE COAT.
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> ON YOUR FAVORITE COAT.        >> ON MY FAVORITE, IT WAS REALLY
>> ON YOUR FAVORITE COAT.        >> ON MY FAVORITE, IT WAS REALLY ON MY HAND.
>> ON MY FAVORITE, IT WAS REALLY ON MY HAND.                      IT'S OKAY.
ON MY HAND.                      IT'S OKAY.                       I'M FINE.
IT'S OKAY.                       I'M FINE.                        >> JUST KEEP WHISKING, BUDDY.
I'M FINE.                        >> JUST KEEP WHISKING, BUDDY.    [ LAUGHTER ]
>> JUST KEEP WHISKING, BUDDY.    [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IT WAS JUST STARTLING.
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IT WAS JUST STARTLING.        IT STARTLED ME, HOT FAT ON MY
>> IT WAS JUST STARTLING.        IT STARTLED ME, HOT FAT ON MY    HAND.
IT STARTLED ME, HOT FAT ON MY    HAND.                            STARTLED ME.
HAND.                            STARTLED ME.                     >> ALL RIGHT.
STARTLED ME.                     >> ALL RIGHT.                    >> I GET ALL JUMPY.
>> ALL RIGHT.                    >> I GET ALL JUMPY.              >> SEE HOW THAT'S STARTING TO
>> I GET ALL JUMPY.              >> SEE HOW THAT'S STARTING TO    THICKEN UP?
>> SEE HOW THAT'S STARTING TO    THICKEN UP?                      NOW GRATE THE NUTMEG.
THICKEN UP?                      NOW GRATE THE NUTMEG.            >> GRATE THE NUTMEG.
NOW GRATE THE NUTMEG.            >> GRATE THE NUTMEG.             >> AND THEN YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE
>> GRATE THE NUTMEG.             >> AND THEN YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE THAT OFF THE HEAT AND ADD THE
>> AND THEN YOU'RE GOING TO TAKE THAT OFF THE HEAT AND ADD THE    FETA.
THAT OFF THE HEAT AND ADD THE    FETA.                            ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE, I HAVE
FETA.                            ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE, I HAVE  ABOUT THREE QUARTERS OF A POUND,
ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE, I HAVE  ABOUT THREE QUARTERS OF A POUND, A POUND OF GROUND BEEF.
ABOUT THREE QUARTERS OF A POUND, A POUND OF GROUND BEEF.          I'VE TOASTED THAT UP IN A LITTLE
A POUND OF GROUND BEEF.          I'VE TOASTED THAT UP IN A LITTLE BIT OF OLIVE OIL.
I'VE TOASTED THAT UP IN A LITTLE BIT OF OLIVE OIL.                TO THIS I'M GOING TO ADD SOME
BIT OF OLIVE OIL.                TO THIS I'M GOING TO ADD SOME    PINE NUTS.
TO THIS I'M GOING TO ADD SOME    PINE NUTS.                       I'M GOING TO ADD --
PINE NUTS.                       I'M GOING TO ADD --              COULD YOU DICE THAT ONION?
I'M GOING TO ADD --              COULD YOU DICE THAT ONION?       >> DICING, DICING.
COULD YOU DICE THAT ONION?       >> DICING, DICING.               HOW SMALL, SYMON?
>> DICING, DICING.               HOW SMALL, SYMON?                >> OH, HERE YOU GO.
HOW SMALL, SYMON?                >> OH, HERE YOU GO.              I'M GOING TO ADD SOME SLICED
>> OH, HERE YOU GO.              I'M GOING TO ADD SOME SLICED     GARLIC.
I'M GOING TO ADD SOME SLICED     GARLIC.                          AND THEN I'M GOING TO ADD A
GARLIC.                          AND THEN I'M GOING TO ADD A      WHOLE BUNCH OF FRESH HERBS AND A
AND THEN I'M GOING TO ADD A      WHOLE BUNCH OF FRESH HERBS AND A LITTLE BIT OF CORIANDER.
WHOLE BUNCH OF FRESH HERBS AND A LITTLE BIT OF CORIANDER.         AND THIS IS WHERE YOU COULD
LITTLE BIT OF CORIANDER.         AND THIS IS WHERE YOU COULD      REALLY HAVE FUN WITH IT.
AND THIS IS WHERE YOU COULD      REALLY HAVE FUN WITH IT.         I'M DOING IT WITH GROUND BEEF
REALLY HAVE FUN WITH IT.         I'M DOING IT WITH GROUND BEEF    BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I GREW UP
I'M DOING IT WITH GROUND BEEF    BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I GREW UP    EATING.
BECAUSE THAT'S WHAT I GREW UP    EATING.                          YOU COULD CERTAINLY DO IT WITH
EATING.                          YOU COULD CERTAINLY DO IT WITH   GROUND TURKEY OR ANY GROUND MEAT
YOU COULD CERTAINLY DO IT WITH   GROUND TURKEY OR ANY GROUND MEAT THAT YOU KIND OF LIKE.
GROUND TURKEY OR ANY GROUND MEAT THAT YOU KIND OF LIKE.           AND I HAVE FRESH OREGANO, FRESH
THAT YOU KIND OF LIKE.           AND I HAVE FRESH OREGANO, FRESH  PARSLEY.
AND I HAVE FRESH OREGANO, FRESH  PARSLEY.                         >> SO NOW LET ME ASK YOU THIS,
PARSLEY.                         >> SO NOW LET ME ASK YOU THIS,   SYMON.
>> SO NOW LET ME ASK YOU THIS,   SYMON.                           >> YES, CHEF.
SYMON.                           >> YES, CHEF.                    >> STUFFED CABBAGE AND STUFFED
>> YES, CHEF.                    >> STUFFED CABBAGE AND STUFFED   PEPPERS.
>> STUFFED CABBAGE AND STUFFED   PEPPERS.                         SAME FILLING?
PEPPERS.                         SAME FILLING?                    >> YOU COULD USE THE SAME
SAME FILLING?                    >> YOU COULD USE THE SAME        FILLING.
>> YOU COULD USE THE SAME        FILLING.                         OH, YES, YOU COULD.
FILLING.                         OH, YES, YOU COULD.              AND WHEN I GREW UP, IT WAS
OH, YES, YOU COULD.              AND WHEN I GREW UP, IT WAS       FUNNY.
AND WHEN I GREW UP, IT WAS       FUNNY.                           STUFFED PEPPERS, FOR SOME
FUNNY.                           STUFFED PEPPERS, FOR SOME        REASON, TOOK MORE OF A GREEK
STUFFED PEPPERS, FOR SOME        REASON, TOOK MORE OF A GREEK     SPIN.
REASON, TOOK MORE OF A GREEK     SPIN.                            AND STUFFED CABBAGE WAS VERY
SPIN.                            AND STUFFED CABBAGE WAS VERY     EASTERN EURO.
AND STUFFED CABBAGE WAS VERY     EASTERN EURO.                    BUT THEY WOULD BOTH WORK
EASTERN EURO.                    BUT THEY WOULD BOTH WORK         TOGETHER.
BUT THEY WOULD BOTH WORK         TOGETHER.                        ALL RIGHT, SO NOW WE ADD OUR
TOGETHER.                        ALL RIGHT, SO NOW WE ADD OUR     ONION.
ALL RIGHT, SO NOW WE ADD OUR     ONION.                           AND WE ADD A LITTLE BIT MORE FAT
ONION.                           AND WE ADD A LITTLE BIT MORE FAT TO THIS.
AND WE ADD A LITTLE BIT MORE FAT TO THIS.                         I'M GOING TO ADD SOME FRESH
TO THIS.                         I'M GOING TO ADD SOME FRESH      OREGANO.
I'M GOING TO ADD SOME FRESH      OREGANO.                         SOME FRESH PARSLEY.
OREGANO.                         SOME FRESH PARSLEY.              SOMETIMES I'D EVEN PUT MINT IN
SOME FRESH PARSLEY.              SOMETIMES I'D EVEN PUT MINT IN   HERE IF I'M FEELING UNBELIEVABLY
SOMETIMES I'D EVEN PUT MINT IN   HERE IF I'M FEELING UNBELIEVABLY CRAZY.
HERE IF I'M FEELING UNBELIEVABLY CRAZY.                           >> HOW ABOUT HOT PEPPERS?
CRAZY.                           >> HOW ABOUT HOT PEPPERS?        >> I WOULD PUT HOT PEPPERS IN.
>> HOW ABOUT HOT PEPPERS?        >> I WOULD PUT HOT PEPPERS IN.   SOME SALT.
>> I WOULD PUT HOT PEPPERS IN.   SOME SALT.                       >> WOULD YOU WITH A GOAT?
SOME SALT.                       >> WOULD YOU WITH A GOAT?        ON A BOAT?
>> WOULD YOU WITH A GOAT?        ON A BOAT?                       >> I WILL NOT EAT GREEN EGGS AND
ON A BOAT?                       >> I WILL NOT EAT GREEN EGGS AND HAM.
>> I WILL NOT EAT GREEN EGGS AND HAM.                             >> THERE YOU GO.
HAM.                             >> THERE YOU GO.                 >> AND A LITTLE BIT OF CORIANDER
>> THERE YOU GO.                 >> AND A LITTLE BIT OF CORIANDER SEED.
>> AND A LITTLE BIT OF CORIANDER SEED.                            AND SOME CRACKED BLACK PEPPER.
SEED.                            AND SOME CRACKED BLACK PEPPER.   NOW, M.B. IF YOU COULD TAKE THAT
AND SOME CRACKED BLACK PEPPER.   NOW, M.B. IF YOU COULD TAKE THAT PEPPER, CUT THE TOP OFF AND
NOW, M.B. IF YOU COULD TAKE THAT PEPPER, CUT THE TOP OFF AND      HOLLOW IT FOR ME.
PEPPER, CUT THE TOP OFF AND      HOLLOW IT FOR ME.                CLINTON, YOU HAVE DONE A
HOLLOW IT FOR ME.                CLINTON, YOU HAVE DONE A         FABULOUS JOB WITH THIS.
CLINTON, YOU HAVE DONE A         FABULOUS JOB WITH THIS.          >> FEELING GOOD ABOUT THAT?
FABULOUS JOB WITH THIS.          >> FEELING GOOD ABOUT THAT?      >> I NEED A LITTLE MORE MILK.
>> FEELING GOOD ABOUT THAT?      >> I NEED A LITTLE MORE MILK.    >> YOU WENT --
>> I NEED A LITTLE MORE MILK.    >> YOU WENT --                   [ LAUGHTER ]
>> YOU WENT --                   [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> MILK.
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> MILK.                         [ LAUGHTER ]
>> MILK.                         [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WE HAVE A LOT OF ROUX.
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WE HAVE A LOT OF ROUX.        >> DID YOUR MOTHER STOP TELLING
>> WE HAVE A LOT OF ROUX.        >> DID YOUR MOTHER STOP TELLING  YOU TO YELL IN THE HOUSE?
>> DID YOUR MOTHER STOP TELLING  YOU TO YELL IN THE HOUSE?        >> DO YOU WANT ME TO FLATTEN IT
YOU TO YELL IN THE HOUSE?        >> DO YOU WANT ME TO FLATTEN IT  OR LEAVE IT THERE?
>> DO YOU WANT ME TO FLATTEN IT  OR LEAVE IT THERE?               >> YOU CAN COVER IT JUST A
OR LEAVE IT THERE?               >> YOU CAN COVER IT JUST A       LITTLE BIT.
>> YOU CAN COVER IT JUST A       LITTLE BIT.                      >> DON'T WANT TO CHALLENGE IT.
LITTLE BIT.                      >> DON'T WANT TO CHALLENGE IT.   >> ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE.
>> DON'T WANT TO CHALLENGE IT.   >> ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE.      LOOK AT THIS.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO OVER HERE.      LOOK AT THIS.                    >> OH, MIRACULOUSLY.
LOOK AT THIS.                    >> OH, MIRACULOUSLY.             >> SO WE HAVE A COUPLE THAT
>> OH, MIRACULOUSLY.             >> SO WE HAVE A COUPLE THAT      WE'VE ALREADY STUFFED.
>> SO WE HAVE A COUPLE THAT      WE'VE ALREADY STUFFED.           IN THE BASE OF THIS WE HAVE --
WE'VE ALREADY STUFFED.           IN THE BASE OF THIS WE HAVE --   >> I'M BACK.
IN THE BASE OF THIS WE HAVE --   >> I'M BACK.                     [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> I'M BACK.                     [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> I STOLE THIS FROM A CAT.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> I STOLE THIS FROM A CAT.      >> DUMP IT IN, DUMP IT IN BEFORE
>> I STOLE THIS FROM A CAT.      >> DUMP IT IN, DUMP IT IN BEFORE THAT CAT --
>> DUMP IT IN, DUMP IT IN BEFORE THAT CAT --                      [ AUDIENCE OOHS ]
THAT CAT --                      [ AUDIENCE OOHS ]                >> YOU KNOCKED IT.
[ AUDIENCE OOHS ]                >> YOU KNOCKED IT.               BATALI.
>> YOU KNOCKED IT.               BATALI.                          >> I DIDN'T DO IT.
BATALI.                          >> I DIDN'T DO IT.               >> YOU HIT THE WHISK.
>> I DIDN'T DO IT.               >> YOU HIT THE WHISK.            [ APPLAUSE ]
>> BUT THIS IS A GOOD STUDY IN   RATIO.                           IF YOU LOOK AT THE RATIO, YOU
RATIO.                           IF YOU LOOK AT THE RATIO, YOU    ALWAYS KNOW WHAT IT IS.
IF YOU LOOK AT THE RATIO, YOU    ALWAYS KNOW WHAT IT IS.          IT'S OKAY IF YOU HAVE A LITTLE
ALWAYS KNOW WHAT IT IS.          IT'S OKAY IF YOU HAVE A LITTLE   EXTRA, NO REASON TO PANIC.
IT'S OKAY IF YOU HAVE A LITTLE   EXTRA, NO REASON TO PANIC.       I DON'T KNOW WHO'S GOING TO
EXTRA, NO REASON TO PANIC.       I DON'T KNOW WHO'S GOING TO      CLEAN UP THE STOVE.
I DON'T KNOW WHO'S GOING TO      CLEAN UP THE STOVE.              MAYBE GO FIND THAT CAT.
CLEAN UP THE STOVE.              MAYBE GO FIND THAT CAT.          [ LAUGHTER ]
MAYBE GO FIND THAT CAT.          [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> SO THE MILK DOESN'T GO IN
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> SO THE MILK DOESN'T GO IN     HERE.
>> SO THE MILK DOESN'T GO IN     HERE.                            >> OH, YOU JUST WAIT.
HERE.                            >> OH, YOU JUST WAIT.            >> I AM SO WAITING.
>> OH, YOU JUST WAIT.            >> I AM SO WAITING.              >> I WANT YOU TO STUFF THESE
>> I AM SO WAITING.              >> I WANT YOU TO STUFF THESE     TWO.
>> I WANT YOU TO STUFF THESE     TWO.                             >> I WOULD LOVE TO.
TWO.                             >> I WOULD LOVE TO.              >> OH, THE RICE.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO.              >> OH, THE RICE.                 >> OH, THE RICE.
>> OH, THE RICE.                 >> OH, THE RICE.                 >> OH, MY GOD, THE MILK GOT ME
>> OH, THE RICE.                 >> OH, MY GOD, THE MILK GOT ME   ALL SIDETRACKED.
>> OH, MY GOD, THE MILK GOT ME   ALL SIDETRACKED.                 ALL RIGHT.
ALL SIDETRACKED.                 ALL RIGHT.                       >> I'M JUST GOING TO STAND OVER
ALL RIGHT.                       >> I'M JUST GOING TO STAND OVER  HERE.
>> I'M JUST GOING TO STAND OVER  HERE.                            [ LAUGHTER ]
HERE.                            [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IT ALL STARTED WITH A LITTLE
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IT ALL STARTED WITH A LITTLE  FAT SPLATTER, AND THEN THINGS
>> IT ALL STARTED WITH A LITTLE  FAT SPLATTER, AND THEN THINGS    WENT TO HELL.
FAT SPLATTER, AND THEN THINGS    WENT TO HELL.                    >> WELL, I WAS WATCHING YOU SAY
WENT TO HELL.                    >> WELL, I WAS WATCHING YOU SAY  16 OUNCES, AND I'M LOOKING AT
>> WELL, I WAS WATCHING YOU SAY  16 OUNCES, AND I'M LOOKING AT    THAT LITTLE THING OVER THERE AND
16 OUNCES, AND I'M LOOKING AT    THAT LITTLE THING OVER THERE AND I'M LIKE, THAT IS NOT 16 OUNCES.
THAT LITTLE THING OVER THERE AND I'M LIKE, THAT IS NOT 16 OUNCES. >> ALL RIGHT, SO THEN WE TAKE
I'M LIKE, THAT IS NOT 16 OUNCES. >> ALL RIGHT, SO THEN WE TAKE    THIS BECHAMEL.
>> ALL RIGHT, SO THEN WE TAKE    THIS BECHAMEL.                   WE PUT IT ON TOP.
THIS BECHAMEL.                   WE PUT IT ON TOP.                AND IT'S GOING TO SLOWLY OOZE
WE PUT IT ON TOP.                AND IT'S GOING TO SLOWLY OOZE    AND BAKE DOWN INTO OUR STUFFED
AND IT'S GOING TO SLOWLY OOZE    AND BAKE DOWN INTO OUR STUFFED   PEPPERS AND GIVE IT A LITTLE BIT
AND BAKE DOWN INTO OUR STUFFED   PEPPERS AND GIVE IT A LITTLE BIT OF CARAMELLY, SALTY GOODNESS ON
PEPPERS AND GIVE IT A LITTLE BIT OF CARAMELLY, SALTY GOODNESS ON  TOP.
OF CARAMELLY, SALTY GOODNESS ON  TOP.                             I'M GOING TO STICK THIS IN THE
TOP.                             I'M GOING TO STICK THIS IN THE   OVEN.
I'M GOING TO STICK THIS IN THE   OVEN.                            IT'S GOING TO GO TO ABOUT
OVEN.                            IT'S GOING TO GO TO ABOUT        375 DEGREES UNTIL IT'S GOLDEN
IT'S GOING TO GO TO ABOUT        375 DEGREES UNTIL IT'S GOLDEN    AND COOKED THROUGH.
375 DEGREES UNTIL IT'S GOLDEN    AND COOKED THROUGH.              OH, GOD, WHEN WE COME BACK,
AND COOKED THROUGH.              OH, GOD, WHEN WE COME BACK,      CLINTON'S GOING TO SHOW YOU HIS
OH, GOD, WHEN WE COME BACK,      CLINTON'S GOING TO SHOW YOU HIS  MOTHER'S DAY GIFT AND I'M GOING
CLINTON'S GOING TO SHOW YOU HIS  MOTHER'S DAY GIFT AND I'M GOING  TO MESS HIM ALL UP.
MOTHER'S DAY GIFT AND I'M GOING  TO MESS HIM ALL UP.              [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
TO MESS HIM ALL UP.              [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
Your body was made for better             things than
rheumatoid arthritis.
Before you and your        rheumatologist move to another
treatment, ask if XELJANZ is            right for you.
XELJANZ is a small pill for              adults with
moderate to severe RA for whom   methotrexate did not work well.
XELJANZ can reduce joint pain    and swelling in as little as
two weeks, and help stop further           joint damage.
XELJANZ can lower your ability        to fight infections,
including tuberculosis.
Serious, sometimes fatal      infections, lymphoma and other
cancers have happened.
Don't start XELJANZ if you have           an infection.
Tears in the stomach or        intestines, low blood cell
counts and higher liver tests     and cholesterol levels have
happened.
Your doctor should perform blood         tests before you
start and while taking XELJANZ, and monitor certain liver tests.
Tell your doctor if you were in       a region where fungal
infections are common and if you           have had TB,
hepatitis B or C, or are prone           to infections.
XELJANZ can reduce the symptoms              of RA,
even without methotrexate, and          is also available
in a once-daily pill.
Ask about XELJANZ XR.
Now you can squeeze
a dollop of Daisy.
With Daisy squeeze sour cream.
Daisy is different than             other sour creams.
Only simple ingredients,
so it's simply pure.
Squeeze it on your favorite                dishes.
♪ Do a dollop of Daisy. ♪
Honey Nut Cheerios...
Are made with delicious honey
and real oats.
[kissing sound]
Ahhh!! Hey little guy.
I try hard to get a great shape.
This I can do, easily.
Benefiber® Healthy Shape is
a clear, taste-free,
100% natural daily fiber...
that's clinically proven to help
me feel fuller longer.
Benefiber® Healthy Shape.
This I Can Do!
Millions of you are               online right now,
searching one topic.
That will generate over           600 million results.
And if you've been             diagnosed with cancer,
searching for answers            like where to treat,
can feel even more                  overwhelming.
So start your search               with a specialist
at Cancer Treatment              Centers of America.
Start with teams of               cancer treatment
experts under one roof.
Start where specialists           use advanced genomic
testing to guide precision           cancer treatment...
...that may lead to              targeted therapies
and more treatment                    options.
Start where there's a           commitment to analyzing
the latest research and            conducting clinical
trials-to help each                patient get the
personalized cancer              care they deserve.
Start at one of the              Cancer Treatment
Centers of America               hospitals near you.
The evolution of               cancer care is here.
Learn more at              cancercenter.com/experts
Appointments available now.
♪                                >> Announcer: WE'RE SERVING UP   WEEKNIGHT WOWS, TODAY ON "THE
>> Announcer: WE'RE SERVING UP   WEEKNIGHT WOWS, TODAY ON "THE    CHEW."
WEEKNIGHT WOWS, TODAY ON "THE    CHEW."                           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
CHEW."                           [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >>> HEY EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >>> HEY EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK  TO "THE CHEW."
>>> HEY EVERYBODY, WELCOME BACK  TO "THE CHEW."                   IT IS REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK, SO
TO "THE CHEW."                   IT IS REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK, SO  I AM ANSWERING A VIEWER'S PLEA
IT IS REQUEST A RECIPE WEEK, SO  I AM ANSWERING A VIEWER'S PLEA   WITH MY MEDITERRANEAN STUFFED
I AM ANSWERING A VIEWER'S PLEA   WITH MY MEDITERRANEAN STUFFED    PEPPERS WITH A LITTLE BIT OF
WITH MY MEDITERRANEAN STUFFED    PEPPERS WITH A LITTLE BIT OF     FETA.
PEPPERS WITH A LITTLE BIT OF     FETA.                            SO HERE'S WHAT WE DID, WE
FETA.                            SO HERE'S WHAT WE DID, WE        MADE -- JUST TO BE CLEAR -- FOUR
SO HERE'S WHAT WE DID, WE        MADE -- JUST TO BE CLEAR -- FOUR OUNCES OF ROUX.
MADE -- JUST TO BE CLEAR -- FOUR OUNCES OF ROUX.                  LOOK AT IT AS A RATIO.
OUNCES OF ROUX.                  LOOK AT IT AS A RATIO.           FOUR OUNCES OF ROUX, TWO AND TWO
LOOK AT IT AS A RATIO.           FOUR OUNCES OF ROUX, TWO AND TWO ALWAYS WILL THICKEN 32 OUNCES OF
FOUR OUNCES OF ROUX, TWO AND TWO ALWAYS WILL THICKEN 32 OUNCES OF LIQUID.
ALWAYS WILL THICKEN 32 OUNCES OF LIQUID.                          SO IF YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT AS A
LIQUID.                          SO IF YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT AS A  RATIO -- JUST LOOK AT IT AS THE
SO IF YOU'RE LOOKING AT IT AS A  RATIO -- JUST LOOK AT IT AS THE  RATIO.
RATIO -- JUST LOOK AT IT AS THE  RATIO.                           YOU CAN BREAK IT DOWN OR UP ANY
RATIO.                           YOU CAN BREAK IT DOWN OR UP ANY  WAY YOU WANT.
YOU CAN BREAK IT DOWN OR UP ANY  WAY YOU WANT.                    >> 2, 2, 32.
WAY YOU WANT.                    >> 2, 2, 32.                     >> 2, 2, 32.
>> 2, 2, 32.                     >> 2, 2, 32.                     [ APPLAUSE ]
>> 2, 2, 32.                     [ APPLAUSE ]                     THEN WE TOOK THE GROUND BEEF, WE
[ APPLAUSE ]                     THEN WE TOOK THE GROUND BEEF, WE TOOK THE PINE NUTS, THE ONIONS,
THEN WE TOOK THE GROUND BEEF, WE TOOK THE PINE NUTS, THE ONIONS,  THE GARLIC, FRESH OREGANO,
TOOK THE PINE NUTS, THE ONIONS,  THE GARLIC, FRESH OREGANO,       PARSLEY, A LITTLE BIT OF COOKED
THE GARLIC, FRESH OREGANO,       PARSLEY, A LITTLE BIT OF COOKED  RICE, WE MIX IT ALL TOGETHER.
PARSLEY, A LITTLE BIT OF COOKED  RICE, WE MIX IT ALL TOGETHER.    WE STUFF THOSE BEAUTIFUL RED
RICE, WE MIX IT ALL TOGETHER.    WE STUFF THOSE BEAUTIFUL RED     PEPPERS WITH IT.
WE STUFF THOSE BEAUTIFUL RED     PEPPERS WITH IT.                 A LITTLE BIT OF "CHEW" TOMATO
PEPPERS WITH IT.                 A LITTLE BIT OF "CHEW" TOMATO    SAUCE ON THE BOTTOM, AND THEN WE
A LITTLE BIT OF "CHEW" TOMATO    SAUCE ON THE BOTTOM, AND THEN WE TOPPED IT WITH THAT FETA
SAUCE ON THE BOTTOM, AND THEN WE TOPPED IT WITH THAT FETA         BECHAMEL.
TOPPED IT WITH THAT FETA         BECHAMEL.                        WE PUT THEM IN THE OVEN,
BECHAMEL.                        WE PUT THEM IN THE OVEN,         375 DEGREES FOR ABOUT 35 MINUTES
WE PUT THEM IN THE OVEN,         375 DEGREES FOR ABOUT 35 MINUTES SO THEY GOT GOLDEN BROWN AND
375 DEGREES FOR ABOUT 35 MINUTES SO THEY GOT GOLDEN BROWN AND     DELICIOUS.
SO THEY GOT GOLDEN BROWN AND     DELICIOUS.                       >> CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THEM.
DELICIOUS.                       >> CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THEM.       DU, NA NA NA!
>> CAN'T WAIT TO SEE THEM.       DU, NA NA NA!                    [ CHEERS ]
DU, NA NA NA!                    [ CHEERS ]                       >> THERE YOU GO.
[ CHEERS ]                       >> THERE YOU GO.                 >> WOW.
>> THERE YOU GO.                 >> WOW.                          >> WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT,
>> WOW.                          >> WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT,       CLINTON?
>> WOULD YOU LOOK AT THAT,       CLINTON?                         >> SYMON, THOSE ARE BEAUTIFUL.
CLINTON?                         >> SYMON, THOSE ARE BEAUTIFUL.   YOUR STOVETOP, HOWEVER, IS
>> SYMON, THOSE ARE BEAUTIFUL.   YOUR STOVETOP, HOWEVER, IS       FILTHY.
YOUR STOVETOP, HOWEVER, IS       FILTHY.                          [ LAUGHTER ]
FILTHY.                          [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WELL, I COULDN'T FIND THAT
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WELL, I COULDN'T FIND THAT    DAMN CAT.
>> WELL, I COULDN'T FIND THAT    DAMN CAT.                        [ LAUGHTER ]
DAMN CAT.                        [ LAUGHTER ]                     PASS THESE DOWN, TELL ME WHAT
[ LAUGHTER ]                     PASS THESE DOWN, TELL ME WHAT    YOU THINK.
PASS THESE DOWN, TELL ME WHAT    YOU THINK.                       >> CARLA HALL.
YOU THINK.                       >> CARLA HALL.                   >> THANK YOU.
>> CARLA HALL.                   >> THANK YOU.                    >> LET'S HAVE A LITTLE TASTE.
>> THANK YOU.                    >> LET'S HAVE A LITTLE TASTE.    >> THE THING THAT I LOVE ABOUT
>> LET'S HAVE A LITTLE TASTE.    >> THE THING THAT I LOVE ABOUT   STUFFED PEPPERS AS I WAS SAYING
>> THE THING THAT I LOVE ABOUT   STUFFED PEPPERS AS I WAS SAYING  EARLIER IS YOU CAN REALLY
STUFFED PEPPERS AS I WAS SAYING  EARLIER IS YOU CAN REALLY        CUSTOMIZE THEM AND MAKE THEM
EARLIER IS YOU CAN REALLY        CUSTOMIZE THEM AND MAKE THEM     YOURSELF.
CUSTOMIZE THEM AND MAKE THEM     YOURSELF.                        YOU CAN USE ANY KIND OF GROUND
YOURSELF.                        YOU CAN USE ANY KIND OF GROUND   MEAT.
YOU CAN USE ANY KIND OF GROUND   MEAT.                            SOMETIMES I MAKE THEM WITH LIZ
MEAT.                            SOMETIMES I MAKE THEM WITH LIZ   WITH QUINOA, YOU KNOW, AND TAKE
SOMETIMES I MAKE THEM WITH LIZ   WITH QUINOA, YOU KNOW, AND TAKE  THE MEAT OUT.
WITH QUINOA, YOU KNOW, AND TAKE  THE MEAT OUT.                    >> OH, YOU DO?
THE MEAT OUT.                    >> OH, YOU DO?                   >> OH, YEAH.
>> OH, YOU DO?                   >> OH, YEAH.                     >> DON'T DO THAT.
>> OH, YEAH.                     >> DON'T DO THAT.                [ LAUGHTER ]
>> DON'T DO THAT.                [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IT'S DELICIOUS.
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> IT'S DELICIOUS.               >> DON'T DO THAT.
>> IT'S DELICIOUS.               >> DON'T DO THAT.                >> NO, IT'S LIKE A -- YOU CAN
>> DON'T DO THAT.                >> NO, IT'S LIKE A -- YOU CAN    MAKE A TUBULE STUFFED PEPPER
>> NO, IT'S LIKE A -- YOU CAN    MAKE A TUBULE STUFFED PEPPER     WHICH I THINK IS FANTASTIC.
MAKE A TUBULE STUFFED PEPPER     WHICH I THINK IS FANTASTIC.      >> CAN I HAVE SOME OF THE "CHEW"
WHICH I THINK IS FANTASTIC.      >> CAN I HAVE SOME OF THE "CHEW" SAUCE, PLEASE?
>> CAN I HAVE SOME OF THE "CHEW" SAUCE, PLEASE?                   >> YEAH, YOU CAN HAVE A LITTLE
SAUCE, PLEASE?                   >> YEAH, YOU CAN HAVE A LITTLE   "CHEW" SAUCE STRAIGHT FROM THE
>> YEAH, YOU CAN HAVE A LITTLE   "CHEW" SAUCE STRAIGHT FROM THE   GARDEN OF MARIO BATALI.
"CHEW" SAUCE STRAIGHT FROM THE   GARDEN OF MARIO BATALI.          >> FANTASTIC.
GARDEN OF MARIO BATALI.          >> FANTASTIC.                    [ LAUGHTER ]
>> FANTASTIC.                    [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> SEE, NOW THIS LOOKS LIKE A
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> SEE, NOW THIS LOOKS LIKE A    WEEKNIGHT MEAL AT MY HOUSE.
>> SEE, NOW THIS LOOKS LIKE A    WEEKNIGHT MEAL AT MY HOUSE.      LIKE, THE KIDS HAD TO COOK
WEEKNIGHT MEAL AT MY HOUSE.      LIKE, THE KIDS HAD TO COOK       SOMETIMES, AND THIS WOULD BE THE
LIKE, THE KIDS HAD TO COOK       SOMETIMES, AND THIS WOULD BE THE KIND OF DISH THAT WE COULD MAKE
SOMETIMES, AND THIS WOULD BE THE KIND OF DISH THAT WE COULD MAKE  BECAUSE YOU COULD PUT IT
KIND OF DISH THAT WE COULD MAKE  BECAUSE YOU COULD PUT IT         TOGETHER VERY EASY, VERY
BECAUSE YOU COULD PUT IT         TOGETHER VERY EASY, VERY         QUICKLY, RIGHT?
TOGETHER VERY EASY, VERY         QUICKLY, RIGHT?                  AND HOW'S IT TASTING, AMERICA?
QUICKLY, RIGHT?                  AND HOW'S IT TASTING, AMERICA?   >> FABULOUS.
AND HOW'S IT TASTING, AMERICA?   >> FABULOUS.                     >> IT'S DELICIOUS.
>> FABULOUS.                     >> IT'S DELICIOUS.               >> THIS IS REALLY GREAT.
>> IT'S DELICIOUS.               >> THIS IS REALLY GREAT.         IT'S REALLY, REALLY GOOD.
>> THIS IS REALLY GREAT.         IT'S REALLY, REALLY GOOD.        >> OH, MY GOD.
IT'S REALLY, REALLY GOOD.        >> OH, MY GOD.                   >> I LOVE PINE NUTS.
>> OH, MY GOD.                   >> I LOVE PINE NUTS.             RICE.
>> I LOVE PINE NUTS.             RICE.                            MEAT.
RICE.                            MEAT.                            >> IT'S REALLY HOT, SYMON.
MEAT.                            >> IT'S REALLY HOT, SYMON.       >> OH, YOU KNOW, WE DON'T SERVE
>> IT'S REALLY HOT, SYMON.       >> OH, YOU KNOW, WE DON'T SERVE  ANYTHING COLD IN MARIO BATALI'S
>> OH, YOU KNOW, WE DON'T SERVE  ANYTHING COLD IN MARIO BATALI'S  HOT FOOD CAFE.
ANYTHING COLD IN MARIO BATALI'S  HOT FOOD CAFE.                   [ LAUGHTER ]
HOT FOOD CAFE.                   [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WELL, ON THE TOPIC OF
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> WELL, ON THE TOPIC OF         EARTH --
>> WELL, ON THE TOPIC OF         EARTH --                         [ LAUGHTER ]
EARTH --                         [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> I JUST WANTED TO WATCH YOU DO
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> I JUST WANTED TO WATCH YOU DO THAT.
>> I JUST WANTED TO WATCH YOU DO THAT.                            IT WAS CUTE.
THAT.                            IT WAS CUTE.                     ALL RIGHT, I HAVE AN IDEA
IT WAS CUTE.                     ALL RIGHT, I HAVE AN IDEA        INSPIRED BY MY FAVORITE THING
ALL RIGHT, I HAVE AN IDEA        INSPIRED BY MY FAVORITE THING    FOR ME TO DO FOR MY MOM ON
INSPIRED BY MY FAVORITE THING    FOR ME TO DO FOR MY MOM ON       MOTHER'S DAY.
FOR ME TO DO FOR MY MOM ON       MOTHER'S DAY.                    WANT TO COME OVER HERE?
MOTHER'S DAY.                    WANT TO COME OVER HERE?          >> I WOULD LOVE TO.
WANT TO COME OVER HERE?          >> I WOULD LOVE TO.              >> OKAY, GREAT.
>> I WOULD LOVE TO.              >> OKAY, GREAT.                  [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> OKAY, GREAT.                  [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> OH, THAT'S ME AND MY MOM,
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> OH, THAT'S ME AND MY MOM,     TERRY.
>> OH, THAT'S ME AND MY MOM,     TERRY.                           HEY, TERRY.
TERRY.                           HEY, TERRY.                      >> HI, TERRY.
HEY, TERRY.                      >> HI, TERRY.                    >> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
>> HI, TERRY.                    >> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.           >> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.
>> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.           >> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.           SHE'S AWESOME.
>> SHE'S SO BEAUTIFUL.           SHE'S AWESOME.                   ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT I DO WITH MY
SHE'S AWESOME.                   ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT I DO WITH MY  MOM EVERY MOTHER'S DAY -- EXCEPT
ALL RIGHT, SO WHAT I DO WITH MY  MOM EVERY MOTHER'S DAY -- EXCEPT NOT THIS YEAR, BECAUSE SHE DID
MOM EVERY MOTHER'S DAY -- EXCEPT NOT THIS YEAR, BECAUSE SHE DID   IT ALREADY -- IS I GO TO HER
NOT THIS YEAR, BECAUSE SHE DID   IT ALREADY -- IS I GO TO HER     HOUSE, I HELP HER DO ALL THE
IT ALREADY -- IS I GO TO HER     HOUSE, I HELP HER DO ALL THE     PLANTING IN HER BACKYARD FOR ALL
HOUSE, I HELP HER DO ALL THE     PLANTING IN HER BACKYARD FOR ALL THE FLOWERS AND STUFF LIKE THAT.
PLANTING IN HER BACKYARD FOR ALL THE FLOWERS AND STUFF LIKE THAT. AND, YOU KNOW, WE TALK A LOT
THE FLOWERS AND STUFF LIKE THAT. AND, YOU KNOW, WE TALK A LOT     ON THIS SHOW ABOUT FRESH HERBS
AND, YOU KNOW, WE TALK A LOT     ON THIS SHOW ABOUT FRESH HERBS   AND HOW THEY REALLY DO MAKE A
ON THIS SHOW ABOUT FRESH HERBS   AND HOW THEY REALLY DO MAKE A    DIFFERENCE IN YOUR FOOD.
AND HOW THEY REALLY DO MAKE A    DIFFERENCE IN YOUR FOOD.         SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE AN INDOOR
DIFFERENCE IN YOUR FOOD.         SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE AN INDOOR HERB GARDEN WITH A CAKE STAND
SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE AN INDOOR HERB GARDEN WITH A CAKE STAND    AND SOME TEACUPS.
HERB GARDEN WITH A CAKE STAND    AND SOME TEACUPS.                >> OH, MY GOD, IT'S SO CUTE.
AND SOME TEACUPS.                >> OH, MY GOD, IT'S SO CUTE.     >> IT'S REALLY CUTE WHEN IT ALL
>> OH, MY GOD, IT'S SO CUTE.     >> IT'S REALLY CUTE WHEN IT ALL  COMES TOGETHER.
>> IT'S REALLY CUTE WHEN IT ALL  COMES TOGETHER.                  SO IF YOU GO TO THE LOCAL FLEA
COMES TOGETHER.                  SO IF YOU GO TO THE LOCAL FLEA   MARKET OR MAYBE YOU HAVE SOME OF
SO IF YOU GO TO THE LOCAL FLEA   MARKET OR MAYBE YOU HAVE SOME OF THESE IN YOUR GARAGE ALREADY,
MARKET OR MAYBE YOU HAVE SOME OF THESE IN YOUR GARAGE ALREADY,    MIX AND MATCHED TEACUPS AND
THESE IN YOUR GARAGE ALREADY,    MIX AND MATCHED TEACUPS AND      SAUCERS.
MIX AND MATCHED TEACUPS AND      SAUCERS.                         ALL YOU DO IS YOU TAKE SOME
SAUCERS.                         ALL YOU DO IS YOU TAKE SOME      PEBBLES, OR EVEN ONE BIG ROCK
ALL YOU DO IS YOU TAKE SOME      PEBBLES, OR EVEN ONE BIG ROCK    WOULD BE FINE.
PEBBLES, OR EVEN ONE BIG ROCK    WOULD BE FINE.                   YOU PUT THEM AT THE BOTTOM,
WOULD BE FINE.                   YOU PUT THEM AT THE BOTTOM,      BECAUSE THERE'S NO DRAINAGE IN
YOU PUT THEM AT THE BOTTOM,      BECAUSE THERE'S NO DRAINAGE IN   THE TEACUPS, SO YOU NEED A
BECAUSE THERE'S NO DRAINAGE IN   THE TEACUPS, SO YOU NEED A       LITTLE BIT --
THE TEACUPS, SO YOU NEED A       LITTLE BIT --                    >> YOU HAVE THE NICEST PEBBLES
LITTLE BIT --                    >> YOU HAVE THE NICEST PEBBLES   I'VE EVER SEEN.
>> YOU HAVE THE NICEST PEBBLES   I'VE EVER SEEN.                  >> THEY'RE SO SHINY.
I'VE EVER SEEN.                  >> THEY'RE SO SHINY.             I PUT THEM IN MY ROCK TUMBLER.
>> THEY'RE SO SHINY.             I PUT THEM IN MY ROCK TUMBLER.   [ LAUGHTER ]
I PUT THEM IN MY ROCK TUMBLER.   [ LAUGHTER ]                     >> OH, MY GOD, I HAD A ROCK
[ LAUGHTER ]                     >> OH, MY GOD, I HAD A ROCK      TUMBLER AS A KID.
>> OH, MY GOD, I HAD A ROCK      TUMBLER AS A KID.                >> I STILL HAVE ONE.
TUMBLER AS A KID.                >> I STILL HAVE ONE.             ALL RIGHT, SO THEN YOU BUY THESE
>> I STILL HAVE ONE.             ALL RIGHT, SO THEN YOU BUY THESE AT THE LOCAL NURSERY.
ALL RIGHT, SO THEN YOU BUY THESE AT THE LOCAL NURSERY.            HERBS AT THIS STAGE COST ABOUT
AT THE LOCAL NURSERY.            HERBS AT THIS STAGE COST ABOUT   $2.99, $3.99.
HERBS AT THIS STAGE COST ABOUT   $2.99, $3.99.                    >> WHICH IS THE SAME PRICE AS
$2.99, $3.99.                    >> WHICH IS THE SAME PRICE AS    THE PACKAGE THAT YOU GET IN THE
>> WHICH IS THE SAME PRICE AS    THE PACKAGE THAT YOU GET IN THE  STORE.
THE PACKAGE THAT YOU GET IN THE  STORE.                           >> YES, WHICH IS A ONE USE
STORE.                           >> YES, WHICH IS A ONE USE       PACKAGE, BASICALLY.
>> YES, WHICH IS A ONE USE       PACKAGE, BASICALLY.              >> EXACTLY.
PACKAGE, BASICALLY.              >> EXACTLY.                      >> AND THEN WHAT I'M GOING TO DO
>> EXACTLY.                      >> AND THEN WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS SORT OF BREAK IT UP A LITTLE
>> AND THEN WHAT I'M GOING TO DO IS SORT OF BREAK IT UP A LITTLE  BIT.
IS SORT OF BREAK IT UP A LITTLE  BIT.                             BREAK UP AT ROOT BALL, TAKE AWAY
BIT.                             BREAK UP AT ROOT BALL, TAKE AWAY ANY EXCESS SOIL RIGHT HERE.
BREAK UP AT ROOT BALL, TAKE AWAY ANY EXCESS SOIL RIGHT HERE.      AND THEN WHAT YOU CAN DO IS PUT
ANY EXCESS SOIL RIGHT HERE.      AND THEN WHAT YOU CAN DO IS PUT  THAT RIGHT IN THE TEACUPS, AND
AND THEN WHAT YOU CAN DO IS PUT  THAT RIGHT IN THE TEACUPS, AND   THEN REPLACE SOME OF THAT SOIL
THAT RIGHT IN THE TEACUPS, AND   THEN REPLACE SOME OF THAT SOIL   AROUND THE SIDE.
THEN REPLACE SOME OF THAT SOIL   AROUND THE SIDE.                 OBVIOUSLY, I'LL DO IT A LITTLE
AROUND THE SIDE.                 OBVIOUSLY, I'LL DO IT A LITTLE   BIT NEATER AT HOME FOR MOM.
OBVIOUSLY, I'LL DO IT A LITTLE   BIT NEATER AT HOME FOR MOM.      >> THANKS, ALL CLEAN.
BIT NEATER AT HOME FOR MOM.      >> THANKS, ALL CLEAN.            OKAY AND THEN, SO YOU CAN DO --
>> THANKS, ALL CLEAN.            OKAY AND THEN, SO YOU CAN DO --  THIS IS SAGE, OBVIOUSLY.
OKAY AND THEN, SO YOU CAN DO --  THIS IS SAGE, OBVIOUSLY.         AND HERE WE HAVE SOME THYME.
THIS IS SAGE, OBVIOUSLY.         AND HERE WE HAVE SOME THYME.     THOSE GROW REALLY, REALLY WELL
AND HERE WE HAVE SOME THYME.     THOSE GROW REALLY, REALLY WELL   INDOORS AS WELL AS OREGANO.
THOSE GROW REALLY, REALLY WELL   INDOORS AS WELL AS OREGANO.      SO THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU HAVE
INDOORS AS WELL AS OREGANO.      SO THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU HAVE  YOUR MIX AND MATCH TEACUPS, YOU
SO THEN WHAT YOU DO IS YOU HAVE  YOUR MIX AND MATCH TEACUPS, YOU  PUT THEM ON A CAKE STAND THAT
YOUR MIX AND MATCH TEACUPS, YOU  PUT THEM ON A CAKE STAND THAT    YOU MIGHT ALREADY OWN OR YOU CAN
PUT THEM ON A CAKE STAND THAT    YOU MIGHT ALREADY OWN OR YOU CAN FIND AT THE FLEA MARKET FOR LIKE
YOU MIGHT ALREADY OWN OR YOU CAN FIND AT THE FLEA MARKET FOR LIKE FIVE BUCKS.
FIND AT THE FLEA MARKET FOR LIKE FIVE BUCKS.                      AND THEN, IF YOUR MOM DOESN'T
FIVE BUCKS.                      AND THEN, IF YOUR MOM DOESN'T    HAVE ANY OUTDOOR SPACE, SHE CAN
AND THEN, IF YOUR MOM DOESN'T    HAVE ANY OUTDOOR SPACE, SHE CAN  PUT THIS IN A WELL LIT AREA OF
HAVE ANY OUTDOOR SPACE, SHE CAN  PUT THIS IN A WELL LIT AREA OF   THE HOUSE.
PUT THIS IN A WELL LIT AREA OF   THE HOUSE.                       OR IF THEY START TO GROW, SHE
THE HOUSE.                       OR IF THEY START TO GROW, SHE    CAN TRANSPLANT THEM OUTSIDE.
OR IF THEY START TO GROW, SHE    CAN TRANSPLANT THEM OUTSIDE.     >> LOVE THAT.
CAN TRANSPLANT THEM OUTSIDE.     >> LOVE THAT.                    [ APPLAUSE ]
>> LOVE THAT.                    [ APPLAUSE ]                     >> THE THYME, THE OREGANO, THE
[ APPLAUSE ]                     >> THE THYME, THE OREGANO, THE   SAGE, ALL WORK REALLY WELL
>> THE THYME, THE OREGANO, THE   SAGE, ALL WORK REALLY WELL       INDOORS.
SAGE, ALL WORK REALLY WELL       INDOORS.                         YOU MIGHT HAVE TO PLANT YOUR
INDOORS.                         YOU MIGHT HAVE TO PLANT YOUR     BASIL AND YOUR PARSLEY AND YOUR
YOU MIGHT HAVE TO PLANT YOUR     BASIL AND YOUR PARSLEY AND YOUR  ROSEMARY OUTSIDE, BECAUSE THOSE
BASIL AND YOUR PARSLEY AND YOUR  ROSEMARY OUTSIDE, BECAUSE THOSE  GET A LITTLE BIT BIGGER.
ROSEMARY OUTSIDE, BECAUSE THOSE  GET A LITTLE BIT BIGGER.         SO ANYWAY, IT'S A NICE IDEA FOR
GET A LITTLE BIT BIGGER.         SO ANYWAY, IT'S A NICE IDEA FOR  YOURSELF AS WELL.
SO ANYWAY, IT'S A NICE IDEA FOR  YOURSELF AS WELL.                HAPPY EARLY MOTHER'S DAY TO ALL
YOURSELF AS WELL.                HAPPY EARLY MOTHER'S DAY TO ALL  THE MOMS OUT THERE.
HAPPY EARLY MOTHER'S DAY TO ALL  THE MOMS OUT THERE.              UP NEXT, CARLA IS COOKING WITH
THE MOMS OUT THERE.              UP NEXT, CARLA IS COOKING WITH   "SCANDAL'S" DARBY STANCHFIELD.
UP NEXT, CARLA IS COOKING WITH   "SCANDAL'S" DARBY STANCHFIELD.   DON'T GO AWAY.
"SCANDAL'S" DARBY STANCHFIELD.   DON'T GO AWAY.                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DON'T GO AWAY.                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
If You've Got A Life,              You Gotta Swiffer
Type 2 diabetes, listen up.
We're not professional athletes.
But that doesn't               mean we're giving up.
I'm in this for me.
For me.
Along with diet and exercise,
FARXIGA helps                  lower blood sugar
in adults with type 2 diabetes.
Lowering A1C by                 up to 1.2 points.
Do not take if                allergic to FARXIGA.
If you experience symptoms of     a serious allergic reaction
such as rash, swelling,
difficulty breathing                or swallowing,
stop taking and seek           medical help right away.
Do not take FARXIGA if you      have severe kidney problems,
are on dialysis, or              have bladder cancer.
Tell your doctor right away
if you have blood or           red color in your urine
or pain while you urinate.
FARXIGA can cause               serious side effects
including dehydration,
genital yeast infections            in women and men,
serious urinary                 tract infections,
low blood sugar,               and kidney problems.
Stop taking FARXIGA and call        your doctor right away
if you have signs                 of ketoacidosis,
which is serious and              may lead to death.
I'm in this for my family.
I'm in this for me.
Ask your doctor about FARXIGA
and learn how you can               get it for FREE.
If you can't afford                your medication,
AstraZeneca may be able to help.
Americans - 83% try                to eat healthy.
Yet up 90% fall short in getting  key nutrients from food alone.
Let's do more.                Add One A Day Women's
complete with key             nutrients we may need.
Plus it supports                   bone health
with calcium                    and vitamin D.
One A Day Women's in             gummies and tablets.
Come.
Explore a place where you can    fly on the back of a banshee.
Walk under floating mountains.
And navigate a mystical river.
Welcome to a                world - beyond belief.
Pandora - The World of Avatar.
Only at the Walt Disney               World Resort.
♪"Good To Be Alive"♪                by Andy Grammer
♪
100% whole grains, real
chocolate chips. Quaker Chewy.
Break out the good.
>> Announcer: WE'VE GOT          WEEKNIGHT WOWS, RIGHT NOW ON     "THE CHEW."
WEEKNIGHT WOWS, RIGHT NOW ON     "THE CHEW."                      [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
"THE CHEW."                      [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> WELCOME BACK TO "THE CHEW."
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> WELCOME BACK TO "THE CHEW."   AND YOU KNOW OUR NEXT GUEST AS
>> WELCOME BACK TO "THE CHEW."   AND YOU KNOW OUR NEXT GUEST AS   ONE OF THE AMAZING ACTORS IN THE
AND YOU KNOW OUR NEXT GUEST AS   ONE OF THE AMAZING ACTORS IN THE HIT ABC SHOW "SCANDAL," BUT DID
ONE OF THE AMAZING ACTORS IN THE HIT ABC SHOW "SCANDAL," BUT DID  YOU KNOW SHE'S ALSO AMAZING IN
HIT ABC SHOW "SCANDAL," BUT DID  YOU KNOW SHE'S ALSO AMAZING IN   THE KITCHEN?
YOU KNOW SHE'S ALSO AMAZING IN   THE KITCHEN?                     SHE'S ABOUT TO SHOW OFF HER
THE KITCHEN?                     SHE'S ABOUT TO SHOW OFF HER      SKILLS HERE.
SHE'S ABOUT TO SHOW OFF HER      SKILLS HERE.                     FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME,
SKILLS HERE.                     FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME,         FINALLY, PLEASE WELCOME THE
FOR THE VERY FIRST TIME,         FINALLY, PLEASE WELCOME THE      TALENTED DARBY STANCHFIELD.
FINALLY, PLEASE WELCOME THE      TALENTED DARBY STANCHFIELD.      [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
FINALLY.                         >> FINALLY GOT YOU.              WELCOME TO "THE CHEW."
>> FINALLY GOT YOU.              WELCOME TO "THE CHEW."           >> I'M SUCH A FAN.
WELCOME TO "THE CHEW."           >> I'M SUCH A FAN.               >> THIS IS SO AWESOME TO HAVE
>> I'M SUCH A FAN.               >> THIS IS SO AWESOME TO HAVE    YOU HERE.
>> THIS IS SO AWESOME TO HAVE    YOU HERE.                        >> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.
YOU HERE.                        >> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.         >> I MEAN, WE'VE HAD SO PEOPLE.
>> THANKS FOR HAVING ME.         >> I MEAN, WE'VE HAD SO PEOPLE.  WELL, FIRST OFF, CONGRATS ON THE
>> I MEAN, WE'VE HAD SO PEOPLE.  WELL, FIRST OFF, CONGRATS ON THE 100th EPISODE OF "SCANDAL."
WELL, FIRST OFF, CONGRATS ON THE 100th EPISODE OF "SCANDAL."      AND WE'VE HAD SO MANY OF YOUR
100th EPISODE OF "SCANDAL."      AND WE'VE HAD SO MANY OF YOUR    GLADIATORS AS WELL AS THE
AND WE'VE HAD SO MANY OF YOUR    GLADIATORS AS WELL AS THE        PRESIDENT OF THE SHOW.
GLADIATORS AS WELL AS THE        PRESIDENT OF THE SHOW.           >> I KNOW, IT'S MY FIRST TIME.
PRESIDENT OF THE SHOW.           >> I KNOW, IT'S MY FIRST TIME.   >> I KNOW.
>> I KNOW, IT'S MY FIRST TIME.   >> I KNOW.                       >> SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.
>> I KNOW.                       >> SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.        >> I KNOW.
>> SO EXCITED TO BE HERE.        >> I KNOW.                       I KNOW, AND I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE
>> I KNOW.                       I KNOW, AND I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE  SO MUCH IN COMMON.
I KNOW, AND I FEEL LIKE WE HAVE  SO MUCH IN COMMON.               >> YES.
SO MUCH IN COMMON.               >> YES.                          >> YOU KNOW, WE BOTH LOVE
>> YES.                          >> YOU KNOW, WE BOTH LOVE        SOMETHING -- TEA.
>> YOU KNOW, WE BOTH LOVE        SOMETHING -- TEA.                I'M A TEA LOVER.
SOMETHING -- TEA.                I'M A TEA LOVER.                 >> YOU HAVE TO SEE THE
I'M A TEA LOVER.                 >> YOU HAVE TO SEE THE           DOCUMENTARY THAT I JUST SHOT
>> YOU HAVE TO SEE THE           DOCUMENTARY THAT I JUST SHOT     WITH PURE LEAF.
DOCUMENTARY THAT I JUST SHOT     WITH PURE LEAF.                  IT'S ON PURELEAF.COM WEBSITE,
WITH PURE LEAF.                  IT'S ON PURELEAF.COM WEBSITE,    AND IT'S ALL ABOUT -- WE WENT TO
IT'S ON PURELEAF.COM WEBSITE,    AND IT'S ALL ABOUT -- WE WENT TO A TEA ESTATE IN INDONESIA AND I
AND IT'S ALL ABOUT -- WE WENT TO A TEA ESTATE IN INDONESIA AND I  LEARNED HOW TO PICK TEA AND
A TEA ESTATE IN INDONESIA AND I  LEARNED HOW TO PICK TEA AND      DISCOVERED THAT BEAUTIFUL ART OF
LEARNED HOW TO PICK TEA AND      DISCOVERED THAT BEAUTIFUL ART OF CRAFTING PURE LEAF TEA.
DISCOVERED THAT BEAUTIFUL ART OF CRAFTING PURE LEAF TEA.          THE DEDICATION AND THE CARE THAT
CRAFTING PURE LEAF TEA.          THE DEDICATION AND THE CARE THAT GOES INTO IT.
THE DEDICATION AND THE CARE THAT GOES INTO IT.                    >> WAS IT YOUR FIRST TIME IN
GOES INTO IT.                    >> WAS IT YOUR FIRST TIME IN     INDONESIA?
>> WAS IT YOUR FIRST TIME IN     INDONESIA?                       >> IT WAS MY FIRST TIME.
INDONESIA?                       >> IT WAS MY FIRST TIME.         MY FIRST TIME THROUGH A TEA
>> IT WAS MY FIRST TIME.         MY FIRST TIME THROUGH A TEA      ESTATE.
MY FIRST TIME THROUGH A TEA      ESTATE.                          >> OH, MY GOD.
ESTATE.                          >> OH, MY GOD.                   >> AMAZING.
>> OH, MY GOD.                   >> AMAZING.                      >> AND I CAN JUST PICTURE THERE
>> AMAZING.                      >> AND I CAN JUST PICTURE THERE  LIKE ROLLING HILLS, A LUSH GREEN
>> AND I CAN JUST PICTURE THERE  LIKE ROLLING HILLS, A LUSH GREEN AND --
LIKE ROLLING HILLS, A LUSH GREEN AND --                           >> THE RAIN, THE PEOPLE, THE
AND --                           >> THE RAIN, THE PEOPLE, THE     PEOPLE IN THE VILLAGE.
>> THE RAIN, THE PEOPLE, THE     PEOPLE IN THE VILLAGE.           IT WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL
PEOPLE IN THE VILLAGE.           IT WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL        EXPERIENCE.
IT WAS THE MOST BEAUTIFUL        EXPERIENCE.                      >> WHEN YOU BROUGHT SOMETHING
EXPERIENCE.                      >> WHEN YOU BROUGHT SOMETHING    BACK WITH YOU, YOU BROUGHT A
>> WHEN YOU BROUGHT SOMETHING    BACK WITH YOU, YOU BROUGHT A     RECIPE THAT I'M REALLY EXCITED
BACK WITH YOU, YOU BROUGHT A     RECIPE THAT I'M REALLY EXCITED   TO TRY.
RECIPE THAT I'M REALLY EXCITED   TO TRY.                          TELL ME WHAT WE'RE MAKING.
TO TRY.                          TELL ME WHAT WE'RE MAKING.       >> NASI GORENG.
TELL ME WHAT WE'RE MAKING.       >> NASI GORENG.                  >> NASI GORENG.
>> NASI GORENG.                  >> NASI GORENG.                  >> IT'S BASICALLY CHICKEN FRIED
>> NASI GORENG.                  >> IT'S BASICALLY CHICKEN FRIED  RICE.
>> IT'S BASICALLY CHICKEN FRIED  RICE.                            IT'S A TRADITION INDONESIAN
RICE.                            IT'S A TRADITION INDONESIAN      DISH, AND BECAUSE I LOVE PURE
IT'S A TRADITION INDONESIAN      DISH, AND BECAUSE I LOVE PURE    LEAF TEA SO MUCH, I AM -- I'M
DISH, AND BECAUSE I LOVE PURE    LEAF TEA SO MUCH, I AM -- I'M    USING PURE LEAF AS ONE
LEAF TEA SO MUCH, I AM -- I'M    USING PURE LEAF AS ONE           INGREDIENT.
USING PURE LEAF AS ONE           INGREDIENT.                      >> OKAY.
INGREDIENT.                      >> OKAY.                         >> IT'S A VERSATILE INGREDIENT.
>> OKAY.                         >> IT'S A VERSATILE INGREDIENT.  >> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S A VERSATILE INGREDIENT.  >> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.              SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE THE RICE
>> OKAY, ALL RIGHT.              SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE THE RICE  FIRST?
SO WE'RE GOING TO MAKE THE RICE  FIRST?                           >> YES, WE'RE MAKING THE RICE
FIRST?                           >> YES, WE'RE MAKING THE RICE    FIRST.
>> YES, WE'RE MAKING THE RICE    FIRST.                           >> OKAY.
FIRST.                           >> OKAY.                         SO, WE HAVE OUR RICE, AND THEN
>> OKAY.                         SO, WE HAVE OUR RICE, AND THEN   YOU'RE GOING TO USE THE TEA.
SO, WE HAVE OUR RICE, AND THEN   YOU'RE GOING TO USE THE TEA.     >> PURE LEAF, YES.
YOU'RE GOING TO USE THE TEA.     >> PURE LEAF, YES.               TWO CUPS OF TEA TO GO WITH THE
>> PURE LEAF, YES.               TWO CUPS OF TEA TO GO WITH THE   RICE.
TWO CUPS OF TEA TO GO WITH THE   RICE.                            >> SO, ONE PART OF RICE?
RICE.                            >> SO, ONE PART OF RICE?         OKAY, SO JUST TALK ABOUT RATIOS.
>> SO, ONE PART OF RICE?         OKAY, SO JUST TALK ABOUT RATIOS. IT'S TWO TO ONE.
OKAY, SO JUST TALK ABOUT RATIOS. IT'S TWO TO ONE.                 SO, TWO PARTS LIQUID --
IT'S TWO TO ONE.                 SO, TWO PARTS LIQUID --          >> AND YOU CAN FIND THE RECIPE
SO, TWO PARTS LIQUID --          >> AND YOU CAN FIND THE RECIPE   ON PURELEAF.COM
>> AND YOU CAN FIND THE RECIPE   ON PURELEAF.COM                  >> OKAY.
ON PURELEAF.COM                  >> OKAY.                         >> YES.
>> OKAY.                         >> YES.                          >> MARIO, YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE
>> YES.                          >> MARIO, YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE   THIS.
>> MARIO, YOU'RE GOING TO LOVE   THIS.                            IT'S SPICY.
THIS.                            IT'S SPICY.                      IT'S SO --
IT'S SPICY.                      IT'S SO --                       >> IT'S SO SPICY.
IT'S SO --                       >> IT'S SO SPICY.                ARE YOU READY, MARIO?
>> IT'S SO SPICY.                ARE YOU READY, MARIO?            >> BRING IT ON.
ARE YOU READY, MARIO?            >> BRING IT ON.                  >> HE'S ALWAYS READY FOR SPICE.
>> BRING IT ON.                  >> HE'S ALWAYS READY FOR SPICE.  >> OKAY, AND YOU LET THAT SIMMER
>> HE'S ALWAYS READY FOR SPICE.  >> OKAY, AND YOU LET THAT SIMMER FOR ABOUT 15 MINUTES.
>> OKAY, AND YOU LET THAT SIMMER FOR ABOUT 15 MINUTES.            >> OKAY.
FOR ABOUT 15 MINUTES.            >> OKAY.                         >> AND SO THAT'S THE FIRST STEP.
>> OKAY.                         >> AND SO THAT'S THE FIRST STEP. >> THAT'S AWESOME.
>> AND SO THAT'S THE FIRST STEP. >> THAT'S AWESOME.               SO, OKAY.
>> THAT'S AWESOME.               SO, OKAY.                        THIS DISH OBVIOUSLY, SORT OF,
SO, OKAY.                        THIS DISH OBVIOUSLY, SORT OF,    INSPIRED YOU.
THIS DISH OBVIOUSLY, SORT OF,    INSPIRED YOU.                    HAS TRAVEL ALWAYS INSPIRED YOUR
INSPIRED YOU.                    HAS TRAVEL ALWAYS INSPIRED YOUR  COOKING?
HAS TRAVEL ALWAYS INSPIRED YOUR  COOKING?                         >> YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY MY
COOKING?                         >> YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY MY      ENVIRONMENT THAT I'M IN THAT
>> YOU KNOW, IT'S REALLY MY      ENVIRONMENT THAT I'M IN THAT     INSPIRES ME.
ENVIRONMENT THAT I'M IN THAT     INSPIRES ME.                     NOW, WE CHOP UP THE CHICKEN.
INSPIRES ME.                     NOW, WE CHOP UP THE CHICKEN.     IT'S BEEN MARINATED IN CURRY AND
NOW, WE CHOP UP THE CHICKEN.     IT'S BEEN MARINATED IN CURRY AND COCONUT OIL, AND WE'LL ADD
IT'S BEEN MARINATED IN CURRY AND COCONUT OIL, AND WE'LL ADD       SHALLOTS AND CELERY.
COCONUT OIL, AND WE'LL ADD       SHALLOTS AND CELERY.             >> IT SMELLS AMAZING.
SHALLOTS AND CELERY.             >> IT SMELLS AMAZING.            >> DOESN'T IT?
>> IT SMELLS AMAZING.            >> DOESN'T IT?                   SPICY, JUST LIKE I LIKE IT.
>> DOESN'T IT?                   SPICY, JUST LIKE I LIKE IT.      >> SPICES.
SPICY, JUST LIKE I LIKE IT.      >> SPICES.                       >> BUT I MET THE GARDENER AND
>> SPICES.                       >> BUT I MET THE GARDENER AND    I -- SO TRAVEL AS WELL, BUT ALSO
>> BUT I MET THE GARDENER AND    I -- SO TRAVEL AS WELL, BUT ALSO JUST LIKE MY NATURAL
I -- SO TRAVEL AS WELL, BUT ALSO JUST LIKE MY NATURAL             ENVIRONMENT, WHATEVER'S AROUND
JUST LIKE MY NATURAL             ENVIRONMENT, WHATEVER'S AROUND   ME.
ENVIRONMENT, WHATEVER'S AROUND   ME.                              WHATEVER I CAN PLANT AND GROW.
ME.                              WHATEVER I CAN PLANT AND GROW.   >> LOVE THAT.
WHATEVER I CAN PLANT AND GROW.   >> LOVE THAT.                    >> JUST LIKE YOUR GUYS' HERBAL
>> LOVE THAT.                    >> JUST LIKE YOUR GUYS' HERBAL   GARDEN.
>> JUST LIKE YOUR GUYS' HERBAL   GARDEN.                          >> I KNOW, WHICH IS SO CUTE.
GARDEN.                          >> I KNOW, WHICH IS SO CUTE.     WELL, I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING YOU ON
>> I KNOW, WHICH IS SO CUTE.     WELL, I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING YOU ON INSTAGRAM.
WELL, I'VE BEEN FOLLOWING YOU ON INSTAGRAM.                       HAVE TO TELL YOU.
INSTAGRAM.                       HAVE TO TELL YOU.                IN ADDITION TO YOUR AMAZING,
HAVE TO TELL YOU.                IN ADDITION TO YOUR AMAZING,     CUTE OUTFIT.
IN ADDITION TO YOUR AMAZING,     CUTE OUTFIT.                     SO MANY CUTE THINGS.
CUTE OUTFIT.                     SO MANY CUTE THINGS.             >> THANK YOU.
SO MANY CUTE THINGS.             >> THANK YOU.                    >> BUT ALSO, I MEAN, YOU
>> THANK YOU.                    >> BUT ALSO, I MEAN, YOU         ACTUALLY COOK AND YOU HAVE SOME
>> BUT ALSO, I MEAN, YOU         ACTUALLY COOK AND YOU HAVE SOME  WONDERFUL DISHES AND YOU HAD
ACTUALLY COOK AND YOU HAVE SOME  WONDERFUL DISHES AND YOU HAD     THAT BROCCOLI AND --
WONDERFUL DISHES AND YOU HAD     THAT BROCCOLI AND --             >> YES.
THAT BROCCOLI AND --             >> YES.                          WITH THE SAUCE.
>> YES.                          WITH THE SAUCE.                  OKAY, AND THEN WE ADD SOME
WITH THE SAUCE.                  OKAY, AND THEN WE ADD SOME       CHILI.
OKAY, AND THEN WE ADD SOME       CHILI.                           >> OKAY.
CHILI.                           >> OKAY.                         >> SOME CHILI SAUCE.
>> OKAY.                         >> SOME CHILI SAUCE.             >> CHILI SAUCE.
>> SOME CHILI SAUCE.             >> CHILI SAUCE.                  >> TO THE CHICKEN, ONCE IT'S ALL
>> CHILI SAUCE.                  >> TO THE CHICKEN, ONCE IT'S ALL SAUTEED, IT SMELLS -- YOU KNOW
>> TO THE CHICKEN, ONCE IT'S ALL SAUTEED, IT SMELLS -- YOU KNOW   WHAT?
SAUTEED, IT SMELLS -- YOU KNOW   WHAT?                            EVERYBODY WILL BE IMPRESSED JUST
WHAT?                            EVERYBODY WILL BE IMPRESSED JUST BY THE SMELL OF YOUR CHICKEN.
EVERYBODY WILL BE IMPRESSED JUST BY THE SMELL OF YOUR CHICKEN.    YOU KNOW HOW THAT IS.
BY THE SMELL OF YOUR CHICKEN.    YOU KNOW HOW THAT IS.            >> YEAH.
YOU KNOW HOW THAT IS.            >> YEAH.                         >> IT'S A NICE --
>> YEAH.                         >> IT'S A NICE --                >> ALL RIGHT.
>> IT'S A NICE --                >> ALL RIGHT.                    AND THEN SOME NUTMEG?
>> ALL RIGHT.                    AND THEN SOME NUTMEG?            >> SOME NUTMEG.
AND THEN SOME NUTMEG?            >> SOME NUTMEG.                  >> ALL RIGHT.
>> SOME NUTMEG.                  >> ALL RIGHT.                    WE GET THAT IN THERE.
>> ALL RIGHT.                    WE GET THAT IN THERE.            >> AND WE REALLY -- WE'VE
WE GET THAT IN THERE.            >> AND WE REALLY -- WE'VE        CHOPPED UP THE CHICKEN, MAKE
>> AND WE REALLY -- WE'VE        CHOPPED UP THE CHICKEN, MAKE     SURE IT'S THOROUGHLY COOKED.
CHOPPED UP THE CHICKEN, MAKE     SURE IT'S THOROUGHLY COOKED.     >> OH, THIS JUST LOOKS SO GOOD.
SURE IT'S THOROUGHLY COOKED.     >> OH, THIS JUST LOOKS SO GOOD.  SO, SO GOOD.
>> OH, THIS JUST LOOKS SO GOOD.  SO, SO GOOD.                     >> FLAVORS INFUSED.
SO, SO GOOD.                     >> FLAVORS INFUSED.              YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT THIS
>> FLAVORS INFUSED.              YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT THIS  DISH, TOO?
YOU KNOW WHAT'S GOOD ABOUT THIS  DISH, TOO?                       IT'S GOOD LEFTOVER.
DISH, TOO?                       IT'S GOOD LEFTOVER.              YOU KNOW, THE DISHES WHERE IT'S
IT'S GOOD LEFTOVER.              YOU KNOW, THE DISHES WHERE IT'S  LIKE IT GETS BETTER WITH --
YOU KNOW, THE DISHES WHERE IT'S  LIKE IT GETS BETTER WITH --      >> I KNOW.
LIKE IT GETS BETTER WITH --      >> I KNOW.                       IT'S LIKE OVERNIGHT --
>> I KNOW.                       IT'S LIKE OVERNIGHT --           >> YEAH, OVERNIGHT THING.
IT'S LIKE OVERNIGHT --           >> YEAH, OVERNIGHT THING.        WHAT IS THAT?
>> YEAH, OVERNIGHT THING.        WHAT IS THAT?                    OKAY.
WHAT IS THAT?                    OKAY.                            >> THAT IS LIKE EVERYTHING
OKAY.                            >> THAT IS LIKE EVERYTHING       GETTING -- SO, YOU'RE NO
>> THAT IS LIKE EVERYTHING       GETTING -- SO, YOU'RE NO         STRANGER TO ADVENTURES.
GETTING -- SO, YOU'RE NO         STRANGER TO ADVENTURES.          I MEAN, YOU'VE HAD THE ADVENTURE
STRANGER TO ADVENTURES.          I MEAN, YOU'VE HAD THE ADVENTURE IN INDONESIA.
I MEAN, YOU'VE HAD THE ADVENTURE IN INDONESIA.                    I UNDERSTAND YOUR DAD WAS, LIKE,
IN INDONESIA.                    I UNDERSTAND YOUR DAD WAS, LIKE, A CRAB FISHERMAN.
I UNDERSTAND YOUR DAD WAS, LIKE, A CRAB FISHERMAN.                >> YES, HE'S LIKE THE "DEADLIEST
A CRAB FISHERMAN.                >> YES, HE'S LIKE THE "DEADLIEST CATCH" GUY.
>> YES, HE'S LIKE THE "DEADLIEST CATCH" GUY.                      >> REALLY?
CATCH" GUY.                      >> REALLY?                       >> SERIOUSLY, LOOK AT YOU.
>> REALLY?                       >> SERIOUSLY, LOOK AT YOU.       >> YEAH, THAT'S US FISHING, AND
>> SERIOUSLY, LOOK AT YOU.       >> YEAH, THAT'S US FISHING, AND  OF COURSE, HE CATCHES THE BIGGER
>> YEAH, THAT'S US FISHING, AND  OF COURSE, HE CATCHES THE BIGGER HALIBUT, BUT YEAH.
OF COURSE, HE CATCHES THE BIGGER HALIBUT, BUT YEAH.               THAT'S OUR TRIP TO ALASKA.
HALIBUT, BUT YEAH.               THAT'S OUR TRIP TO ALASKA.       >> YOURS AS WELL.
THAT'S OUR TRIP TO ALASKA.       >> YOURS AS WELL.                YOURS AS WELL.
>> YOURS AS WELL.                YOURS AS WELL.                   >> IT'S ALSO -- YEAH.
YOURS AS WELL.                   >> IT'S ALSO -- YEAH.            ALSO PRETTY GOOD SIZE FISH,
>> IT'S ALSO -- YEAH.            ALSO PRETTY GOOD SIZE FISH,      RIGHT?
ALSO PRETTY GOOD SIZE FISH,      RIGHT?                           >> SO THIS IS YOUR RICE?
RIGHT?                           >> SO THIS IS YOUR RICE?         >> THE RICE.
>> SO THIS IS YOUR RICE?         >> THE RICE.                     >> LET ME -- I WANT TO TASTE IT.
>> THE RICE.                     >> LET ME -- I WANT TO TASTE IT. >> YES.
>> LET ME -- I WANT TO TASTE IT. >> YES.                          ISN'T THAT NICE?
>> YES.                          ISN'T THAT NICE?                 >> RIGHT?
ISN'T THAT NICE?                 >> RIGHT?                        >> YES, AND SO WE ADD THE RICE.
>> RIGHT?                        >> YES, AND SO WE ADD THE RICE.  >> YEAH.
>> YES, AND SO WE ADD THE RICE.  >> YEAH.                         >> BECAUSE IT IS CHICKEN FRIED
>> YEAH.                         >> BECAUSE IT IS CHICKEN FRIED   RICE.
>> BECAUSE IT IS CHICKEN FRIED   RICE.                            SO IT ALSO PUTS A LITTLE BIT OF
RICE.                            SO IT ALSO PUTS A LITTLE BIT OF  A CRISP TO THE RICE.
SO IT ALSO PUTS A LITTLE BIT OF  A CRISP TO THE RICE.             >> OKAY.
A CRISP TO THE RICE.             >> OKAY.                         >> AND GET THAT IN THERE.
>> OKAY.                         >> AND GET THAT IN THERE.        >> SO, WE'RE GOING TO GET IN
>> AND GET THAT IN THERE.        >> SO, WE'RE GOING TO GET IN     THERE.
>> SO, WE'RE GOING TO GET IN     THERE.                           WE'RE GOING TO STIR THIS UP AND
THERE.                           WE'RE GOING TO STIR THIS UP AND  WE'RE GOING TO LET THE RICE
WE'RE GOING TO STIR THIS UP AND  WE'RE GOING TO LET THE RICE      COOK.
WE'RE GOING TO LET THE RICE      COOK.                            WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO COOK,
COOK.                            WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO COOK, PLUS MORE FUN WITH DARBY WHEN WE
WE'RE GOING TO CONTINUE TO COOK, PLUS MORE FUN WITH DARBY WHEN WE COME BACK.
PLUS MORE FUN WITH DARBY WHEN WE COME BACK.                       DON'T GO AWAY.
COME BACK.                       DON'T GO AWAY.                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DON'T GO AWAY.                   [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> TOMORROW, WE'RE PACKING UP
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >> TOMORROW, WE'RE PACKING UP    THE STATION WAGON AND
>> TOMORROW, WE'RE PACKING UP    THE STATION WAGON AND            CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS.
THE STATION WAGON AND            CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS. CLINTON'S HANGING WITH THE
CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS. CLINTON'S HANGING WITH THE       FABULOUS CYNTHIA NIXON.
CLINTON'S HANGING WITH THE       FABULOUS CYNTHIA NIXON.          AND "GREY'S ANATOMY" STAR
FABULOUS CYNTHIA NIXON.          AND "GREY'S ANATOMY" STAR        JAMES PICKENS JR IS SHARING ONE
AND "GREY'S ANATOMY" STAR        JAMES PICKENS JR IS SHARING ONE  OF HIS FAVORITE SOUTHERN
JAMES PICKENS JR IS SHARING ONE  OF HIS FAVORITE SOUTHERN         RECIPES.
OF HIS FAVORITE SOUTHERN         RECIPES.                         IT'S THE CULINARY ADVENTURE OF A
RECIPES.                         IT'S THE CULINARY ADVENTURE OF A LIFETIME, TOMORROW ON AN ALL-NEW
IT'S THE CULINARY ADVENTURE OF A LIFETIME, TOMORROW ON AN ALL-NEW "CHEW."
LIFETIME, TOMORROW ON AN ALL-NEW "CHEW."                          [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
"CHEW."                          [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
What's going on here?
Our insurance company may not     have a Name Your Price Tool
[ shouting ]              but we got disses for days!
Your mother is so lame,
she never put any notes            in your lunch bag.
Sandwiches o-o-only.
Yeah!
Yeah, well if you use           Progressive's Name Your
Price Tool, maybe you            could use the savings
to buy a decent suit.
I got this Jaime.
♪ You could throw                 shade all day ♪
♪ But it'll never land ♪
♪ 'Cause we got the             Name Your Price Tool ♪
♪ In the palm                  of our h-a-a-and ♪
Mic drop.
Mime: Ouch.
What? It was a sweet burn.
Progressive's Name                Your Price Tool.
Word to your wallet.
(AVO) Did you know two areas
of your brain can make it hard          to lose weight?
CONTRAVE is an FDA-approved     weight-loss medicine that may
help adults who are overweight
or struggle with obesity
lose weight and keep it off.
CONTRAVE is believed to work on      two areas of the brain:
Your hunger center...
(Woman) I'm so hungry.
(AVO) To reduce hunger. And your         reward system...
(Woman) Ice cream.
French fries.
(AVO) To help control cravings.
Across three long-term studies,       CONTRAVE patients lost
approximately 2-4x more weight             than with
diet and exercise alone.
CONTRAVE is not for everyone.    One ingredient in CONTRAVE may
increase suicidal thoughts or   actions in some children, teens,
and young adults within the           first few months.
Other serious side effects     include seizures, increase in
blood pressure or heart rate,    liver damage, manic episodes,
glaucoma and allergic reactions.
Do not take with opioids.
Reduce hunger, help control               cravings.
CONTRAVE. The #1 prescribed          weight-loss brand.
Go to CONTRAVE.com.
For millions of people who      suffer from lower back pain
finding relief can seem             almost as painful.
Finally the search is over.
Drug-free Aleve                  Direct Therapy®.
A TENS device with              high intensity power
that uses chnology
once only available in             doctors' offices.
Its smart wireless design
lets you control its intensity
for deep penetrating            relief at the source.
The power of relief              is in your hands.
Aleve Direct Therapy.
Find yours in the                pain relief aisle.
>>> IT'S NOT EASY BEING A        MILLENNIAL.                      >> YOU YOUNG WHIPPERSNAPPER, YOU
MILLENNIAL.                      >> YOU YOUNG WHIPPERSNAPPER, YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY BE BUYING A
>> YOU YOUNG WHIPPERSNAPPER, YOU CAN'T POSSIBLY BE BUYING A       HOUSE.
CAN'T POSSIBLY BE BUYING A       HOUSE.                           >> THE STRUGGLE IS REAL AND SO
HOUSE.                           >> THE STRUGGLE IS REAL AND SO   ARE HIS RHYMES.
>> THE STRUGGLE IS REAL AND SO   ARE HIS RHYMES.                  >> KEEP DREAMING, BUDDY.
ARE HIS RHYMES.                  >> KEEP DREAMING, BUDDY.         KEEP DREAMING.
>> KEEP DREAMING, BUDDY.         KEEP DREAMING.                   >> NEXT "RIGHT THIS MINUTE."
This is Violet.
She's been waiting for
this moment for awhile.
A moment other kids
wouldn't think twice about.
Her first bowl of Cheerios.
Because now that Cheerios are
gluten free,
Violet, and many others
are enjoying their first
bowl today.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >>> WELCOME BACK.
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          >>> WELCOME BACK.                WE'RE IN THE KITCHEN WITH THE
>>> WELCOME BACK.                WE'RE IN THE KITCHEN WITH THE    STAR OF ABC'S "SCANDAL,"
WE'RE IN THE KITCHEN WITH THE    STAR OF ABC'S "SCANDAL,"         DARBY STANCHFIELD!
STAR OF ABC'S "SCANDAL,"         DARBY STANCHFIELD!               [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
DARBY STANCHFIELD!               [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          OKAY, SO BEFORE THE BREAK, WE
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          OKAY, SO BEFORE THE BREAK, WE    STARTED ON ONE OF HER RECIPES
OKAY, SO BEFORE THE BREAK, WE    STARTED ON ONE OF HER RECIPES    THAT LOOKS AND SMELLS SO GOOD!
STARTED ON ONE OF HER RECIPES    THAT LOOKS AND SMELLS SO GOOD!   IT'S NASI GORENG, OR FRIED RICE
THAT LOOKS AND SMELLS SO GOOD!   IT'S NASI GORENG, OR FRIED RICE  WITH CHICKEN.
IT'S NASI GORENG, OR FRIED RICE  WITH CHICKEN.                    AND, SO DARBY, YOU FINISHED IT
WITH CHICKEN.                    AND, SO DARBY, YOU FINISHED IT   WITH DRIED CHILI AND CAYENNE
AND, SO DARBY, YOU FINISHED IT   WITH DRIED CHILI AND CAYENNE     PEPPER.
WITH DRIED CHILI AND CAYENNE     PEPPER.                          >> CAYENNE, YES.
PEPPER.                          >> CAYENNE, YES.                 >> OKAY.
>> CAYENNE, YES.                 >> OKAY.                         >> JUST TO FINISH IT OFF.
>> OKAY.                         >> JUST TO FINISH IT OFF.        SO LET'S HAVE A TASTE.
>> JUST TO FINISH IT OFF.        SO LET'S HAVE A TASTE.           >> AND, WE'VE BEEN TALKING --
SO LET'S HAVE A TASTE.           >> AND, WE'VE BEEN TALKING --    WE'VE BEEN GABBING ABOUT TEA THE
>> AND, WE'VE BEEN TALKING --    WE'VE BEEN GABBING ABOUT TEA THE ENTIRE BREAK.
WE'VE BEEN GABBING ABOUT TEA THE ENTIRE BREAK.                    >> YES.
ENTIRE BREAK.                    >> YES.                          I LOVE TEA.
>> YES.                          I LOVE TEA.                      >> I KNEW YOU WOULD LOVE THIS,
I LOVE TEA.                      >> I KNEW YOU WOULD LOVE THIS,   MARIO.
>> I KNEW YOU WOULD LOVE THIS,   MARIO.                           >> I HAVE SUCH A DEEPER
MARIO.                           >> I HAVE SUCH A DEEPER          APPRECIATION FOR TEA AFTER GOING
>> I HAVE SUCH A DEEPER          APPRECIATION FOR TEA AFTER GOING TO INDONESIA, THE TEA STATE.
APPRECIATION FOR TEA AFTER GOING TO INDONESIA, THE TEA STATE.     >> IT'S SO GOOD!
TO INDONESIA, THE TEA STATE.     >> IT'S SO GOOD!                 >> OH, MY GOD.
>> IT'S SO GOOD!                 >> OH, MY GOD.                   >> THAT'S NICE.
>> OH, MY GOD.                   >> THAT'S NICE.                  >> RIGHT?
>> THAT'S NICE.                  >> RIGHT?                        >> IT'S RIGHT UP MY GAME.
>> RIGHT?                        >> IT'S RIGHT UP MY GAME.        >> YES, MA'AM.
>> IT'S RIGHT UP MY GAME.        >> YES, MA'AM.                   [ APPLAUSE ]
>> YES, MA'AM.                   [ APPLAUSE ]                     >> YOU TASTE EVERYTHING.
[ APPLAUSE ]                     >> YOU TASTE EVERYTHING.         >> YES, RIGHT?
>> YOU TASTE EVERYTHING.         >> YES, RIGHT?                   ARE YOU SWEATING YET?
>> YES, RIGHT?                   ARE YOU SWEATING YET?            >> AND COLD, WITH AN EGG ON TOP.
ARE YOU SWEATING YET?            >> AND COLD, WITH AN EGG ON TOP. COULD YOU IMAGINE?
>> AND COLD, WITH AN EGG ON TOP. COULD YOU IMAGINE?               >> THAT'S RIGHT.
COULD YOU IMAGINE?               >> THAT'S RIGHT.                 IN THE MORNING.
>> THAT'S RIGHT.                 IN THE MORNING.                  VERY VERSITILE.
IN THE MORNING.                  VERY VERSITILE.                  >> OH, MY GOD.
VERY VERSITILE.                  >> OH, MY GOD.                   I LOVE IT.
>> OH, MY GOD.                   I LOVE IT.                       GOING HOME TO MAKE THIS.
I LOVE IT.                       GOING HOME TO MAKE THIS.         >> WHEN WE WERE IN INDONESIA,
GOING HOME TO MAKE THIS.         >> WHEN WE WERE IN INDONESIA,    SHOOTING THE DOCUMENTARY, WE HAD
>> WHEN WE WERE IN INDONESIA,    SHOOTING THE DOCUMENTARY, WE HAD THIS.
SHOOTING THE DOCUMENTARY, WE HAD THIS.                            BREAKFAST, NOON AND DINNER.
THIS.                            BREAKFAST, NOON AND DINNER.      BECAUSE, IT'S JUST A VERY
BREAKFAST, NOON AND DINNER.      BECAUSE, IT'S JUST A VERY        POPULAR DISH.
BECAUSE, IT'S JUST A VERY        POPULAR DISH.                    IT'S A WAY TO BE PURPOSEFUL, YOU
POPULAR DISH.                    IT'S A WAY TO BE PURPOSEFUL, YOU KNOW, WITH LEFTOVERS.
IT'S A WAY TO BE PURPOSEFUL, YOU KNOW, WITH LEFTOVERS.            >> YES.
KNOW, WITH LEFTOVERS.            >> YES.                          >> RIGHT.
>> YES.                          >> RIGHT.                        >> OF COURSE.
>> RIGHT.                        >> OF COURSE.                    >> AND, IT'S A REALLY NICE WAY
>> OF COURSE.                    >> AND, IT'S A REALLY NICE WAY   TO SERVE FAMILIES.
>> AND, IT'S A REALLY NICE WAY   TO SERVE FAMILIES.               LIKE, GROUPS OF FAMILIES.
TO SERVE FAMILIES.               LIKE, GROUPS OF FAMILIES.        LIKE OUR CREW.
LIKE, GROUPS OF FAMILIES.        LIKE OUR CREW.                   SO I LIKE MAKING IT FOR MY
LIKE OUR CREW.                   SO I LIKE MAKING IT FOR MY       FAMILY.
SO I LIKE MAKING IT FOR MY       FAMILY.                          [ APPLAUSE ]
FAMILY.                          [ APPLAUSE ]                     YOU KNOW?
[ APPLAUSE ]                     YOU KNOW?                        >> THIS IS JUST THE RIGHT AMOUNT
YOU KNOW?                        >> THIS IS JUST THE RIGHT AMOUNT OF SPICE.
>> THIS IS JUST THE RIGHT AMOUNT OF SPICE.                        >> YEAH!
OF SPICE.                        >> YEAH!                         >> DARBY, THANK YOU!
>> YEAH!                         >> DARBY, THANK YOU!             [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
>> DARBY, THANK YOU!             [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          GUYS, MAKE SURE TO CATCH DARBY
[ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          GUYS, MAKE SURE TO CATCH DARBY   IN "SCANDAL" EVERY THURSDAY
GUYS, MAKE SURE TO CATCH DARBY   IN "SCANDAL" EVERY THURSDAY      NIGHT.
IN "SCANDAL" EVERY THURSDAY      NIGHT.                           9:00 P.M. EASTERN, RIGHT HERE ON
NIGHT.                           9:00 P.M. EASTERN, RIGHT HERE ON ABC!
9:00 P.M. EASTERN, RIGHT HERE ON ABC!                             >> UNFORTUNATELY WE'RE OUT OF
ABC!                             >> UNFORTUNATELY WE'RE OUT OF    TIME.
>> UNFORTUNATELY WE'RE OUT OF    TIME.                            A BIG THANKS TO DARBY, ALSO A
TIME.                            A BIG THANKS TO DARBY, ALSO A    BIG THANKS TO KEVIN BACON FOR
A BIG THANKS TO DARBY, ALSO A    BIG THANKS TO KEVIN BACON FOR    STOPPING BY.
BIG THANKS TO KEVIN BACON FOR    STOPPING BY.                     COME BACK TOMORROW, WE'RE
STOPPING BY.                     COME BACK TOMORROW, WE'RE        CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS
COME BACK TOMORROW, WE'RE        CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS  WITH CYNTHIA NIXON AND
CELEBRATING GREAT AMERICAN EATS  WITH CYNTHIA NIXON AND           JAMES PICKENS JR.
WITH CYNTHIA NIXON AND           JAMES PICKENS JR.                GO TO THECHEW.COM FOR ALL THINGS
JAMES PICKENS JR.                GO TO THECHEW.COM FOR ALL THINGS "CHEW."
GO TO THECHEW.COM FOR ALL THINGS "CHEW."                          AND HAVE A FABULOUS DAY,
"CHEW."                          AND HAVE A FABULOUS DAY,         EVERYBODY!
AND HAVE A FABULOUS DAY,         EVERYBODY!                       [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]
EVERYBODY!                       [ CHEERS AND APPLAUSE ]          ♪
>> Hey, everybody.               I'm hoping to make some people
I'm hoping to make some people   very rich today.
very rich today.                 Maybe million-dollar-rich.
Maybe million-dollar-rich.       Man, I love my job.
Man, I love my job.              Let's play "Who Wants To Be
Let's play "Who Wants To Be      A Millionaire."
A Millionaire."                  [cheers and applause]
[cheers and applause]            [dramatic music]
[dramatic music]                 ♪ ♪
♪ ♪                              Hey, everybody.
Hey, everybody.                  Welcome to the show.
Welcome to the show.             You guys ready to play
You guys ready to play           "Millionaire" today?
"Millionaire" today?             [cheers and applause]
[cheers and applause]            Let's do it.
Let's do it.                     Whether she's arm wrestling or
Whether she's arm wrestling or   playing checkers, our first
playing checkers, our first      contestant is always ready
contestant is always ready       to compete.
to compete.                      From Spirit Lake, Iowa,
From Spirit Lake, Iowa,          please welcome Katrina Ross.
please welcome Katrina Ross.     [cheers and applause]
[cheers and applause]            Hi, Katrina.
Hi, Katrina.                     How you doing?
How you doing?                   >> Wonderful.
>> Wonderful.                    >> Welcome.
>> Welcome.                      >> Whoo!
>> Whoo!                         [dramatic music]
[dramatic music]                 >> Welcome to "Millionaire."
>> Welcome to "Millionaire."     >> Thank you.
>> Thank you.                    It's so good to be here.
It's so good to be here.         >> You are competitive?
>> You are competitive?          >> I am so competitive.
>> I am so competitive.          >> Almost to a fault?
>> Almost to a fault?            >> To a fault.
>> To a fault.                   To a fault, I'm passing it on
To a fault, I'm passing it on    to my next generation.
to my next generation.           >> Okay, you have a
>> Okay, you have a              ten-month-old son?
ten-month-old son?               >> I do, Luke, yes.
>> I do, Luke, yes.              >> Luke.
>> Luke.                         >> Yes, and he's starting
>> Yes, and he's starting        to crawl.
to crawl.                        >> Yes.
>> Yes.                          >> And we actually just entered
>> And we actually just entered  him in a crawl-off competition.
him in a crawl-off competition.  >> Where would one find a
>> Where would one find a        crawl-off competition?
crawl-off competition?           >> You know, it was during
>> You know, it was during       halftime of a basketball game.
halftime of a basketball game.   >> Okay.
>> Okay.                         >> Uh-huh.
>> Uh-huh.                       >> And they said, "Bring your
>> And they said, "Bring your    babies out..."
babies out..."                   >> Said, "Bring your babies out,
>> Said, "Bring your babies out, we're gonna have them crawl."
we're gonna have them crawl."    We practiced the week ahead
We practiced the week ahead      of time.
of time.                         He was ready to go.
He was ready to go.              >> You practiced?
>> You practiced?                I mean, they just do
I mean, they just do             that, anyway.
that, anyway.                    I mean, he just crawls.
I mean, he just crawls.          >> They do, but they
>> They do, but they             get distracted.
get distracted.                  >> That's not practice.
>> That's not practice.          >> They get distracted, so I
>> They get distracted, so I     wanted to make sure he was
wanted to make sure he was       focused, he was fast,
focused, he was fast,            ready to go.
ready to go.                     >> I hate it when ten-month-olds
>> I hate it when ten-month-olds don't focus.
don't focus.                     >> I know, it's the worst.
>> I know, it's the worst.       >> Like, "Come on."
>> Like, "Come on."              >> It's the worst.
>> It's the worst.               Exactly, right?
Exactly, right?                  >> "Act your age."
>> "Act your age."               >> Yeah, yeah.
>> Yeah, yeah.                   >> Wait, never mind.
>> Wait, never mind.             Anyway, well, hopefully you can
Anyway, well, hopefully you can  focus today, because we have
focus today, because we have     a big objective ahead.
a big objective ahead.           That is $1 million.
That is $1 million.              Let me tell ya...
Let me tell ya...                Let me tell ya what you're
Let me tell ya what you're       up against.
up against.                      14 questions.
14 questions.                    The money values growing from
The money values growing from    $500 all the way up to that
$500 all the way up to that      $1 million.
$1 million.                      [cheers and applause]
[cheers and applause]            Every question you answer
Every question you answer        correctly moves you one step
correctly moves you one step     closer to that top prize.
closer to that top prize.        Remember, at any time you can
Remember, at any time you can    walk away with the money you've
walk away with the money you've  earned up to that point.
earned up to that point.         If you give me an incorrect
If you give me an incorrect      answer, you walk away
answer, you walk away            with nothing.
with nothing.                    That is, until you get to those
That is, until you get to those  two thresholds: $5,000,
two thresholds: $5,000,          then again at $50,000.
then again at $50,000.           Also, you have your
Also, you have your              three lifelines.
three lifelines.                 "Ask the Audience," they can
"Ask the Audience," they can     help you out on a question.
help you out on a question.      There's the "50/50," we'll take
There's the "50/50," we'll take  away two incorrect answers.
away two incorrect answers.      And your "Plus One," which
And your "Plus One," which       you're gonna tell me about.
you're gonna tell me about.      Who's here to help you today?
Who's here to help you today?    >> I brought my dad here to
>> I brought my dad here to      help me, Dave.
help me, Dave.                   [cheers and applause]
[cheers and applause]            >> Sometimes a girl just needs
>> Sometimes a girl just needs   her dad.
her dad.                         >> Sometimes a girl needs
>> Sometimes a girl needs        her dad.
her dad.                         He is my secret weapon.
He is my secret weapon.          And I also have my wife,
And I also have my wife,         Kristy, here.
Kristy, here.                    >> Good to have you both.
>> Good to have you both.        Dave, good to have you.
Dave, good to have you.          Well, hopefully they're just
Well, hopefully they're just     gonna sit there and watch you
gonna sit there and watch you    win $1 million.
win $1 million.                  >> That's what I'm hoping.
>> That's what I'm hoping.       >> Are you ready to go?
>> Are you ready to go?          >> Oh, I think so, let's do it.
>> Oh, I think so, let's do it.  >> Let's do it.
>> Let's do it.                  Good luck.
Good luck.                       Let's play "Who Wants To Be
Let's play "Who Wants To Be      A Millionaire."
A Millionaire."                  [cheers and applause]
[cheers and applause]            [dramatic musical flourish]
[dramatic musical flourish]      ♪ ♪
♪ ♪                              We start with the $500 question.
We start with the $500 question. >> All right.
>> All right.                    >> A fundamental principle of
>> A fundamental principle of    medical ethics,
medical ethics,                  "primum non nocere" is a Latin
"primum non nocere" is a Latin   phrase meaning that first and
phrase meaning that first and    foremost, doctors should what?
>> Whew, okay, so...             I know part of the oath that
I know part of the oath that     doctors take includes
doctors take includes            "do no harm," so I'm going to
"do no harm," so I'm going to    say B, final answer.
say B, final answer.             >> And they really shouldn't
>> And they really shouldn't     giggle, either.
giggle, either.                  >> I hope not.
>> I hope not.                   >> But you're right.
>> But you're right.             Do no harm.
Do no harm.                      >> Whoo!
>> Whoo!                         Whoo-hoo!
Whoo-hoo!                        >> Just like that, you're on
>> Just like that, you're on     the board, $500.
the board, $500.                 >> That's the most money I've
>> That's the most money I've    ever won in my life, so...
ever won in my life, so...       >> That's it.
>> That's it.                    >> Whew, I'm good.
>> Whew, I'm good.               >> We should be done.
>> We should be done.            We're gonna take a timeout,
We're gonna take a timeout,      and we'll be back--no.
and we'll be back--no.           >> No, let's keep going.
>> No, let's keep going.         >> You know what?
>> You know what?                Let's keep going.
Let's keep going.                We're here.
We're here.                      >> That's right.
>> That's right.                 >> $1,000 question, here you go.
>> $1,000 question, here you go. A tourism site for the
A tourism site for the           South Pacific's Cook Islands
South Pacific's Cook Islands     credits the locale's beautiful
credits the locale's beautiful   views to its unofficial ban on
views to its unofficial ban on   buildings taller than a what?
>> Buildings can be no taller    than a coconut tree.
than a coconut tree.             D, final answer.
D, final answer.                 >> Makes sense, you're right.
>> Makes sense, you're right.    [cheers and applause]
[cheers and applause]            There you go.
There you go.                    >> All right.
>> All right.                    >> $1,000 in the bank.
>> $1,000 in the bank.           Now a chance to get to $2,000
Now a chance to get to $2,000    with this question.
with this question.              Noting that the latter type
Noting that the latter type      spares "furniture and guests
spares "furniture and guests     from unintended blows,"
from unintended blows,"          Party City's website offers
Party City's website offers      a selection of "traditional"
a selection of "traditional"     and "pull string" what?
>> Only one that you are trying  to hit--besides clowns,
to hit--besides clowns,          'cause I hate clowns--would be
'cause I hate clowns--would be   C, piñatas, final answer.
C, piñatas, final answer.        >> 100% correct.
>> 100% correct.                 >> Whew!
>> Whew!                         [cheers and applause]
>> $2,000.                       $3,000 question.
$3,000 question.                 >> Okay, whew.
>> Okay, whew.                   >> The infamous Sony hack of
>> The infamous Sony hack of     2014 revealed that which
2014 revealed that which         celebrity once used
celebrity once used              batmansenior@mac.com
batmansenior@mac.com             as his email address?